英文字幕：Lesson 50.
中文字幕：课50。
英文字幕：Taken for a ride.
中文字幕：被带去兜风。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why did the writer not get off the bus at Woodford Green?
中文字幕：为什么这位作家没有在伍德福德格林下车？
英文字幕：I love travelling in the country, but I don't like losing my way.
中文字幕：我喜欢在乡下旅行，但我不喜欢迷路。
英文字幕：I went on an excursion recently, but my trip took me longer than I expected.
中文字幕：我最近去远足了，但我的旅行比我预期的要长。
英文字幕：I'm going to Woodford Green.
中文字幕：我要去伍德福德绿地。
英文字幕：I said to the conductor as I got on the bus, but I don't know where it is.
中文字幕：我上车时对售票员说，但我不知道它在哪里。
英文字幕：I'll tell you where to get off.
中文字幕：我会告诉你在哪里下车。
英文字幕：Answered the conductor.
中文字幕：列车长回答。
英文字幕：I sat in the front of the bus to get a good view of the countryside.
中文字幕：我坐在公共汽车前面，以便能很好地欣赏乡村的景色。
英文字幕：After some time the bus stopped.
中文字幕：过了一会儿，公共汽车停了下来。
英文字幕：Looking round I realised with a shock that I was the only passenger left on the bus.
中文字幕：环顾四周，我震惊地意识到，我是公共汽车上唯一剩下的乘客。
英文字幕：You'll have to get off here, the conductor said.
中文字幕：你必须在这里下车，售票员说。
英文字幕：This is as far as we go.
中文字幕：这是我们目前所能达到的极限。
英文字幕：Is this Woodford Green?
中文字幕：这是伍德福德·格林吗？
英文字幕：I asked.
中文字幕：我问。
英文字幕：Oh dear!
中文字幕：哦，天哪！
英文字幕：Said the conductor suddenly.
中文字幕：列车员突然说。
英文字幕：I forgot to put you off.
中文字幕：我忘了耽误你。
英文字幕：It doesn't matter, I said.
中文字幕：没关系，我说。
英文字幕：I'll get off here.
中文字幕：我在这里下车。
英文字幕：We're going back now, said the conductor.
中文字幕：我们现在要回去了，售票员说。
英文字幕：Well in that case, I prefer to stay on the bus.
中文字幕：既然如此，我宁愿呆在公共汽车上。
英文字幕：I answered.
中文字幕：我回答。