英文字幕：Lesson 49.
中文字幕：课49。
英文字幕：The end of a dream.
中文字幕：一个梦的结束。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：How did the dream end?
中文字幕：梦是怎么结束的？
英文字幕：Tired of sleeping on the floor, a young man in Tehran saved up for years to buy a real
中文字幕：德黑兰的一名年轻人厌倦了睡在地板上，攒了多年钱买了一套真正的
英文字幕：bed.
中文字幕：床。
英文字幕：For the first time in his life, he became the proud owner of a bed which had springs
中文字幕：他有生以来第一次自豪地拥有了一张有弹簧的床
英文字幕：and a mattress.
中文字幕：还有床垫。
英文字幕：Because the weather was very hot, he carried the bed onto the roof of his house.
中文字幕：因为天气很热，他把床搬到屋顶上。
英文字幕：He slept very well for the first two nights, but on the third night a storm blew up.
中文字幕：前两个晚上他睡得很好，但第三天晚上，一场风暴袭来。
英文字幕：A gust of wind swept the bed off the roof and sent it crashing into the courtyard below.
中文字幕：一阵风把床从屋顶上刮下来，撞到下面的院子里。
英文字幕：The young man did not wake up until the bed had struck the ground.
中文字幕：直到床撞到地上，年轻人才醒过来。
英文字幕：Although the bed was smashed to pieces, the man was miraculously unheard.
中文字幕：尽管床被砸成了碎片，但这个人却奇迹般地没有被听到。
英文字幕：When he woke up, he was still on the mattress.
中文字幕：当他醒来时，他还在床垫上。
英文字幕：Blancing at the bits of wood and metaled at lay around him, the man sadly picked up the
中文字幕：那人看到周围躺着的木头和金属碎片，顿时镇定下来，悲伤地捡起了
英文字幕：mattress and carried it into his house.
中文字幕：床垫，并把它带进了他的房子。
英文字幕：After he had put it on the floor, he promptly went to sleep again.
中文字幕：他把它放在地板上后，立刻又睡着了。