英文字幕：Lesson 30
中文字幕：第30课
英文字幕：Football or Polo?
中文字幕：足球还是马球？
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What happened to the man in the boat?
中文字幕：船上的那个人怎么了？
英文字幕：The whale is a small river that cuts across the park near my home.
中文字幕：鲸鱼是一条小河，穿过我家附近的公园。
英文字幕：I like sitting by the whale on fine afternoons.
中文字幕：我喜欢在晴朗的下午坐在鲸鱼旁边。
英文字幕：It was warm last Sunday, so I went and sat on the river bank as usual.
中文字幕：上星期天很暖和，所以我像往常一样去河边坐了下来。
英文字幕：Some children were playing games on the bank, and there were some people rowing on the river.
中文字幕：一些孩子在岸边玩游戏，还有一些人在河上划船。
英文字幕：Suddenly, one of the children kicked a ball very hard, and it went towards a passing boat.
中文字幕：突然，其中一个孩子狠狠地踢了一个球，球朝一艘经过的船飞去。
英文字幕：Some people on the bank called out to the man in the boat, but he did not hear them.
中文字幕：岸上的一些人向船上的人喊道，但他没有听到。
英文字幕：The ball struck him so hard that he nearly fell into the water.
中文字幕：球重重地打在他身上，他差点掉进水里。
英文字幕：I turned to look at the children, but there weren't any in sight. They had all run away.
中文字幕：我转过身去看孩子们，但一个也没有。他们都跑掉了。
英文字幕：The man laughed when he realised what had happened.
中文字幕：当那人意识到发生了什么事时，他笑了。
英文字幕：He called out to the children and threw the ball back to the bank.
中文字幕：他大声喊着孩子们，把球扔回岸边。