英文字幕：Lesson 63. She was not amused.
中文字幕：课63。她没有被逗乐。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why did Jenny want to leave the wedding reception?
中文字幕：为什么珍妮想离开婚宴？
英文字幕：Jeremy Hampton has a large circle of friends and is very popular at parties.
中文字幕：杰里米·汉普顿有很多朋友，在聚会上很受欢迎。
英文字幕：Everybody admires him for his great sense of humour.
中文字幕：大家都钦佩他的幽默感。
英文字幕：Everybody that is except his six-year-old daughter, Jenny.
中文字幕：除了他六岁的女儿珍妮。
英文字幕：Recently, one of Jeremy's closest friends asked him to make a speech at a wedding reception.
中文字幕：最近，Jeremy的一位密友邀请他在婚宴上发表演讲。
英文字幕：This is the sort of thing that Jeremy loves.
中文字幕：这正是Jeremy所钟爱的。
英文字幕：He prepared the speech carefully and went to the wedding with Jenny.
中文字幕：他精心准备了演讲稿，和珍妮一起去参加了婚礼。
英文字幕：He had included a large number of funny stories in the speech.
中文字幕：他在演讲中加入了大量有趣的故事。
英文字幕：And of course, it was a great success.
中文字幕：当然，这是一个巨大的成功。
英文字幕：As soon as he had finished, Jenny told him she wanted to go home.
中文字幕：他一讲完，珍妮就告诉他她想回家。
英文字幕：Jeremy was a little disappointed by this, but he did as his daughter asked.
中文字幕：杰里米对此有点失望，但他还是按照女儿的要求做了。
英文字幕：On the way home, he asked Jenny if she had enjoyed the speech.
中文字幕：在回家的路上，他问珍妮是否喜欢这次演讲。
英文字幕：To his surprise, she said she hadn't.
中文字幕：令他惊讶的是，她说她没有。
英文字幕：Jeremy asked her why this was so.
中文字幕：Jeremy问她为什么会这样。
英文字幕：And she told him that she did not like to see so many people laughing at him.
中文字幕：她告诉他，她不喜欢看到这么多人嘲笑他。