英文字幕：Lesson 42. Not very musical.
中文字幕：课42。不太有音乐性。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What happened when the snake charmer began to play jazz?
中文字幕：当耍蛇人开始演奏爵士乐时发生了什么？
英文字幕：As we had had a long walk through one of the markets of Old Delhi,
中文字幕：我们在旧德里的一个市场里走了很长一段路，
英文字幕：we stopped at a square to have a rest.
中文字幕：我们在一个广场停下来休息。
英文字幕：After a time we noticed a snake charmer with two large baskets
中文字幕：过了一会儿，我们注意到一个拿着两个大篮子的耍蛇人
英文字幕：at the other side of the square, so we went to have a look at him.
中文字幕：在广场的另一边，所以我们去看了他一眼。
英文字幕：As soon as he saw us, he picked up a long pipe,
中文字幕：他一看见我们，就拿起一根长烟斗，
英文字幕：which was covered with coins and opened one of the baskets.
中文字幕：里面装满了硬币，打开了一个篮子。
英文字幕：When he began to play a tune, we had our first glimpse of the snake.
中文字幕：当他开始演奏曲子时，我们第一眼看到了那条蛇。
英文字幕：It rose out of the basket and began to follow the movements of the pipe.
中文字幕：它从篮子里爬出来，开始跟着管子的运动。
英文字幕：We were very much surprised when the snake charmer suddenly began to play jazz
中文字幕：当耍蛇人突然开始演奏爵士乐时，我们非常惊讶
英文字幕：and modern pop songs.
中文字幕：以及现代流行歌曲。
英文字幕：The snake, however, continued to dance slowly.
中文字幕：然而，蛇继续慢慢地跳舞。
英文字幕：It obviously could not tell the difference between Indian music and jazz.
中文字幕：它显然无法区分印度音乐和爵士乐。