英文字幕：Lesson 52. A pretty carpet. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课52。漂亮的地毯。先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What is the writer's carpet made of? We have just moved into a new house and I have
中文字幕：这位作家的地毯是什么做的？我们刚搬进新房子，我
英文字幕：been working hard all morning. I have been trying to get my new room in order.
中文字幕：整个上午都在努力工作。我一直在努力整理我的新房间。
英文字幕：This has not been easy because I own over a thousand books. To make matters worse, the
中文字幕：这并不容易，因为我有一千多本书。更糟糕的是
英文字幕：room is rather small. So I have temporarily put my books on the floor. At the moment, they
中文字幕：房间相当小。所以我暂时把书放在地板上。目前，他们
英文字幕：cover every inch of floor space and I actually have to walk on them to get in or out of the
中文字幕：覆盖了每一寸地板空间，我实际上必须走在上面才能进出
英文字幕：room. A short while ago, my sister helped me to carry one of my old bookcases up the stairs.
中文字幕：房间。不久前，我姐姐帮我把一个旧书架搬上楼。
英文字幕：She went into my room and got a big surprise when she saw all those books on the floor.
中文字幕：她走进我的房间，当她看到地板上的那些书时，大吃一惊。
英文字幕：This is the prettiest carpet I have ever seen. She said. She gazed at it for some time and then added.
中文字幕：这是我见过的最漂亮的地毯。她说。她盯着它看了一会儿，然后补充道。
英文字幕：You don't need bookcases at all. You can sit here in your spare time and read the carpet.
中文字幕：你根本不需要书架。你可以在业余时间坐在这里看地毯。