英文字幕：Lesson 38
中文字幕：第38课
英文字幕：Everything except the weather
中文字幕：除了天气之外的一切
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答以下问题
英文字幕：Why did Harrison sell his house so quickly?
中文字幕：为什么哈里森这么快就卖掉了房子？
英文字幕：My old friend Harrison had lived in the Mediterranean for many years
中文字幕：我的老朋友哈里森在地中海生活了很多年
英文字幕：before he returned to England
中文字幕：在他回到英国之前
英文字幕：He had often dreamed of retiring in England
中文字幕：他经常梦想着在英国退休
英文字幕：and had planned to settle down in the country
中文字幕：并计划在该国定居
英文字幕：He had no sooner returned than he bought a house and went to live there
中文字幕：他一回来就买了一栋房子，住在那里
英文字幕：Almost immediately he began to complain about the weather
中文字幕：他几乎立刻开始抱怨天气
英文字幕：For even though it was still summer, it rained continually
中文字幕：因为虽然还是夏天，雨却一直下个不停
英文字幕：and it was often bitterly cold
中文字幕：而且天气经常冷得要命
英文字幕：After so many years of sunshine, Harrison got a shock
中文字幕：经过这么多年的阳光，哈里森大吃一惊
英文字幕：He acted as if he had never lived in England before
中文字幕：他表现得好像以前从未在英国生活过
英文字幕：In the end, it was more than he could bear
中文字幕：最后，他受不了了
英文字幕：He had hardly had time to settle down when he sold the house and left the country
中文字幕：他还没来得及安顿下来，就卖掉了房子，离开了这个国家
英文字幕：The dream he had had for so many years ended there
中文字幕：他多年来的梦想到此为止
英文字幕：Harrison had thought of everything except the weather
中文字幕：除了天气，哈里森什么都想了