英文字幕：Listen 76. April Fool's Day. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：听76。愚人节。先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What was the joke? To end our special news bulletin said the voice of the television
中文字幕：笑话是什么？电视台的声音说，结束我们的特别新闻简报
英文字幕：announcer. We are going over to the macaroni fields of Calabria. Macaroni has been grown
中文字幕：播音员。我们要去卡拉布里亚的通心粉田。通心粉已经种好了
英文字幕：in this area for over 600 years. Two of the leading growers, Giuseppe Moldova and Ricardo
中文字幕：在这个地区已经有600多年了。两家领先的种植者，Giuseppe Moldova和Ricardo
英文字幕：Brabante, tell me that they have been expecting a splendid crop this year and harvesting has
中文字幕：布拉班特，告诉我，他们一直在期待今年的丰收，收获已经
英文字幕：begun earlier than usual. Here you can see two workers who between them have just finished
中文字幕：比平时开始得早。在这里，你可以看到两个工人刚刚完成
英文字幕：cutting three cart loads of golden brown macaroni stalks. The whole village has been working
中文字幕：切下三车金棕色通心粉茎。整个村子都在工作
英文字幕：day and night, gathering and threshing this year's crop before the September rains. On the
中文字幕：日夜不停，在九月降雨前收割和脱粒今年的作物。上
英文字幕：right you can see Mrs. Brabante herself. She has been helping her husband for 30 years now.
中文字幕：好的，你可以看到布拉班特夫人本人。她已经帮助丈夫30年了。
英文字幕：Mrs. Brabante is talking to the manager of the local factory where the crop is processed.
中文字幕：布拉班特夫人正在和加工作物的当地工厂的经理谈话。
英文字幕：This last scene shows you what will happen at the end of the harvest. The famous Calabrian
中文字幕：最后一个场景向您展示了收获结束时会发生什么。著名的卡拉布里亚
英文字幕：macaroni eating competition. Senior Fratelli, the present champion, has won it every year since 1991.
中文字幕：通心粉吃比赛。现任冠军老弗拉泰利自1991年以来每年都获得冠军。
英文字幕：And that ends our special bulletin for today, Thursday, April the 1st. We're now going back to the studio.
中文字幕：今天，4月1日，星期四，我们的特别报道到此结束。我们现在要回演播室了。