英文字幕：Lesson 53
中文字幕：第53课
英文字幕：Hot snake
中文字幕：热蛇
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What caused the fire?
中文字幕：火灾的起因是什么？
英文字幕：At last, firemen have put out a big forest fire in California.
中文字幕：最后，消防员扑灭了加利福尼亚州的一场大火。
英文字幕：Since then, they have been trying to find out how the fire began.
中文字幕：从那以后，他们一直在试图找出火灾是如何开始的。
英文字幕：Forest fires are often caused by broken glass or by cigarette ends,
中文字幕：森林火灾通常是由碎玻璃或烟头引起的，
英文字幕：which people carelessly throw away.
中文字幕：人们不小心扔掉了。
英文字幕：Yesterday, the firemen examined the ground carefully,
中文字幕：昨天，消防员仔细检查了地面，
英文字幕：but were not able to find any broken glass.
中文字幕：但找不到任何碎玻璃。
英文字幕：They were also quite sure that a cigarette end did not start the fire.
中文字幕：他们也很确定不是烟头引起的火灾。
英文字幕：This morning, however, a firemen accidentally discovered the cause.
中文字幕：然而，今天早上，一名消防员意外发现了原因。
英文字幕：He noticed the remains of a snake, which was wound round the electric wires of a 16,000-volt power line.
中文字幕：他注意到一条蛇的残骸，这条蛇缠绕在16000伏电力线的电线上。
英文字幕：In this way, he was able to solve the mystery.
中文字幕：就这样，他解开了这个谜。
英文字幕：The explanation was simple, but very unusual.
中文字幕：解释很简单，但很不寻常。
英文字幕：A bird had snatched up the snake from the ground and then dropped it onto the wires.
中文字幕：一只鸟从地上抓起蛇，然后把它扔到电线上。
英文字幕：The snake then wound itself round the wires.
中文字幕：然后，蛇把自己缠绕在电线上。
英文字幕：When it did so, it sensed sparks down to the ground,
中文字幕：当它这样做时，它感觉到地面上有火花，
英文字幕：and these immediately started a fire.
中文字幕：这些立刻引发了火灾。