英文字幕：Lesson 54. Sticky fingers. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课54。手指黏糊糊的。先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What two interruptions did the writer have?
中文字幕：作者受到了哪两次干扰？
英文字幕：After breakfast, I sent the children to school and then I went to the shops. It was still
中文字幕：早餐后，我送孩子们去上学，然后去了商店。它还是
英文字幕：early when I returned home. The children were at school, my husband was at work and the house was quiet.
中文字幕：我回家的时候很早。孩子们在上学，我丈夫在上班，房子里很安静。
英文字幕：So I decided to make some meat pies. In a short time I was busy mixing butter and flour and my hands
中文字幕：所以我决定做些肉馅饼。很快，我就忙着用手搅拌黄油和面粉了
英文字幕：were soon covered with sticky pastry. At exactly that moment the telephone rang.
中文字幕：很快就被黏糊糊的糕点覆盖了。就在那一刻，电话铃响了。
英文字幕：Nothing could have been more annoying. I picked up the receiver between two sticky fingers
中文字幕：没有什么比这更烦人的了。我用两个黏糊糊的手指拿起听筒
英文字幕：and was dismayed when I recognised the voice of Helen Bates. It took me ten minutes to persuade her to ring back later.
中文字幕：当我认出海伦·贝茨的声音时，我很沮丧。我花了十分钟才说服她稍后再打来。
英文字幕：At last I hung up the receiver. What a mess! There was pastry on my fingers, on the telephone
中文字幕：最后我挂断了听筒。真是一团糟！我的手指上和电话里都沾着糕点
英文字幕：and on the door knobs. I had no sooner got back to the kitchen than the doorbell rang,
中文字幕：在门把手上。我刚回到厨房，门铃就响了，
英文字幕：loud enough to wake the dead. This time it was the postman and he wanted me to sign for a registered letter.
中文字幕：声音大到足以吵醒死者。这次是邮递员，他想让我签收一封挂号信。