英文字幕：Lesson 84. On strike.
中文字幕：课84。罢工。
英文字幕：First, listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：首先，听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Who will be driving the buses next week?
中文字幕：下周谁将驾驶公共汽车？
英文字幕：Busmen have decided to go on strike next week.
中文字幕：公共汽车司机决定下周罢工。
英文字幕：The strike is due to begin on Tuesday.
中文字幕：罢工将于周二开始。
英文字幕：No one knows how long it will last.
中文字幕：没有人知道它会持续多久。
英文字幕：The busmen have stated that the strike will continue until general agreement is reached about pay and working conditions.
中文字幕：公共汽车司机表示，罢工将持续到就工资和工作条件达成普遍协议为止。
英文字幕：Most people believe that the strike will last for at least a week.
中文字幕：大多数人认为罢工将持续至少一周。
英文字幕：Many owners of private cars are going to offer free rides to people on their way to work.
中文字幕：许多私家车车主将为上班途中的人们提供免费乘车服务。
英文字幕：This will relieve pressure on the trains to some extent.
中文字幕：这将在一定程度上缓解列车的压力。
英文字幕：Meanwhile, a number of university students have volunteered to drive buses while the strike lasts.
中文字幕：与此同时，一些大学生自愿在罢工期间驾驶公共汽车。
英文字幕：All the students are expert drivers, but before they drive any of the buses, they will have to pass a special test.
中文字幕：所有的学生都是熟练的司机，但在驾驶任何一辆公共汽车之前，他们必须通过一项特殊的测试。
英文字幕：The students are going to take the test in two days time.
中文字幕：学生们将在两天后参加考试。
英文字幕：Even so, people are going to find it difficult to get to work.
中文字幕：即便如此，人们还是会发现很难去上班。
英文字幕：But so far, the public has expressed its gratitude to the students in letters to the press.
中文字幕：但到目前为止，公众已经在给媒体的信中表达了对学生的感激之情。
英文字幕：Only one or two people have objected that the students will drive too fast.
中文字幕：只有一两个人反对学生开车太快。