英文字幕：Lesson 58. A blessing in disguise?
中文字幕：课58。因祸得福？
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why does the vicar refuse to cut down the tree?
中文字幕：牧师为什么拒绝砍倒这棵树？
英文字幕：The tiny village of Frinley is said to possess a cursed tree.
中文字幕：据说弗林利这个小村庄有一棵被诅咒的树。
英文字幕：Because the tree was mentioned in a newspaper,
中文字幕：因为报纸上提到了这棵树，
英文字幕：the number of visitors to Frinley has now increased.
中文字幕：弗林利的游客数量现在有所增加。
英文字幕：The tree was planted near the church 50 years ago,
中文字幕：这棵树是50年前种在教堂附近的，
英文字幕：but it is only in recent years that it has gained an evil reputation.
中文字幕：但直到最近几年，它才获得了坏名声。
英文字幕：It is said that if anyone touches the tree, he will have bad luck.
中文字幕：据说，如果有人碰了这棵树，他会倒霉的。
英文字幕：If he picks a leaf, he will die.
中文字幕：如果他摘一片叶子，他就会死。
英文字幕：Many villages believe that the tree has already claimed a number of victims.
中文字幕：许多村庄认为，这棵树已经造成了一些受害者。
英文字幕：The vicar has been asked to have the tree cut down,
中文字幕：牧师被要求砍倒这棵树，
英文字幕：but so far he has refused.
中文字幕：但到目前为止，他拒绝了。
英文字幕：He has pointed out that the tree is a useful source of income,
中文字幕：他指出，这棵树是一种有用的收入来源，
英文字幕：as tourists have been coming from all parts of the country to see it.
中文字幕：因为游客们从全国各地赶来参观。
英文字幕：In spite of all that has been said,
中文字幕：尽管说了这么多，
英文字幕：the tourists have been picking leaves and cutting their names on the tree trunk.
中文字幕：游客们一直在摘树叶，把他们的名字刻在树干上。
英文字幕：So far, not one of them has been struck down by sudden death.
中文字幕：到目前为止，还没有一人被猝死击倒。