英文字幕：Lesson 25.
中文字幕：课25。
英文字幕：Do the English speak English?
中文字幕：英国人会说英语吗？
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why does the writer not understand the porter?
中文字幕：为什么作者不理解搬运工？
英文字幕：I arrived in London at last.
中文字幕：我终于到了伦敦。
英文字幕：The railway station was big, black and dark.
中文字幕：火车站很大，又黑又暗。
英文字幕：I did not know the way to my hotel, so I asked a porter.
中文字幕：我不知道去酒店的路，所以我问了一个搬运工。
英文字幕：I not only spoke English very carefully, but very clearly as well.
中文字幕：我不仅说英语很仔细，而且说得很清楚。
英文字幕：The porter, however, could not understand me.
中文字幕：然而，搬运工听不懂我的话。
英文字幕：I repeated my question several times, and at last he understood.
中文字幕：我重复了我的问题几次，最后他明白了。
英文字幕：He answered me, but he spoke neither slowly nor clearly.
中文字幕：他回答了我，但他说话既不慢也不清楚。
英文字幕：I am a foreigner, I said.
中文字幕：我是个外国人，我说。
英文字幕：Then he spoke slowly, but I could not understand him.
中文字幕：然后他慢慢地说，但我听不懂。
英文字幕：I teach a never spoke English like that.
中文字幕：我教一个从来不会说英语的人。
英文字幕：The porter and I looked at each other and smiled.
中文字幕：搬运工和我面面相觑，笑了。
英文字幕：Then he said something, and I understood it.
中文字幕：然后他说了些什么，我明白了。
英文字幕：You'll soon learn English.
中文字幕：你很快就会学会英语。
英文字幕：He said, I wonder.
中文字幕：他说，我想知道。
英文字幕：In England each person speaks a different language.
中文字幕：在英国，每个人说不同的语言。
英文字幕：The English understand each other, but I don't understand them.
中文字幕：英国人互相理解，但我不理解他们。
英文字幕：Do they speak English?
中文字幕：他们会说英语吗？