英文字幕：Lesson 28. No parking.
中文字幕：课28。禁止停车。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What is Jasper White's problem?
中文字幕：贾斯珀·怀特的问题是什么？
英文字幕：Jasper White is one of those rare people who believes in ancient myths.
中文字幕：贾斯珀·怀特是少数相信古代神话的人之一。
英文字幕：He has just bought a new house in the city.
中文字幕：他刚刚在城里买了一栋新房子。
英文字幕：But ever since he moved in, he has had trouble with cars and their owners.
中文字幕：但自从他搬进来后，他就和汽车及其车主发生了关系。
英文字幕：When he returns home at night, he always finds that someone has parked a car outside his gate.
中文字幕：当他晚上回家时，他总是发现有人把车停在了他的门外。
英文字幕：Because of this, he has not been able to get his own car into his garage even once.
中文字幕：因此，他甚至一次也没能把自己的车开进车库。
英文字幕：Jasper has put up no parking signs outside his gate, but these have not had any effect.
中文字幕：贾斯珀在大门外没有设置停车标志，但这些标志没有任何效果。
英文字幕：Now he has put an ugly stone head over the gate.
中文字幕：现在他在大门上放了一个丑陋的石头头。
英文字幕：It is one of the ugliest faces I have ever seen.
中文字幕：这是我见过的最丑陋的脸之一。
英文字幕：I asked him what it was and he told me that it was Medusa, the Gorgon.
中文字幕：我问他那是什么，他告诉我那是蛇发女怪美杜莎。
英文字幕：Jasper hopes that she will turn cars and their owners to stone.
中文字幕：贾斯珀希望她能把汽车和车主变成石头。
英文字幕：But none of them has been turned to stone yet.
中文字幕：但它们都还没有变成石头。