英文字幕：Lesson 72. A car called Bluebird. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课72。一辆叫蓝鸟的车。先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What mistake was made? The great racing driver, Sir Malcolm Campbell,
中文字幕：犯了什么错误？伟大的赛车手马尔科姆·坎贝尔爵士，
英文字幕：was the first man to drive at over 300 miles per hour. He set up a new world record in September 1935
中文字幕：他是第一个以每小时300英里以上的速度开车的人。1935年9月，他创造了一项新的世界纪录
英文字幕：at Bonville Saltflats, Utah. Bluebird, the car he was driving, had been specially built for him.
中文字幕：犹他州邦维尔盐滩。他开的那辆蓝鸟汽车是专门为他造的。
英文字幕：It was over 30 feet in length and had a 2,500 horsepower engine.
中文字幕：它的长度超过30英尺，有一个2500马力的发动机。
英文字幕：Although Campbell reached a speed of over 304 miles per hour, he had great difficulty in controlling the
中文字幕：虽然坎贝尔达到了每小时304英里的速度，但他很难控制
英文字幕：car because a tire burst during the first run. After his attempt, Campbell was disappointed to
中文字幕：因为轮胎在第一次行驶时爆裂了。在尝试之后，坎贝尔对
英文字幕：learn that his average speed had been 299 miles per hour. However, a few days later, he was told
中文字幕：得知他的平均速度为每小时299英里。然而，几天后，他被告知
英文字幕：that a mistake had been made. His average speed had been 301 miles per hour. Since that time,
中文字幕：犯了一个错误。他的平均速度是每小时301英里。从那时起，
英文字幕：racing drivers have reached speeds over 600 miles per hour. Following in his father's footsteps,
中文字幕：赛车手已经达到了每小时600英里以上的速度。跟随父亲的脚步，
英文字幕：many years later, Sir Malcolm's son, Donald, also set up a world record. Like his father,
中文字幕：多年后，马尔科姆爵士的儿子唐纳德也创造了世界纪录。像他的父亲一样，
英文字幕：he was driving a car called Bluebird.
中文字幕：他开着一辆叫蓝鸟的车。