英文字幕：Listen 48.
中文字幕：听48。
英文字幕：Did you want to tell me something?
中文字幕：你想告诉我什么吗？
英文字幕：First, listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：首先，听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why did the writer become very worried?
中文字幕：为什么作者变得非常担心？
英文字幕：Dentists always ask questions when it is impossible for you to answer.
中文字幕：牙医总是在你无法回答的时候问问题。
英文字幕：My dentist had just pulled out one of my teeth and had told me to rest for a while.
中文字幕：我的牙医刚刚拔掉了我的一颗牙齿，让我休息一会儿。
英文字幕：I tried to say something, but my mouth was full of cotton wool.
中文字幕：我想说点什么，但嘴里塞满了棉花。
英文字幕：In you I collected matchboxes and asked me whether my collection was growing.
中文字幕：在你身上，我收集了火柴盒，问我的收藏是否在增长。
英文字幕：He then asked me how my brother was and whether I liked my new job in London.
中文字幕：然后他问我哥哥怎么样，我是否喜欢我在伦敦的新工作。
英文字幕：In answer to these questions, I either nodded or made strange noises.
中文字幕：在回答这些问题时，我要么点头，要么发出奇怪的声音。
英文字幕：Meanwhile my tongue was busy searching out the hole where the tooth had been.
中文字幕：与此同时，我的舌头正忙着寻找牙齿原来的洞。
英文字幕：I suddenly felt very worried but could not say anything.
中文字幕：我突然感到很担心，但什么也说不出来。
英文字幕：When the dentist at last removed the cotton wool from my mouth, I was able to tell him
中文字幕：当牙医最终从我口中取出药棉时，我得以告诉他
英文字幕：that he had pulled out the wrong tooth.
中文字幕：他拔错了牙。