英文字幕：Lesson 73. The record holder. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课73。纪录保持者。先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Did the boy go where he wanted to?
中文字幕：那男孩去他想去的地方了吗？
英文字幕：Children who played truant from school are unimaginative.
中文字幕：逃学的孩子缺乏想象力。
英文字幕：A quiet day's fishing or eight hours in a cinema seeing the same film over and over again
中文字幕：安静地钓鱼一天，或者在电影院里看八个小时，一遍又一遍地看同一部电影
英文字幕：is usually as far as they get.
中文字幕：通常是他们能走到的最远的地方。
英文字幕：They have all been put to shame by a boy who while playing truant travelled 1600 miles.
中文字幕：一个逃学的男孩走了1600英里，让他们都感到羞愧。
英文字幕：He hitchhiked to Dover and towards evening went into a boat to find somewhere to sleep.
中文字幕：他搭便车去了多佛，傍晚时分，他上船找地方睡觉。
英文字幕：When he woke up next morning he discovered that the boat had in the meantime travelled to Calais.
中文字幕：第二天早上醒来时，他发现船已经驶向加莱。
英文字幕：No one noticed the boy as he crept off. From there he hitchhiked to Paris in a lorry.
中文字幕：当男孩悄悄离开时，没有人注意到他。从那里，他搭了一辆卡车去了巴黎。
英文字幕：The driver gave him a few biscuits and a cup of coffee and left him just outside the city.
中文字幕：司机给了他几块饼干和一杯咖啡，把他留在城外。
英文字幕：The next car the boy stopped did not take him into the centre of Paris as he hoped it would,
中文字幕：男孩拦下的下一辆车并没有像他希望的那样把他带到巴黎市中心，
英文字幕：but to pay pinot on the French Spanish border. There he was picked up by a policeman
中文字幕：但要在法国和西班牙边境支付皮诺。在那里，他被一名警察抓了起来
英文字幕：and sent back to England by the local authorities. He has surely set up a record for the thousands
中文字幕：并被当地政府送回英国。他无疑创造了数千人的记录
英文字幕：of children who dream of evading school.
中文字幕：那些梦想逃避学校的孩子。