英文字幕：Lesson 32. Shopping made easy.
中文字幕：课32。购物变得容易。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Who was the thief?
中文字幕：小偷是谁？
英文字幕：People are not so honest as they once were.
中文字幕：人们不像以前那么诚实了。
英文字幕：The temptation to steal is greater than ever before, especially in large shops.
中文字幕：偷窃的诱惑比以往任何时候都大，尤其是在大型商店。
英文字幕：A detective recently watched a well-dressed woman who'd always went into a large store on Monday mornings.
中文字幕：一位侦探最近看到一位穿着考究的女人，她总是在周一早上走进一家大商店。
英文字幕：One Monday there were fewer people in the shop than usual when the woman came in.
中文字幕：一个星期一，当那个女人进来时，商店里的人比平时少。
英文字幕：So it was easier for the detective to watch her.
中文字幕：所以侦探更容易监视她。
英文字幕：The woman first bought a few small articles.
中文字幕：这位女士先买了几件小东西。
英文字幕：After a little time she chose one of the most expensive dresses in the shop and handed it to an assistant who wrapped it up for her as quickly as possible.
中文字幕：过了一会儿，她挑了一件店里最贵的衣服，递给店员，店员尽快帮她包好。
英文字幕：Then the woman simply took the parcel and walked out of the shop without paying.
中文字幕：然后，这位女士只是接过包裹，没有付钱就走出了商店。
英文字幕：When she was arrested the detective found out that the shop assistant was her daughter.
中文字幕：当她被捕时，侦探发现店员是她的女儿。
英文字幕：The girl gave her mother a free dress once a week.
中文字幕：这个女孩每周给她妈妈一件免费的裙子。