英文字幕：Lesson 92.
中文字幕：课92。
英文字幕：Asking for trouble.
中文字幕：自找麻烦。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why did the policeman ask the writer to come to the police station?
中文字幕：警察为什么让作家来警察局？
英文字幕：It must have been about two in the morning when I returned home.
中文字幕：我回家的时候一定是凌晨两点左右。
英文字幕：I tried to wake up my wife by ringing the doorbell, but she was fast asleep.
中文字幕：我试图按门铃叫醒我的妻子，但她睡得很熟。
英文字幕：So I got a ladder from the shed in the garden, put it against the wall, and began climbing
中文字幕：于是，我从花园里的棚屋里拿了一架梯子，把它靠在墙上，开始往上爬
英文字幕：towards the bedroom window.
中文字幕：朝向卧室的窗户。
英文字幕：I was almost there when a sarcastic voice below said,
中文字幕：我快到了，这时下面一个讽刺的声音说：，
英文字幕：I don't think the windows need cleaning at this time of the night.
中文字幕：我认为晚上这个时候窗户不需要打扫。
英文字幕：I looked down and nearly fell off the ladder when I saw a policeman.
中文字幕：我往下看，看见一个警察，差点从梯子上摔下来。
英文字幕：I immediately regretted answering in the way I did, but I said,
中文字幕：我立刻后悔自己的回答方式，但我说：，
英文字幕：I enjoy cleaning windows at night.
中文字幕：我喜欢晚上擦窗户。
英文字幕：So do I, answered the policeman in the same tone.
中文字幕：我也是，警察用同样的语气回答。
英文字幕：Excuse my interrupting you.
中文字幕：请原谅我打断你。
英文字幕：I hate to interrupt a man when he's busy working, but would you mind coming with me to the station?
中文字幕：当一个人忙于工作时，我不想打扰他，但你介意和我一起去车站吗？
英文字幕：Well, I'd prefer to stay here, I said.
中文字幕：好吧，我宁愿留在这里，我说。
英文字幕：You see, I've forgotten my key.
中文字幕：你看，我忘了带钥匙。
英文字幕：You're what?
中文字幕：你是什么？
英文字幕：He called.
中文字幕：他打电话来了。
英文字幕：My key!
中文字幕：我的钥匙！
英文字幕：I shouted.
中文字幕：我喊道。
英文字幕：Fortunately, the shouting woke up my wife, who opened the window just as the policeman had started to climb towards me.
中文字幕：幸运的是，喊声吵醒了我的妻子，就在警察开始向我爬来的时候，她打开了窗户。