英文字幕：Lesson 71. A famous clock. First listen and then answer the question. Has big
中文字幕：课71。一个著名的时钟。先听录音，然后回答问题。有很大
英文字幕：Ben ever gone wrong? When you visit London, one of the first things you will see is big
中文字幕：本出过问题吗？当你访问伦敦时，你会看到的第一件事就是大
英文字幕：Ben. The famous clock which can be heard all over the world on the BBC. If the houses of Parliament had
中文字幕：本。这个著名的时钟在英国广播公司（BBC）的节目中全世界都能听到。如果议会大厦
英文字幕：not been burned down in 1834, the great clock would never have been erected. Big Ben takes its name
中文字幕：如果1834年没有被烧毁，这座大钟就永远不会竖立起来。大本钟得名
英文字幕：from Sir Benjamin Hall, who was responsible for the making of the clock when the new houses of
中文字幕：本杰明·霍尔爵士负责制作新房子时的时钟
英文字幕：Parliament were being built. It is not only of immense size, but is extremely accurate as well.
中文字幕：议会正在建设中。它不仅体积庞大，而且非常精确。
英文字幕：Officials from Greenwich Observatory have the clock checked twice a day.
中文字幕：格林威治天文台的官员每天检查两次时钟。
英文字幕：On the BBC, you can hear the clock when it is actually striking because microphones are connected
中文字幕：在英国广播公司，你可以听到时钟实际敲响的声音，因为麦克风是连接的
英文字幕：to the clock tower. Big Ben has rarely gone wrong. Once however, it failed to give the correct time.
中文字幕：前往钟楼。大本钟很少出错。然而，有一次，它未能给出正确的时间。
英文字幕：A painter who had been working on the tower hung a pot of paint on one of the hands and slowed it down.
中文字幕：一位在塔上工作的画家把一壶油漆挂在一只手上，放慢了速度。