英文字幕：Lesson 17 Always young
中文字幕：第17课永远年轻
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why doesn't Aunt Jennifer tell anyone how old she is?
中文字幕：为什么詹妮弗阿姨不告诉任何人她多大了？
英文字幕：My Aunt Jennifer is an actress.
中文字幕：我的詹妮弗阿姨是一名演员。
英文字幕：She must be at least 35 years old.
中文字幕：她必须至少35岁。
英文字幕：In spite of this, she often appears on the stage as a young girl.
中文字幕：尽管如此，她还是经常以年轻女孩的身份出现在舞台上。
英文字幕：Jennifer will have to take part in a new play soon.
中文字幕：詹妮弗很快就要参加一部新戏了。
英文字幕：This time she will be a girl of 17.
中文字幕：这一次，她将是一个17岁的女孩。
英文字幕：In the play she must appear in a bright red dress and long black stockings.
中文字幕：在剧中，她必须穿着鲜红的裙子和黑色长袜。
英文字幕：Last year in another play she had to wear short socks and a bright orange coloured dress.
中文字幕：去年在另一场演出中，她不得不穿短袜和亮橙色的裙子。
英文字幕：If anyone ever asks her how old she is, she always answers.
中文字幕：如果有人问她多大了，她总是回答。
英文字幕：Darling, it must be terrible to be grown up.
中文字幕：亲爱的，长大了一定很可怕。