英文字幕：Lesson 62. After the fire.
中文字幕：课62。火灾之后。
英文字幕：First, listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：首先，听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What was the danger to the villages after the fire?
中文字幕：火灾发生后，村庄面临的危险是什么？
英文字幕：Firemen had been fighting the forest fire for nearly three weeks before they could get it under control.
中文字幕：消防员已经与森林大火搏斗了近三周，才将其控制住。
英文字幕：A short time before, great trees had covered the countryside for miles around.
中文字幕：不久前，几英里外的乡村都长满了大树。
英文字幕：Now, smoke still rose up from the warm ground over the death of the hills.
中文字幕：现在，烟雾仍然从温暖的地面升起，笼罩着山丘的死亡。
英文字幕：Winter was coming on, and the hills threatened the surrounding villages with destruction.
中文字幕：冬天来了，群山威胁着周围的村庄。
英文字幕：For heavy rain would not only wash away the soil, but would cause serious floods as well.
中文字幕：因为大雨不仅会冲走土壤，还会造成严重的洪水。
英文字幕：When the fire had at last been put out, the forest authorities ordered several tons of a special type of grass seed which would grow quickly.
中文字幕：当大火终于被扑灭时，林业部门订购了几吨一种生长迅速的特殊草籽。
英文字幕：The seed was sprayed over the ground in huge quantities by aeroplanes.
中文字幕：飞机把种子大量地撒在地上。
英文字幕：The plains had been planting seed for nearly a month when it began to rain.
中文字幕：平原上播种已经快一个月了，这时开始下雨了。
英文字幕：By then, however, in many places the grass had already taken root.
中文字幕：然而，到那时，在许多地方，草已经扎根了。
英文字幕：In place of the great trees which had been growing there for centuries, patches of green had begun to appear in the blackened soil.
中文字幕：取而代之的是几个世纪以来一直生长在那里的大树，在变黑的土壤中开始出现一片片绿色。
英文字幕：The forest was planted in the forest for nearly a month, and the forest was planted in the forest for nearly a month.
中文字幕：这片森林在森林里种了将近一个月，这片森林也在森林里种植了近一个月。