英文字幕：Lesson 47
中文字幕：第47课
英文字幕：A firsty ghost
中文字幕：第一个鬼
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What evidence is there of a ghost?
中文字幕：有什么鬼的证据？
英文字幕：A public house which was recently bought by Mr Ian Thompson is up for sale.
中文字幕：伊恩·汤普森先生最近购买的一栋公共房屋即将出售。
英文字幕：Mr Thompson is going to sell it because it is haunted.
中文字幕：汤普森先生打算卖掉它，因为它闹鬼。
英文字幕：He told me that he could not go to sleep one night because he heard a strange noise coming from the bar.
中文字幕：他告诉我，有一天晚上他睡不着，因为他听到酒吧里有奇怪的声音。
英文字幕：The next morning he found that the doors had been blocked by chairs and the furniture had been moved.
中文字幕：第二天早上，他发现门被椅子堵住了，家具也被搬走了。
英文字幕：Though Mr Thompson had turned the lights off before he went to bed, they were on in the morning.
中文字幕：虽然汤普森先生在睡觉前把灯关掉了，但第二天早上灯还亮着。
英文字幕：He also said that he had found five empty whiskey bottles which the ghost must have drunk the night before.
中文字幕：他还说，他发现了五个空的威士忌酒瓶，鬼魂一定是前一天晚上喝的。
英文字幕：When I suggested that some villagers must have come in for a free drink, Mr Thompson shook his head.
中文字幕：当我建议一些村民一定是来免费喝酒时，汤普森先生摇了摇头。
英文字幕：The villagers have told him that they will not accept the pub even if he gives it away.
中文字幕：村民们告诉他，即使他把酒吧送人，他们也不会接受。