英文字幕：Lesson 78.
中文字幕：课78。
英文字幕：The last one?
中文字幕：最后一个？
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：For how long did the writer give up smoking?
中文字幕：这位作家戒烟多久了？
英文字幕：After reading an article entitled, cigarette smoking and your health, I lit a cigarette
中文字幕：读完一篇题为《吸烟与健康》的文章后，我点了一根烟
英文字幕：to calm my nerves.
中文字幕：来镇定我的神经。
英文字幕：I smoked with concentration and pleasure, as I was sure that this would be my last cigarette.
中文字幕：我全神贯注地愉快地抽烟，因为我确信这将是我最后一根烟。
英文字幕：For a whole week I did not smoke at all, and during this time my wife suffered terribly.
中文字幕：整整一个星期我都不抽烟，在这段时间里，我妻子遭受了极大的痛苦。
英文字幕：I had all the usual symptoms of someone giving up smoking, a bad temper and an enormous appetite.
中文字幕：我有戒烟者的所有常见症状，脾气暴躁，食欲旺盛。
英文字幕：My friends kept on offering me cigarettes and cigars.
中文字幕：我的朋友们不停地给我香烟和雪茄。
英文字幕：They made no effort to hide their amusement, whenever I produced a packet of sweets from
中文字幕：每当我拿出一包糖果时，他们都毫不掩饰自己的乐趣
英文字幕：my pocket.
中文字幕：我的口袋。
英文字幕：After seven days of this I went to a party.
中文字幕：七天后，我去参加了一个聚会。
英文字幕：Everybody around me was smoking, and I felt extremely uncomfortable.
中文字幕：我周围的人都在抽烟，我感到非常不舒服。
英文字幕：When my old friend Brian urged me to accept a cigarette, it was more than I could bear.
中文字幕：当我的老朋友布莱恩劝我接受一支香烟时，我无法忍受。
英文字幕：I took one guiltily, lit it, and smoked with satisfaction.
中文字幕：我内疚地拿了一个，点燃它，满意地抽烟。
英文字幕：My wife was delighted that things had returned to normal once more.
中文字幕：我妻子很高兴事情再次恢复正常。
英文字幕：Anyway, as Brian pointed out, it is the easiest thing in the world to give up smoking.
中文字幕：不管怎样，正如布莱恩所指出的，戒烟是世界上最容易的事情。
英文字幕：He himself has done it lots of times.
中文字幕：他自己也做过很多次。