英文字幕：Lesson 75
中文字幕：第75课
英文字幕：S-O-S
中文字幕：S-O-S
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：How did the woman get help?
中文字幕：这个女人是怎么得到帮助的？
英文字幕：When a light passenger plane flew off course some time ago, it crashed in the mountains and its pilot was killed.
中文字幕：不久前，一架轻型客机偏离航线，坠毁在山区，飞行员遇难。
英文字幕：The only passengers, a young woman and her two baby daughters, were unhurt.
中文字幕：唯一的乘客，一名年轻女子和她的两个小女儿，没有受伤。
英文字幕：It was the middle of winter, snow lay thick on the ground.
中文字幕：当时是隆冬，地上积雪很厚。
英文字幕：The woman knew that the nearest village was miles away.
中文字幕：女人知道最近的村庄在几英里之外。
英文字幕：When it grew dark, she turned a suitcase into a bed
中文字幕：天黑后，她把行李箱变成了床
英文字幕：and put the children inside it, covering them with all the clothes she could find.
中文字幕：把孩子们放在里面，用她能找到的所有衣服盖住他们。
英文字幕：During the night it got terribly cold.
中文字幕：夜里，天气变得异常寒冷。
英文字幕：The woman kept as near as she could to the children and even tried to get into the case herself, but it was too small.
中文字幕：这名妇女尽可能靠近孩子们，甚至试图自己进入箱子，但箱子太小了。
英文字幕：Early next morning she heard planes passing overhead and wondered how she could send a signal.
中文字幕：第二天一早，她听到飞机从头顶飞过，想知道她怎么能发出信号。
英文字幕：Then she had an idea.
中文字幕：然后她有了一个主意。
英文字幕：She stamped out the letters S-O-S in the snow.
中文字幕：她在雪地里把字母S-O-S印了出来。
英文字幕：Fortunately a pilot saw the signal and sent a message by radio to the nearest town.
中文字幕：幸运的是，一名飞行员看到了信号，并通过无线电向最近的城镇发送了信息。
英文字幕：It was not long before a helicopter arrived on the scene to rescue the survivors of the plane crash.
中文字幕：不久，一架直升机抵达现场营救飞机失事的幸存者。