英文字幕：Lesson 74. Out of the limelight. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课74。远离聚光灯。先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why was there disguise? Too perfect. An ancient bus stopped by a dry riverbed and a party
中文字幕：为什么要伪装？太完美了。一辆古老的公共汽车停在干涸的河床旁，还有一个聚会
英文字幕：of famous actors and actresses got off. Dressed in dark glasses and old clothes, they had
中文字幕：许多著名的男女演员下车了。他们戴着墨镜，穿着旧衣服
英文字幕：taken special precautions so that no one should recognize them. But as they soon discovered,
中文字幕：采取了特别的预防措施，以免被人认出。但他们很快发现，
英文字幕：disguises can sometimes be too perfect.
中文字幕：伪装有时可能太完美了。
英文字幕：This is a wonderful place for a picnic, said Gloria Gleam.
中文字幕：这是一个野餐的好地方，格洛丽亚·格莱姆说。
英文字幕：It couldn't be better, Gloria. Bringsley Meals agreed. No newspaper men, no film fans.
中文字幕：再好不过了，格洛丽亚。布林斯利膳食公司同意了。没有报人，没有影迷。
英文字幕：Why don't we come more often?
中文字幕：我们为什么不经常来呢？
英文字幕：Meanwhile, two other actors, Rockwall Slinger and Merlin Greaves, had carried two large
中文字幕：与此同时，另外两位演员，Rockwall Slinger和Merlin Greaves，带着两个大
英文字幕：food baskets to a shady spot under some trees. When they had all made themselves comfortable,
中文字幕：把食物篮放在一些树下的阴凉处。当他们都感到舒适时，
英文字幕：a stranger appeared. He looked very angry.
中文字幕：一个陌生人出现了。他看起来很生气。
英文字幕：Now you get out of here, all of you, he shouted.
中文字幕：现在你们都离开这里，他喊道。
英文字幕：I'm sure of here. Do you see that notice? It says, no camping, in case you can't read.
中文字幕：我确信在这里。你看到那个通知了吗？上面写着，不要露营，以防你看不懂。
英文字幕：Look, Sheriff, said Rockwall. Don't be too hard on us.
中文字幕：看，警长，罗克沃尔说。别对我们太苛刻。
英文字幕：I'm Rockwall Slinger, and this is Merlin Greaves.
中文字幕：我是罗克沃尔·斯林格，这位是默林·格里夫斯。
英文字幕：Oh, is it, said the Sheriff with a snare?
中文字幕：哦，是吗，警长用圈套说？
英文字幕：Well, I'm Bringsley Mears, and my other name is Gloria Gleam. Now you get out of here, fast.
中文字幕：好吧，我是布林斯利·米尔斯，我的另一个名字是格洛丽亚·格莱姆。现在你快离开这里。
英文字幕：You
中文字幕：你