英文字幕：Lesson 67 Volcanoes
中文字幕：第67课火山
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why does Tazyev risk his life like this?
中文字幕：塔济耶夫为什么要这样冒着生命危险？
英文字幕：Harun Tazyev, the Polish scientist,
中文字幕：波兰科学家哈伦·塔济耶夫，
英文字幕：has spent his lifetime studying active volcanoes
中文字幕：他一生都在研究活火山
英文字幕：and deep caves in all parts of the world.
中文字幕：世界各地的洞穴都很深。
英文字幕：In 1948 he went to Lake Kivu in the Congo
中文字幕：1948年，他去了刚果的基伍湖
英文字幕：to observe a new volcano,
中文字幕：观察一座新火山，
英文字幕：which he later named Keturo.
中文字幕：他后来将其命名为Keturo。
英文字幕：Tazyev was able to set up his camp
中文字幕：塔济耶夫得以建立营地
英文字幕：very close to the volcano,
中文字幕：非常靠近火山，
英文字幕：while it was erupting violently.
中文字幕：当它猛烈地爆发时。
英文字幕：Though he managed to take a number of brilliant photographs,
中文字幕：虽然他设法拍了一些精彩的照片，
英文字幕：he could not stay near the volcano for very long.
中文字幕：他不能在火山附近呆太久。
英文字幕：He noticed that a river of liquid rock was coming towards him.
中文字幕：他注意到一条液态岩石河正朝他走来。
英文字幕：It threatened to surround him completely,
中文字幕：它威胁要完全包围他，
英文字幕：but Tazyev managed to escape just in time.
中文字幕：但塔济耶夫及时逃脱了。
英文字幕：He waited until the volcano became quiet
中文字幕：他一直等到火山安静下来
英文字幕：and he was able to return two days later.
中文字幕：两天后，他回来了。
英文字幕：This time he managed to climb into the mouth of Keturo
中文字幕：这次他设法爬进了Keturo的嘴里
英文字幕：so that he could take photographs and measure temperatures.
中文字幕：这样他就可以拍照和测量温度。
英文字幕：Tazyev has often risked his life in this way.
中文字幕：塔济耶夫经常以这种方式冒着生命危险。
英文字幕：He has been able to tell us more about active volcanoes
中文字幕：他已经能够告诉我们更多关于活火山的信息
英文字幕：than any man alive.
中文字幕：比任何活着的人。