英文字幕：Lesson 6.
中文字幕：课6。
英文字幕：Percy buttons.
中文字幕：珀西按钮。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Who is Percy buttons?
中文字幕：珀西·巴顿斯是谁？
英文字幕：I have just moved to a house in Bridge Street.
中文字幕：我刚搬到桥街的一所房子里。
英文字幕：Yesterday, a beggar knocked at my door.
中文字幕：昨天，一个乞丐敲我的门。
英文字幕：He asked me for a meal and a glass of beer.
中文字幕：他向我要了一顿饭和一杯啤酒。
英文字幕：In return for this, the beggar stood on his head and sang songs.
中文字幕：作为回报，乞丐倒立着唱歌。
英文字幕：I gave him a meal.
中文字幕：我给他吃了一顿饭。
英文字幕：He ate the food and drank the beer.
中文字幕：他吃了食物，喝了啤酒。
英文字幕：Then he put a piece of cheese in his pocket and went away.
中文字幕：然后，他把一块奶酪放进口袋里，走了。
英文字幕：Later, a neighbour told me about him.
中文字幕：后来，一位邻居向我提及了他。
英文字幕：Everybody knows him.
中文字幕：大家都认识他。
英文字幕：His name is Percy buttons.
中文字幕：他的名字叫珀西·巴顿斯。
英文字幕：He calls it every house in the street once a month and always asks for a meal and a glass
中文字幕：他每月给街上的每家每户打一次电话，总是要一顿饭和一杯酒
英文字幕：of beer.
中文字幕：啤酒。