英文字幕：Lesson 85.
中文字幕：课85。
英文字幕：Never too old to learn.
中文字幕：活到老，学到老。
英文字幕：First, listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：首先，听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：How long has Mr. Page been teaching?
中文字幕：佩奇先生教书多久了？
英文字幕：I have just received a letter from my old school
中文字幕：我刚收到母校的一封信
英文字幕：informing me that my former headmaster, Mr. Stuart Page,
中文字幕：通知我，我的前任校长斯图尔特·佩奇先生，
英文字幕：will be retiring next week.
中文字幕：将于下周退休。
英文字幕：Pupils of the school, old and new,
中文字幕：学校的学生，新老，
英文字幕：will be sending him a present to mark the occasion.
中文字幕：将送他一份礼物来纪念这一时刻。
英文字幕：All those who have contributed towards the gift
中文字幕：所有为礼物做出贡献的人
英文字幕：will sign their names in a large album
中文字幕：将在一个大相册中签名
英文字幕：which will be sent to the headmaster's home.
中文字幕：这将被送到校长家。
英文字幕：We shall all remember Mr. Page for his patience in understanding
中文字幕：我们都会记住佩奇先生耐心的理解
英文字幕：and for the kindly encouragement he gave us
中文字幕：感谢他给予我们的善意鼓励
英文字幕：when we went so unwillingly to school.
中文字幕：当我们如此不情愿地去上学的时候。
英文字幕：A great many former pupils will be attending a farewell dinner
中文字幕：许多以前的学生将参加告别晚宴
英文字幕：in his honour next Thursday.
中文字幕：为了下周四的荣誉。
英文字幕：It is a curious coincidence that the day before his retirement,
中文字幕：一个奇怪的巧合是，在他退休的前一天，
英文字幕：Mr. Page will have been teaching for a total of forty years.
中文字幕：佩奇先生总共教了四十年书。
英文字幕：After he has retired, he will devote himself to gardening.
中文字幕：退休后，他将致力于园艺。
英文字幕：For him, this will be an entirely new hobby.
中文字幕：对他来说，这将是一个全新的爱好。
英文字幕：But this does not matter.
中文字幕：但这并不重要。
英文字幕：For as he has often remarked,
中文字幕：正如他经常说的那样，
英文字幕：one is never too old to learn.
中文字幕：活到老，学到老。