英文字幕：Lesson 60. The future.
中文字幕：课60。未来。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Does what Madame Balinsky said come true?
中文字幕：巴林斯基夫人说的话成真了吗？
英文字幕：At a village fair, I decided to visit a fortune teller called Madame Balinsky.
中文字幕：在一次乡村集市上，我决定去拜访一位名叫巴林斯基夫人的算命师。
英文字幕：I went into her tent and she told me to sit down.
中文字幕：我走进她的帐篷，她让我坐下。
英文字幕：After I had given her some money, she looked into a crystal ball and said,
中文字幕：我给了她一些钱后，她看着水晶球说：，
英文字幕：A relation of yours is coming to see you.
中文字幕：你的一个亲戚要来看你。
英文字幕：She will be arriving this evening and intends to stay for a few days.
中文字幕：她将于今晚抵达，并打算停留几天。
英文字幕：The moment you leave this tent, you will get a big surprise.
中文字幕：当你离开这个帐篷的那一刻，你会得到一个大惊喜。
英文字幕：A woman you know well will rush towards you.
中文字幕：一个你熟悉的女人会朝你冲过来。
英文字幕：She will speak to you and then she will lead you away from this place.
中文字幕：她会跟你说话，然后带你离开这个地方。
英文字幕：That is all.
中文字幕：仅此而已。
英文字幕：As soon as I went outside, I forgot all about Madame Balinsky,
中文字幕：我一出门，就把巴林斯基夫人忘得一干二净，
英文字幕：because my wife hurried towards me.
中文字幕：因为我妻子匆匆朝我走来。
英文字幕：Where have you been hiding?
中文字幕：你一直躲在哪里？
英文字幕：She asked impatiently.
中文字幕：她不耐烦地问。
英文字幕：Your sister will be here in less than an hour and we must be at the station to meet her.
中文字幕：你妹妹不到一个小时就会到，我们必须到车站接她。
英文字幕：We are late already.
中文字幕：我们已经迟到了。
英文字幕：As she walked away, I followed her out of the fair.
中文字幕：当她走开时，我跟着她走出了集市。