英文字幕：Lesson 41.
中文字幕：课41。
英文字幕：Do you call that a hat?
中文字幕：你管那叫帽子吗？
英文字幕：First, listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：首先，听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What kind of shopping does the writer enjoy, do you think?
中文字幕：你觉得这位作家喜欢什么样的购物？
英文字幕：Do you call that a hat?
中文字幕：你管那叫帽子吗？
英文字幕：I said to my wife.
中文字幕：我对我妻子说。
英文字幕：I need to be so rude about it.
中文字幕：对此，我必须表现得非常粗鲁。
英文字幕：My wife answered as she looked at herself in the mirror.
中文字幕：我妻子看着镜子里的自己回答。
英文字幕：I sat down on one of those modern chairs with holes in it and waited.
中文字幕：我坐在一把有洞的现代椅子上等待。
英文字幕：We had been in the hat shop for half an hour, and my wife was still in front of the mirror.
中文字幕：我们在帽子店已经逛了半个小时，我妻子还在镜子前。
英文字幕：We mustn't buy things we don't need, I remarked suddenly.
中文字幕：我们不能买不需要的东西，我突然说。
英文字幕：I regretted saying it almost at once.
中文字幕：我几乎立刻后悔说了那句话。
英文字幕：You needn't to said that, my wife answered.
中文字幕：你不必这么说，我妻子回答。
英文字幕：I needn't remind you of that terrible tie you bought yesterday.
中文字幕：我不必提醒你昨天买的那条糟糕的领带。
英文字幕：I find it beautiful, I said.
中文字幕：我觉得它很漂亮，我说。
英文字幕：A man can never have too many ties.
中文字幕：一个人永远不会有太多的领带。
英文字幕：And a woman can't have too many hats, she answered.
中文字幕：一个女人不能有太多的帽子，她回答。
英文字幕：Ten minutes later, we walked out of the shop together.
中文字幕：十分钟后，我们一起走出了商店。
英文字幕：My wife was wearing a hat that looked like a lighthouse.
中文字幕：我妻子戴着一顶看起来像灯塔的帽子。