英文字幕：Lesson 82. Monster or fish?
中文字幕：课82。怪物还是鱼？
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What was the monster called?
中文字幕：怪物叫什么名字？
英文字幕：Fishermen and sailors sometimes claimed have seen monsters in the sea.
中文字幕：渔民和水手有时声称在海里看到过怪物。
英文字幕：Though people have often laughed at stories told by semen,
中文字幕：虽然人们经常嘲笑精液讲述的故事，
英文字幕：it is now known that many of these monsters, which have at times been sighted,
中文字幕：现在知道，这些怪物中的许多有时会被发现，
英文字幕：are simply strange fish.
中文字幕：它们只是奇怪的鱼。
英文字幕：Occasionally, unusual creatures are washed to the shore,
中文字幕：偶尔，不寻常的生物会被冲到岸边，
英文字幕：but they are rarely caught out at sea.
中文字幕：但它们很少在海上被捕获。
英文字幕：Some time ago, however, a peculiar fish was caught near Madagascar.
中文字幕：然而，不久前，在马达加斯加附近捕获了一条奇特的鱼。
英文字幕：A small fishing boat was carried miles out to sea by the powerful fish as it pulled on the line.
中文字幕：一条小渔船被这条强壮的鱼拖到了数英里外的海里。
英文字幕：Realising that this was no ordinary fish,
中文字幕：意识到这不是普通的鱼，
英文字幕：the fisherman made every effort not to damage it in any way.
中文字幕：渔夫尽一切努力不以任何方式损坏它。
英文字幕：When it was eventually brought to shore, it was found to be over 13 feet long.
中文字幕：当它最终被带到岸边时，发现它有13英尺长。
英文字幕：It had a head like a horse, big blue eyes, shining silver skin and a bright red tail.
中文字幕：它有一个像马一样的头，大大的蓝眼睛，闪闪发光的银色皮肤和鲜红的尾巴。
英文字幕：The fish, which has since been sent to a museum,
中文字幕：这条鱼后来被送到了博物馆，
英文字幕：where it is being examined by a scientist, is called an ore fish.
中文字幕：科学家正在研究的地方被称为矿石鱼。
英文字幕：Such creatures have rarely been seen alive by man,
中文字幕：人类很少看到这种生物活着，
英文字幕：as they live at a depth of 600 feet.
中文字幕：因为它们生活在600英尺深的地方。