英文字幕：Lesson 81. Escape. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课81。逃跑。先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why did the prisoner attack the driver?
中文字幕：犯人为什么袭击司机？
英文字幕：When he had killed the guard, the prisoner of war quickly dragged him into the bushes.
中文字幕：当他杀死警卫后，战俘很快把他拖进了灌木丛。
英文字幕：Working rapidly in the darkness, he soon changed into the dead man's clothes.
中文字幕：他在黑暗中迅速地工作，很快就换上了死者的衣服。
英文字幕：Now, dressed in a blue uniform and with a rifle over his shoulder,
中文字幕：现在，他穿着蓝色制服，肩上扛着步枪，
英文字幕：the prisoner marched boldly up and down in front of the camp.
中文字幕：囚犯在营地前大胆地走来走去。
英文字幕：He could hear shouting in the camp itself.
中文字幕：他能听到营地里的喊声。
英文字幕：Lights were blazing and men were running here and there.
中文字幕：灯火通明，人们四处奔跑。
英文字幕：They had just discovered that a prisoner had escaped.
中文字幕：他们刚刚发现一名囚犯逃跑了。
英文字幕：At that moment, a large black car with four officers inside it stopped at the camp gates.
中文字幕：这时，一辆载有四名警察的黑色大车停在营地门口。
英文字幕：The officers got out and the prisoner stood to attention and saluted as they passed.
中文字幕：军官们走了出来，囚犯站在那里，在他们经过时敬礼。
英文字幕：When they had gone, the driver of the car came towards him.
中文字幕：他们走后，汽车司机朝他走来。
英文字幕：The man obviously wanted to talk.
中文字幕：那人显然想说话。
英文字幕：He was rather elderly with grey hair and clear blue eyes.
中文字幕：他年事已高，灰白的头发，清澈的蓝眼睛。
英文字幕：The prisoner felt sorry for him, but there was nothing else he could do.
中文字幕：囚犯为他感到难过，但他别无选择。
英文字幕：As the man came near, the prisoner knocked him to the ground with a sharp blow.
中文字幕：当那人走近时，囚犯一拳把他打倒在地。
英文字幕：Then, jumping into the car, he drove off as quickly as he could.
中文字幕：然后，他跳进车里，以最快的速度开走了。