英文字幕：Lesson 86. Out of control.
中文字幕：课86。失控。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What was the danger?
中文字幕：危险是什么？
英文字幕：As the man tried to swing the speedboat round, the steering wheel came away in his hands.
中文字幕：当那人试图把快艇转过来时，方向盘在他手里松开了。
英文字幕：He waved desperately to his companion, who had been water-skying for the last 15 minutes.
中文字幕：他绝望地向同伴挥手，他的同伴在过去的15分钟里一直在滑水。
英文字幕：Both men had hardly had time to realise what was happening when they were thrown violently into the sea.
中文字幕：两人还没来得及意识到发生了什么，就被猛烈地扔进了海里。
英文字幕：The speedboat had struck a boy, but it continued to move very quickly across the water.
中文字幕：快艇撞上了一个男孩，但它继续在水面上快速移动。
英文字幕：Both men had just begun to swim towards the shore when they noticed with dismay that the speedboat was moving in a circle.
中文字幕：两人刚开始向岸边游去，就惊愕地发现快艇正在绕圈行驶。
英文字幕：It now came straight towards them, a tremendous speed.
中文字幕：它以惊人的速度径直向他们驶来。
英文字幕：In less than a minute, it roared past them only a few feet away.
中文字幕：不到一分钟，它就在几英尺外呼啸而过。
英文字幕：After it had passed, they swam on as quickly as they could because they knew that the boat would soon return.
中文字幕：船过去后，他们尽可能快地继续游，因为他们知道船很快就会回来。
英文字幕：They had just had enough time to swim out of danger when the boat again completed a circle.
中文字幕：他们刚有足够的时间游出危险，船又绕了一圈。
英文字幕：On this occasion, however, it had slowed down considerably.
中文字幕：然而，在这一次，它已经大大放缓了。
英文字幕：The petrol had nearly all been used up.
中文字幕：汽油几乎用完了。
英文字幕：Before long, the noise dropped completely, and the boat began to drift gently across the water.
中文字幕：不久，噪音完全消失了，船开始在水面上缓缓漂流。