英文字幕：Lesson 51. Reward for virtue.
中文字幕：课51。美德的回报。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why did Hughes' diet not work?
中文字幕：为什么休斯的饮食不起作用？
英文字幕：My friend Hugh has always been fat,
中文字幕：我的朋友休一直都很胖，
英文字幕：but things got so bad recently that he decided to go on a diet.
中文字幕：但最近情况变得很糟糕，他决定节食。
英文字幕：He began his diet a week ago.
中文字幕：他一周前开始节食。
英文字幕：First of all, he wrote out a long list of all the foods which were forbidden.
中文字幕：首先，他列出了一长串被禁止的食物。
英文字幕：The list included most of the things Hugh loves,
中文字幕：这份清单包括休喜欢的大部分东西，
英文字幕：butter, potatoes, rice, beer, milk, chocolate and sweets.
中文字幕：黄油、土豆、米饭、啤酒、牛奶、巧克力和糖果。
英文字幕：Yesterday I paid him a visit.
中文字幕：昨天我去拜访了他。
英文字幕：I rang the bell.
中文字幕：我按了门铃。
英文字幕：And was not surprised to see that Hugh was still as fat as ever.
中文字幕：看到休仍然像以前一样胖，我并不感到惊讶。
英文字幕：He led me into his room and hurriedly hid a large parcel under his desk.
中文字幕：他把我带进他的房间，匆匆忙忙地把一个大包裹藏在桌子下面。
英文字幕：It was obvious that he was very embarrassed.
中文字幕：很明显，他很尴尬。
英文字幕：When I asked him what he was doing, he smiled guiltily and then put the parcel on the desk.
中文字幕：当我问他在做什么时，他内疚地笑了笑，然后把包裹放在桌子上。
英文字幕：He explained that his diet was so strict that he had to reward himself occasionally.
中文字幕：他解释说，他的饮食非常严格，他不得不偶尔奖励自己。
英文字幕：Then he showed me the contents of the parcel.
中文字幕：然后他给我看了包裹里的东西。
英文字幕：It contained five large bars of chocolate and three bags of sweets.
中文字幕：里面有五大块巧克力和三袋糖果。