英文字幕：Lesson 69. But not murder.
中文字幕：课69。但不是谋杀。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Do you think that the writer passed his driving test?
中文字幕：你认为这位作家通过了驾驶考试吗？
英文字幕：Why?
中文字幕：为什么？
英文字幕：I was being tested for a driving licence for the third time.
中文字幕：我第三次参加驾照考试。
英文字幕：I had been asked to drive in heavy traffic and had done so successfully.
中文字幕：我被要求在交通拥挤的情况下开车，而且做得很成功。
英文字幕：After having been instructed to drive out of town, I began to acquire confidence.
中文字幕：在接到开车出城的指示后，我开始有信心了。
英文字幕：Sure that I had passed, I was almost beginning to enjoy my test.
中文字幕：我确信自己通过了考试，几乎开始享受考试了。
英文字幕：The examiner must have been pleased with my performance for his smile and said,
中文字幕：考官一定对我的表现很满意，他笑着说：，
英文字幕：just one more thing Mr. Eames.
中文字幕：还有一件事，伊姆斯先生。
英文字幕：Let us suppose that a child suddenly crosses the road in front of you.
中文字幕：让我们假设一个孩子突然在你面前过马路。
英文字幕：As soon as I tap on the window, you must stop within five feet.
中文字幕：我一敲窗户，你就必须停在五英尺以内。
英文字幕：I continued driving and after some time the examiner tapped loudly.
中文字幕：我继续开车，过了一段时间，考官大声敲门。
英文字幕：Though the sound could be heard clearly, it took me a long time to react.
中文字幕：虽然声音听得很清楚，但我花了很长时间才做出反应。
英文字幕：I suddenly pressed the brake pedal hard and we were both thrown forward.
中文字幕：我突然用力踩下刹车踏板，我们都被甩了出去。
英文字幕：The examiner looked at me sadly.
中文字幕：考官悲伤地看着我。
英文字幕：Mr. Eames, he said, in a mournful voice.
中文字幕：埃姆斯先生，他悲伤地说。
英文字幕：You have just killed that child.
中文字幕：你刚刚杀了那个孩子。