英文字幕：Lesson 65
中文字幕：第65课
英文字幕：Jumbo verses the police
中文字幕：Jumbo对警察
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答以下问题
英文字幕：Why did the police have to push Jumbo off the main street?
中文字幕：为什么警察要把Jumbo赶出大街？
英文字幕：Last Christmas the circus owner Jimmy Gates decided to take some presents to a children's
中文字幕：去年圣诞节，马戏团老板吉米·盖茨决定给一家儿童马戏团带些礼物
英文字幕：hospital. Dressed up as Father Christmas and accompanied by a guard of honour of six
中文字幕：医院。装扮成圣诞老人，由六名仪仗队陪同
英文字幕：pretty girls he set off down the main street of the city riding a baby elephant called
中文字幕：他骑着一头名叫
英文字幕：Jumbo. He should have known that the police would never allow this sort of thing. A policeman
中文字幕：Jumbo。他应该知道警察绝不会允许这种事情发生。警察叔叔
英文字幕：approached Jimmy and told him he ought to have gone along a side street as Jumbo was holding
中文字幕：走到吉米跟前，告诉他，当琼博抱着他时，他应该沿着一条小巷走
英文字幕：up the traffic. Though Jimmy agreed to go at once Jumbo refused to move.
中文字幕：交通堵塞。虽然吉米同意马上走，但朱波却不肯动。
英文字幕：Fifteen policemen had to push very hard to get him off the main street. The police had
中文字幕：十五名警察不得不用力推他离开主街。警方已经
英文字幕：a difficult time but they were most amused.
中文字幕：这是一段艰难的时期，但他们非常开心。
英文字幕：Jumbo must way a few tons said a policeman afterwards so it was fortunate that we didn't
中文字幕：一位警察后来说，“Jumbo肯定有好几吨重，所以幸运的是我们没有。”
英文字幕：have to carry him. Of course we should arrest him but as he has a good record we shall
中文字幕：必须背着他。我们当然应该逮捕他，但由于他有良好的记录，我们将
英文字幕：let him off this time.
中文字幕：这次放他走。