英文字幕：Lesson 18. He often does this.
中文字幕：课18。他经常这样做。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What had happened to the writer's bag?
中文字幕：作家的包怎么了？
英文字幕：After I had had lunch at a village pub, I looked for my bag.
中文字幕：我在一家乡村酒吧吃过午饭后，找了找我的包。
英文字幕：I had left it on a chair beside the door and now it wasn't there.
中文字幕：我把它放在门边的椅子上，现在不见了。
英文字幕：As I was looking for it, the landlord came in.
中文字幕：就在我找的时候，房东进来了。
英文字幕：Did you have a good meal? He asked.
中文字幕：你吃得好吗？他问。
英文字幕：Yes, thank you, I answered.
中文字幕：是的，谢谢你，我回答。
英文字幕：But I can't pay the bill. I haven't got my bag.
中文字幕：但我付不起账单。我没有包。
英文字幕：The landlord smiled and immediately went out.
中文字幕：房东微笑着立刻走了出去。
英文字幕：In a few minutes he returned with my bag and gave it back to me.
中文字幕：几分钟后，他拿着我的包回来了，还给了我。
英文字幕：I'm very sorry, he said.
中文字幕：我很抱歉，他说。
英文字幕：My dog had taken it into the garden. He often does this.
中文字幕：我的狗把它带进了花园。他经常这样做。