英文字幕：Lesson 35. Stop thief.
中文字幕：课35。抓小偷。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：How did Roy stop the thieves?
中文字幕：罗伊是怎么阻止小偷的？
英文字幕：Roy Trenton used to drive a taxi.
中文字幕：罗伊·特伦顿过去开出租车。
英文字幕：A short while ago, however, he became a bus driver
中文字幕：然而，不久前，他成为了一名公交车司机
英文字幕：and he has not regretted it.
中文字幕：他对此并不后悔。
英文字幕：He is finding his new work far more exciting.
中文字幕：他发现他的新工作更令人兴奋。
英文字幕：When he was driving along Catford Street recently,
中文字幕：最近，当他沿着卡特福德街开车时，
英文字幕：he saw two thieves rush out of a shop and run towards a waiting car.
中文字幕：他看见两个小偷冲出一家商店，朝一辆等候的汽车跑去。
英文字幕：One of them was carrying a bag full of money.
中文字幕：其中一人提着一个装满钱的袋子。
英文字幕：Roy acted quickly and drove the bus straight at the thieves.
中文字幕：罗伊迅速采取行动，驾驶公共汽车直冲小偷。
英文字幕：The one with the money got such a fright that he dropped the bag.
中文字幕：那个有钱的人吓得把包摔了。
英文字幕：As the thieves were trying to get away in their car,
中文字幕：当小偷试图开车逃跑时，
英文字幕：Roy drove his bus into the back of it.
中文字幕：罗伊把他的公共汽车撞到了后面。
英文字幕：While the battered car was moving away, Roy stopped his bus
中文字幕：当那辆破旧的汽车开走时，罗伊停下了公共汽车
英文字幕：and telephoned the police.
中文字幕：并打电话给警察。
英文字幕：The thieves' car was badly damaged and easy to recognise.
中文字幕：小偷的车严重损坏，很容易辨认。
英文字幕：Shortly afterwards, the police stopped the car and both men were arrested.
中文字幕：不久之后，警察拦住了这辆车，两人都被捕了。
英文字幕：.
中文字幕：.