英文字幕：Lesson 8.
中文字幕：课8。
英文字幕：The best and the worst.
中文字幕：最好的和最坏的。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why is Joe's garden the most beautiful one in the town?
中文字幕：为什么乔的花园是镇上最漂亮的花园？
英文字幕：Joe Sanders has the most beautiful garden in our town.
中文字幕：乔·桑德斯拥有我们镇上最美丽的花园。
英文字幕：Every everybody enters for the nicest garden competition each year, but Joe wins every time.
中文字幕：每个人都参加了每年最好的花园比赛，但乔每次都赢了。
英文字幕：Bill Fritz's garden is larger than Joe's.
中文字幕：比尔·弗里茨的花园比乔的大。
英文字幕：Bill works harder than Joe and grows more flowers and vegetables.
中文字幕：比尔比乔工作更努力，种了更多的花和蔬菜。
英文字幕：But Joe's garden is more interesting.
中文字幕：但乔的花园更有趣。
英文字幕：He has made neat paths and has built a wooden bridge over a pool.
中文字幕：他开辟了整洁的小路，在池塘上建了一座木桥。
英文字幕：I like gardens too, but I do not like hard work.
中文字幕：我也喜欢花园，但我不喜欢艰苦的工作。
英文字幕：Every year I enter for the garden competition too.
中文字幕：每年我也参加园艺比赛。
英文字幕：And I always win a little prize for the worst garden in the town.
中文字幕：我总是赢得镇上最差花园的小奖。