英文字幕：Lesson 59. In or out.
中文字幕：课59。进或出。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why did Rix run away?
中文字幕：为什么Rix逃跑了？
英文字幕：Our dog Rix used to sit outside our front gate and bark.
中文字幕：我们的狗里克斯过去常常坐在前门外面吠叫。
英文字幕：Every time he wanted to come into the garden, he would bark until someone opened the gate.
中文字幕：每次他想走进花园，他都会吠叫，直到有人打开门。
英文字幕：As the neighbours complained of the noise, my husband spent weeks training him to press his paw on the latch to let himself in.
中文字幕：当邻居们抱怨噪音时，我丈夫花了数周时间训练他把爪子按在门闩上，让自己进去。
英文字幕：Rix soon became an expert at opening the gate.
中文字幕：里克斯很快就成了开门专家。
英文字幕：However, when I was going out shopping last week, I noticed him in the garden near the gate.
中文字幕：然而，当我上周出去购物时，我注意到他在门口附近的花园里。
英文字幕：This time he was barking so that someone would let him out.
中文字幕：这一次，他吠叫着，希望有人能放他出去。
英文字幕：Since then, he has developed another bad habit.
中文字幕：从那以后，他又养成了另一个坏习惯。
英文字幕：As soon as he opens the gate from outside, he comes into the garden and waits until the gate shuts.
中文字幕：他一从外面打开门，就走进花园，一直等到门关上。
英文字幕：Then he sits and barks until someone lets him out.
中文字幕：然后它坐着吠叫，直到有人放它出去。
英文字幕：After this, he immediately lets himself in and begins barking again.
中文字幕：在这之后，他立刻让自己进去，又开始吠叫。
英文字幕：Yesterday, my husband removed the gate and Rix got so annoyed, we have not seen him since.
中文字幕：昨天，我丈夫拆掉了大门，里克斯很生气，从那以后我们就再也没见过他。