英文字幕：Lesson 77. A successful operation. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课77。一次成功的手术。先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Did the doctors find out how the woman died? The mummy of an Egyptian woman who died in
中文字幕：医生们知道那个女人是怎么死的吗？一具埃及妇女的木乃伊，死于
英文字幕：800 BC has just had an operation. The mummy is that of Sheppan Mut who was once a singer in the temple of Thebes.
中文字幕：公元前800年刚刚进行了一次手术。这具木乃伊是谢潘·穆特的木乃伊，他曾是底比斯神庙的一名歌手。
英文字幕：As there were strange marks on the X-ray plates taken of the mummy, doctors have been trying to find out whether the woman died of a rare disease.
中文字幕：由于这具木乃伊的X光片上有奇怪的痕迹，医生们一直在试图找出这名妇女是否死于一种罕见的疾病。
英文字幕：The only way to do this was to operate. The operation which lasted for over four hours proved to be very difficult because of the hard resin which covered the skin.
中文字幕：唯一的办法就是手术。由于皮肤上覆盖着坚硬的树脂，持续了四个多小时的手术非常困难。
英文字幕：The doctors removed a section of the mummy and sent it to a laboratory.
中文字幕：医生们取出了木乃伊的一部分，并将其送往实验室。
英文字幕：They also found something which the X-ray plates did not show. A small wax figure of the god Dua Mutef.
中文字幕：他们还发现了X光片没有显示的东西。杜阿穆特夫神的小蜡像。
英文字幕：This god which has the head of a cow was normally placed inside the mummy.
中文字幕：这个牛头神通常被放在木乃伊里面。
英文字幕：The doctors have not yet decided how the woman died. They feared that the mummy would fall to pieces when they cut it open.
中文字幕：医生们还没有决定这名妇女是怎么死的。他们担心切开木乃伊时会摔成碎片。
英文字幕：But fortunately this has not happened. The mummy successfully survived the operation.
中文字幕：但幸运的是，这并没有发生。这具木乃伊在手术中成功地活了下来。