英文字幕：Lesson 44.
中文字幕：课44。
英文字幕：Through the forest.
中文字幕：穿过森林。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：How did Mrs. Sterling get her bag back?
中文字幕：斯特林太太是怎么把包拿回来的？
英文字幕：Mrs. Anne Sterling did not think of the risk she was taking
中文字幕：安妮·斯特林夫人没有想到她冒的风险
英文字幕：when she ran through a forest after two men.
中文字幕：当她穿过森林追赶两个男人时。
英文字幕：They had rushed up to her while she was having a picnic at the edge of a forest
中文字幕：当她在森林边缘野餐时，他们冲向她
英文字幕：with her children and tried to steal her handbag.
中文字幕：她带着孩子，试图偷她的手提包。
英文字幕：In the struggle the strap broke and with the bag in their possession
中文字幕：在打斗中，带子断了，袋子在他们手里
英文字幕：both men started running through the trees.
中文字幕：两人开始在树林中奔跑。
英文字幕：Mrs. Sterling got so angry that she ran after them.
中文字幕：斯特林太太非常生气，她追了上去。
英文字幕：She was soon out of breath but she continued to run.
中文字幕：她很快上气不接下气，但她继续跑。
英文字幕：When she caught up with them she saw that they had sat down
中文字幕：当她追上他们时，她看到他们已经坐了下来
英文字幕：and were going through the contents of the bag so she ran straight at them.
中文字幕：她正在翻包里的东西，于是径直朝他们跑去。
英文字幕：The men got such a fright that they dropped the bag and ran away.
中文字幕：那些人吓得把袋子掉在地上跑掉了。
英文字幕：The strap needs mending.
中文字幕：这条带子需要修理。
英文字幕：Said Mrs. Sterling later.
中文字幕：斯特林太太后来说。
英文字幕：But they did not steal anything.
中文字幕：但他们没有偷任何东西。