英文字幕：Lesson 24
中文字幕：第24课
英文字幕：It could be worse.
中文字幕：情况可能会更糟。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Had the writers money been stolen?
中文字幕：作家的钱被偷了吗？
英文字幕：I entered the hotel manager's office and sat down.
中文字幕：我走进酒店经理的办公室，坐了下来。
英文字幕：I had just lost 50 pounds and I felt very upset.
中文字幕：我刚刚减掉了50磅，我感到非常沮丧。
英文字幕：I left the money in my room, I said.
中文字幕：我把钱忘在房间里了，我说。
英文字幕：And it's not there now.
中文字幕：现在它不在那里。
英文字幕：The manager was sympathetic, but he could do nothing.
中文字幕：经理很同情，但他什么也做不了。
英文字幕：Everyone's losing money these days, he said.
中文字幕：这些天每个人都在赔钱，他说。
英文字幕：He started to complain about this wicked world,
中文字幕：他开始抱怨这个邪恶的世界，
英文字幕：but was interrupted by a knock at the door.
中文字幕：但被敲门声打断了。
英文字幕：A girl came in and put an envelope on his desk.
中文字幕：一个女孩走了进来，把一个信封放在他的桌子上。
英文字幕：It contained 50 pounds.
中文字幕：里面有50磅。
英文字幕：I found this outside this gentleman's room.
中文字幕：我在这位先生的房间外发现了这个。
英文字幕：She said.
中文字幕：她说。
英文字幕：Well, I said to the manager.
中文字幕：好吧，我对经理说。
英文字幕：There is still some honesty in this world.
中文字幕：这个世界上仍然有一些诚实。