英文字幕：Lesson 80.
中文字幕：课80。
英文字幕：The Crystal Palace.
中文字幕：水晶宫。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：How many people visited the Great Exhibition of 1851?
中文字幕：有多少人参观了1851年的大展览？
英文字幕：Perhaps the most extraordinary building of the 19th century was the Crystal Palace, which
中文字幕：也许19世纪最非凡的建筑是水晶宫
英文字幕：was built in Hyde Park for the Great Exhibition of 1851.
中文字幕：为1851年的世界博览会在海德公园建造。
英文字幕：The Crystal Palace was different from all other buildings in the world, for it was made
中文字幕：水晶宫不同于世界上所有其他建筑，因为它是由
英文字幕：of iron and glass.
中文字幕：铁和玻璃。
英文字幕：It was one of the biggest buildings of all time and a lot of people from many countries
中文字幕：这是有史以来最大的建筑之一，有很多来自不同国家的人
英文字幕：came to see it.
中文字幕：来看看。
英文字幕：A great many goods were sent to the exhibition from various parts of the world.
中文字幕：来自世界各地的大量货物被送往展览会。
英文字幕：There was also a great deal of machinery on display.
中文字幕：展出的机器也很多。
英文字幕：The most wonderful piece of machinery on show was Nazmith's steam hammer.
中文字幕：展出的最奇妙的机器是Nazmith的蒸汽锤。
英文字幕：Though in those days travelling was not as easy as it is today, steamboats carried thousands
中文字幕：虽然那时旅行不像今天那么容易，但汽船载着数千人
英文字幕：of visitors across the channel from Europe.
中文字幕：来自欧洲海峡对岸的游客。
英文字幕：On arriving in England they were taken to the Crystal Palace by train.
中文字幕：抵达英国后，他们被火车带到水晶宫。
英文字幕：There were six million visitors in all and the profits from the exhibition were used to
中文字幕：总共有600万参观者，展览的利润被用来
英文字幕：build museums and colleges.
中文字幕：建造博物馆和大学。
英文字幕：Later the Crystal Palace was moved to South London.
中文字幕：后来，水晶宫搬到了伦敦南部。
英文字幕：It remained one of the most famous buildings in the world until it was burnt down in 1936.
中文字幕：它一直是世界上最著名的建筑之一，直到1936年被烧毁。