英文字幕：Lesson 91. Three men in a basket. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课91。篮子里有三个人。先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Where was the station's commanding officer?
中文字幕：车站的指挥官在哪里？
英文字幕：A pilot noticed a balloon which seemed to be making for a Royal Air Force station nearby.
中文字幕：一名飞行员注意到一个气球似乎正朝附近的皇家空军基地飞去。
英文字幕：He informed the station at once. But no one there was able to explain the mystery.
中文字幕：他立刻通知了车站。但没有人能够解释这个谜。
英文字幕：The officer in the control tower was very angry when he heard the news.
中文字幕：控制塔的官员听到这个消息非常生气。
英文字幕：Because balloons can be a great danger to aircraft.
中文字幕：因为气球对飞机来说可能是一个很大的危险。
英文字幕：He said that someone might be spying on the station and the pilot was ordered to keep track of the strange object.
中文字幕：他说，可能有人在监视空间站，飞行员被命令追踪这个奇怪的物体。
英文字幕：The pilot managed to circle the balloon for some time.
中文字幕：飞行员设法绕着气球转了一段时间。
英文字幕：He could make out three men in a basket under it and one of them was holding a pair of binoculars.
中文字幕：他能认出篮子里有三个人，其中一个拿着望远镜。
英文字幕：When the balloon was over the station, the pilot saw one of the men taking photographs.
中文字幕：当气球飞越空间站时，飞行员看到其中一名男子在拍照。
英文字幕：Soon afterwards, the balloon began to descend and it landed near an airfield.
中文字幕：不久之后，气球开始下降，降落在机场附近。
英文字幕：The police were called in. But they could not arrest anyone.
中文字幕：警察被叫来了。但他们无法逮捕任何人。
英文字幕：For the basket contained two members of Parliament and the commanding officer of the station.
中文字幕：因为篮子里有两名议员和车站的指挥官。
英文字幕：As the commanding officer explained later,
中文字幕：正如指挥官稍后解释的那样，
英文字幕：one half of the station did not know what the other half was doing.
中文字幕：车站的一半人不知道另一半在做什么。