英文字幕：Lesson 93. A noble gift.
中文字幕：课93。一份高贵的礼物。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Where was the Statue of Liberty made?
中文字幕：自由女神像是在哪里建造的？
英文字幕：One of the most famous monuments in the world, the Statue of Liberty,
中文字幕：世界上最著名的纪念碑之一，自由女神像，
英文字幕：was presented to the United States of America in the 19th century
中文字幕：于19世纪赠送给美利坚合众国
英文字幕：by the people of France.
中文字幕：法国人民。
英文字幕：The great statue, which was designed by the sculptor Auguste Bartolady,
中文字幕：这座伟大的雕像是由雕塑家奥古斯特·巴托Lady设计的，
英文字幕：took ten years to complete.
中文字幕：花了十年时间才完成。
英文字幕：The actual figure was made of copper supported by a metal framework,
中文字幕：实际的图形是由金属框架支撑的铜制成的，
英文字幕：which had been especially constructed by Eiffel.
中文字幕：这是埃菲尔特别建造的。
英文字幕：Before it could be transported to the United States,
中文字幕：在运往美国之前，
英文字幕：a site had to be found for it, and a pedestal had to be built.
中文字幕：必须为它找到一个地点，并建造一个基座。
英文字幕：The site chosen was an island at the entrance of New York Harbor.
中文字幕：选定的地点是纽约港入口处的一个岛屿。
英文字幕：By 1884, a statue, which was 151 feet tall, had been erected in Paris.
中文字幕：到1884年，一座151英尺高的雕像在巴黎竖立起来。
英文字幕：The following year, it was taken to pieces and sent to America.
中文字幕：第二年，它被拆解并运往美国。
英文字幕：By the end of October 1886, the statue had been put together again,
中文字幕：到1886年10月底，雕像已经重新组装好，
英文字幕：and it was officially presented to the American people by Bartolady.
中文字幕：它是由Bartolady正式赠送给美国人民的。
英文字幕：Ever since then, the great monument has been a symbol of liberty
中文字幕：从那时起，这座伟大的纪念碑就成为了自由的象征
英文字幕：for the millions of people who have passed through New York Harbor
中文字幕：为了数百万经过纽约港的人们
英文字幕：to make their homes in America.
中文字幕：在美国安家。