英文字幕：Lesson 68 Persistent First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：第68课坚持不懈听录音，然后回答以下问题。
英文字幕：Why did Elizabeth tell Nigel that she was going to the dentist?
中文字幕：伊丽莎白为什么告诉奈杰尔她要去看牙医？
英文字幕：I crossed the street to avoid meeting him, but he saw me and came running towards me.
中文字幕：我过马路是为了避开他，但他看见了我，朝我跑过来。
英文字幕：It was no use pretending that I had not seen him, so I waived to him.
中文字幕：假装没看见他是没有用的，所以我放弃了他。
英文字幕：I never enjoy meeting Nigel Dykes.
中文字幕：我从来都不喜欢见到奈杰尔·戴克斯。
英文字幕：He never has anything to do.
中文字幕：他从不有事可做。
英文字幕：No matter how busy you are, he always insists on coming with you.
中文字幕：无论你有多忙，他总是坚持要和你一起去。
英文字幕：I have to think of a way of preventing him from following me around all morning.
中文字幕：我必须想办法阻止他整个上午都跟着我。
英文字幕：Hello Nigel, I said.
中文字幕：你好，奈杰尔，我说。
英文字幕：Fancy meeting you here.
中文字幕：没想到在这里见到你。
英文字幕：Hi Elizabeth, Nigel answered.
中文字幕：你好，伊丽莎白，奈杰尔回答。
英文字幕：I was just wondering how to spend the morning until I saw you.
中文字幕：我只是想知道如何度过这个上午，直到我见到你。
英文字幕：You're not busy doing anything, are you?
中文字幕：你什么都不忙，是吗？
英文字幕：No, not at all, I answered.
中文字幕：不，一点也不，我回答。
英文字幕：I'm going to...
中文字幕：我要。。。
英文字幕：Would you mind my coming with you?
中文字幕：你介意我和你一起去吗？
英文字幕：He asked before I had finished speaking.
中文字幕：我还没说完，他就问道。
英文字幕：Not at all, I lied.
中文字幕：一点也不，我撒谎了。
英文字幕：But I'm going to the dentist.
中文字幕：但我要去看牙医。
英文字幕：Then I'll come with you, he answered.
中文字幕：那我跟你一起去，他回答。
英文字幕：There's always plenty to read in the waiting room.
中文字幕：候诊室里总是有很多书要读。