英文字幕：Lesson 3. Please send me a card.
中文字幕：课3。请给我寄张卡片。
英文字幕：First, listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：首先，听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：How many cards did the writer send?
中文字幕：作者寄了多少张卡片？
英文字幕：Postcards always spoil my holidays.
中文字幕：明信片总是破坏我的假期。
英文字幕：Last summer, I went to Italy.
中文字幕：去年夏天，我去了意大利。
英文字幕：I visited museums and sat in public gardens.
中文字幕：我参观了博物馆，坐在公共花园里。
英文字幕：A friendly waiter taught me a few words of Italian.
中文字幕：一位友好的服务员教了我几句意大利语。
英文字幕：Then he lent me a book.
中文字幕：然后他借给我一本书。
英文字幕：I read a few lines, but I did not understand a word.
中文字幕：我读了几行，但一个字也听不懂。
英文字幕：Every day I thought about postcards.
中文字幕：我每天都在想明信片。
英文字幕：My holidays passed quickly, but I did not send cards to my friends.
中文字幕：我的假期过得很快，但我没有给朋友寄卡片。
英文字幕：On the last day, I made a big decision.
中文字幕：在最后一天，我做出了一个重大决定。
英文字幕：I got up early and bought 37 cards.
中文字幕：我早早起床，买了37张卡片。
英文字幕：I spent the whole day in my room, but I did not write a single card.
中文字幕：我在房间里呆了一整天，但一张卡片也没写。