英文字幕：Lesson ten. Not for jazz.
中文字幕：第十课。不适合爵士乐。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What happened to the clavicle?
中文字幕：锁骨怎么了？
英文字幕：We have an old musical instrument.
中文字幕：我们有一件旧乐器。
英文字幕：It is called a clavicle.
中文字幕：它被称为锁骨。
英文字幕：It was made in Germany in 1681.
中文字幕：它于1681年在德国制造。
英文字幕：Our clavicle is kept in the living room.
中文字幕：我们的锁骨放在客厅里。
英文字幕：It has belonged to our family for a long time.
中文字幕：它属于我们家很久了。
英文字幕：The instrument was bought by my grandfather many years ago.
中文字幕：这台乐器是我祖父多年前买的。
英文字幕：Recently it was damaged by a visitor.
中文字幕：最近，它被一位游客损坏了。
英文字幕：She tried to play jazz on it.
中文字幕：她试着用它演奏爵士乐。
英文字幕：She struck the keys too hard and two of the strings were broken.
中文字幕：她敲击琴键太用力，两根琴弦断了。
英文字幕：My father was shocked.
中文字幕：我父亲很震惊。
英文字幕：Now we are not allowed to touch it.
中文字幕：现在我们不允许碰它。
英文字幕：It is being repaired by a friend of my father's.
中文字幕：我父亲的一个朋友正在修理它。