英文字幕：Listen 12. Good bye and good luck.
中文字幕：听12。再见，祝你好运。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Where is Captain Allison going and how?
中文字幕：艾利森船长要去哪里，怎么去？
英文字幕：Our neighbour, Captain Charles Allison, will sail from Portsmouth tomorrow.
中文字幕：我们的邻居查尔斯·艾利森船长明天将从朴茨茅斯启航。
英文字幕：We'll meet him at the harbour early in the morning.
中文字幕：我们一大早在港口见他。
英文字幕：He will be in his small boat, Topsil.
中文字幕：他将在他的小船托普西尔号上。
英文字幕：Topsil is a famous little boat.
中文字幕：Topsil是一艘著名的小船。
英文字幕：It has sailed across the Atlantic many times.
中文字幕：它已多次横渡大西洋。
英文字幕：Captain Allison will set out at eight o'clock, so we'll have plenty of time.
中文字幕：艾利森船长将于八点钟出发，因此我们有充足的时间。
英文字幕：We'll see his boat and then we'll say goodbye to him.
中文字幕：我们会去看他的船，然后跟他道别。
英文字幕：He will be away for two months.
中文字幕：他将离开两个月。
英文字幕：We are very proud of him.
中文字幕：我们为他感到骄傲。
英文字幕：He will take part in an important race across the Atlantic.
中文字幕：他将参加一场横跨大西洋的重要比赛。