英文字幕：Listen 27. A wet night.
中文字幕：听着27。一个潮湿的夜晚。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What happened to the boys in the night?
中文字幕：晚上男孩们怎么了？
英文字幕：Late in the afternoon, the boys put up their tent in the middle of a field.
中文字幕：下午晚些时候，男孩们在田野中央支起了帐篷。
英文字幕：As soon as this was done, they cooked a meal over an open fire.
中文字幕：他们一做完，就在明火上煮了一顿饭。
英文字幕：They were all hungry and the food smelled good.
中文字幕：他们都饿了，食物闻起来很香。
英文字幕：After a wonderful meal, they told stories and sang songs by the campfire.
中文字幕：吃完一顿美餐后，他们在篝火旁讲故事、唱歌。
英文字幕：But sometime later, it began to rain.
中文字幕：但过了一会儿，天开始下雨了。
英文字幕：The boys felt tired, so they put out the fire and crept into their tent.
中文字幕：男孩子们觉得累了，于是他们熄灭了火，悄悄溜进了帐篷。
英文字幕：Their sleeping bags were warm and comfortable, so they all slept soundly.
中文字幕：他们的睡袋温暖舒适，所以他们都睡得很香。
英文字幕：In the middle of the night, two boys woke up and began shouting.
中文字幕：半夜，两个男孩醒了过来，开始大叫。
英文字幕：The tent was full of water.
中文字幕：帐篷里装满了水。
英文字幕：They all leapt out of their sleeping bags and hurried outside.
中文字幕：他们都从睡袋里跳出来，匆匆忙忙地走到外面。
英文字幕：It was raining heavily and they found that a stream had formed in the field.
中文字幕：雨下得很大，他们发现田里已经形成了一条小溪。
英文字幕：The stream wound its way across the field and then flowed right under their tent.
中文字幕：溪水蜿蜒穿过田野，然后正好从他们的帐篷下面流过。