英文字幕：Lesson 61.
中文字幕：课61。
英文字幕：Trouble with the Hubble.
中文字幕：哈勃望远镜出了问题。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What is the special importance of a telescope in space?
中文字幕：望远镜在太空中的特殊重要性是什么？
英文字幕：The Hubble telescope was launched into space by NASA on April 20, 1990.
中文字幕：哈勃望远镜于1990年4月20日由美国国家航空航天局发射升空。
英文字幕：At a cost of over a billion dollars.
中文字幕：耗资超过10亿美元。
英文字幕：Right from the start there was trouble with the Hubble.
中文字幕：哈勃望远镜从一开始就出了问题。
英文字幕：The pictures it sent us were very disappointing because its main mirror was faulty.
中文字幕：它发给我们的照片非常令人失望，因为它的主镜有问题。
英文字幕：NASA is now going to put the telescope right, so it will soon be sending up four astronauts to repair it.
中文字幕：美国国家航空航天局现在将对望远镜进行修复，因此很快将派出四名宇航员对其进行维修。
英文字幕：The shuttle Endeavour will be taking the astronauts to the Hubble.
中文字幕：奋进号航天飞机将把宇航员送往哈勃太空望远镜。
英文字幕：A robot arm from the Endeavour will grab the telescope and hold it while the astronauts make the necessary repairs.
中文字幕：当宇航员进行必要的维修时，奋进号上的一个机械臂将抓住望远镜并握住它。
英文字幕：Of course the Hubble is above the Earth's atmosphere, so it will soon be sending us the clearest pictures of the stars and distant galaxies
中文字幕：当然，哈勃望远镜位于地球大气层之上，所以它很快就会向我们发送最清晰的恒星和遥远星系的照片
英文字幕：that we have ever seen.
中文字幕：这是我们见过的。
英文字幕：The Hubble will tell us a great deal about the age and size of the universe.
中文字幕：哈勃望远镜将告诉我们很多关于宇宙的年龄和大小的信息。
英文字幕：By the time you read this, the Hubble's eagle eye will have sent us thousands and thousands of wonderful pictures.
中文字幕：当你读到这篇文章的时候，哈勃望远镜的鹰眼已经给我们发送了成千上万张精彩的照片。