英文字幕：Lesson 39.
中文字幕：课39。
英文字幕：Am I alright?
中文字幕：我还好吗？
英文字幕：First listen, and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why did Mr Gilbert telephone Dr. Millington?
中文字幕：吉尔伯特先生为什么给米林顿医生打电话？
英文字幕：While John Gilbert was in hospital,
中文字幕：约翰·吉尔伯特住院期间，
英文字幕：he asked his doctor to tell him
中文字幕：他请医生告诉他
英文字幕：whether his operation had been successful.
中文字幕：他的手术是否成功。
英文字幕：But the doctor refused to do so.
中文字幕：但医生拒绝这样做。
英文字幕：The following day, the patient asked for a bedside telephone.
中文字幕：第二天，病人要求床边电话。
英文字幕：When he was alone, he telephoned the hospital exchange
中文字幕：当他独自一人时，他给医院的交换机打了电话
英文字幕：and asked for Dr. Millington.
中文字幕：并找了米林顿医生。
英文字幕：When the doctor answered the phone,
中文字幕：当医生接电话时，
英文字幕：Mr Gilbert said he was inquiring about a certain patient.
中文字幕：吉尔伯特先生说他正在询问一位病人的情况。
英文字幕：A Mr. John Gilbert.
中文字幕：约翰·吉尔伯特先生。
英文字幕：He asked if Mr. Gilbert's operation had been successful,
中文字幕：他问吉尔伯特先生的手术是否成功，
英文字幕：and the doctor told him that it had been.
中文字幕：医生告诉他，情况确实如此。
英文字幕：He then asked when Mr. Gilbert would be allowed to go home,
中文字幕：然后他问吉尔伯特先生什么时候可以回家，
英文字幕：and the doctor told him that you would have to stay in hospital for another two weeks.
中文字幕：医生告诉他，你必须再住院两周。
英文字幕：Then Dr. Millington asked the caller if he was a relative of the patient.
中文字幕：然后，米林顿医生问来电者是否是患者的亲属。
英文字幕：No, the patient answered.
中文字幕：不，病人回答。
英文字幕：I am Mr. John Gilbert.
中文字幕：我是约翰·吉尔伯特先生。