英文字幕：Listen 95.
中文字幕：听着95。
英文字幕：A fantasy.
中文字幕：幻想。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why was the ambassador particularly lucky?
中文字幕：为什么这位大使特别幸运？
英文字幕：When the ambassador of Escalopia returned home for lunch, his wife got a shock.
中文字幕：当Escalopia大使回家吃午饭时，他的妻子大吃一惊。
英文字幕：He looked pale and his clothes were in a frightful state.
中文字幕：他脸色苍白，衣服破旧不堪。
英文字幕：What has happened, she asked?
中文字幕：发生了什么事，她问？
英文字幕：How did your clothes get into such a mess?
中文字幕：你的衣服怎么弄得这么乱？
英文字幕：A fire extinguished her my dear.
中文字幕：亲爱的，一场大火把她扑灭了。
英文字幕：Answered the ambassador dryly.
中文字幕：大使冷冷地回答。
英文字幕：University students said the embassy on fire this morning.
中文字幕：大学生说，大使馆今天上午起火。
英文字幕：Good heavens exclaimed his wife and where were you at the time?
中文字幕：天哪，他的妻子惊呼道，你当时在哪里？
英文字幕：I was in my office as usual.
中文字幕：我像往常一样在办公室里。
英文字幕：Answered the ambassador.
中文字幕：大使回答。
英文字幕：The fire broke out in the basement.
中文字幕：地下室发生了火灾。
英文字幕：I went down immediately of course and that fool hoist aimed a fire extinguisher at me.
中文字幕：当然，我立刻就下去了，那个愚蠢的起重机把灭火器对准了我。
英文字幕：He thought I was on fire.
中文字幕：他以为我着火了。
英文字幕：I must definitely get that fellow posted.
中文字幕：我一定要把那个家伙叫出去。
英文字幕：The ambassador's wife went on asking questions when she suddenly noticed a big hole in her husband's
中文字幕：大使的妻子继续问问题，突然发现丈夫的鞋上有个大洞
英文字幕：hat.
中文字幕：帽子。
英文字幕：And how can you explain that?
中文字幕：你怎么解释呢？
英文字幕：She asked.
中文字幕：她问。
英文字幕：All that said the ambassador.
中文字幕：大使说了这么多。
英文字幕：Someone fired a shot through my office window.
中文字幕：有人从我办公室的窗户开了一枪。
英文字幕：Accurate don't you think?
中文字幕：准确，你不觉得吗？
英文字幕：Fortunately I wasn't wearing it at the time.
中文字幕：幸运的是，当时我没有戴它。
英文字幕：If I had been, I would not have been able to get home for lunch.
中文字幕：如果我去了，我就不能回家吃午饭了。