英文字幕：Lesson 40. Food and talk.
中文字幕：课40。食物和谈话。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Was Mrs. Rumble a good companion at dinner?
中文字幕：朗布尔太太是晚餐的好伙伴吗？
英文字幕：Last week at the dinner party, the hostess asked me to sit next to Mrs. Rumble.
中文字幕：上周在晚宴上，女主人让我坐在朗布尔太太旁边。
英文字幕：Mrs. Rumble was a large, unsmiling lady in a tight black dress.
中文字幕：朗布尔太太身材高大，面无表情，身穿黑色紧身连衣裙。
英文字幕：She did not even look up when I took my seat beside her.
中文字幕：我坐在她旁边时，她甚至没有抬头。
英文字幕：Her eyes were fixed on her plate and in a short time she was busy eating.
中文字幕：她的眼睛盯着盘子，很快她就忙着吃东西了。
英文字幕：I tried to make conversation.
中文字幕：我试图进行对话。
英文字幕：A new player is coming to the globe soon.
中文字幕：一个新玩家很快就会来到世界各地。
英文字幕：I said, will you be seeing it?
中文字幕：我说，你会看到吗？
英文字幕：No. She answered.
中文字幕：不，她回答。
英文字幕：Will you be spending your holidays abroad this year?
中文字幕：今年你会去国外度假吗？
英文字幕：I asked.
中文字幕：我问。
英文字幕：No. She answered.
中文字幕：不，她回答。
英文字幕：Will you be staying in England?
中文字幕：你会留在英国吗？
英文字幕：No. She answered.
中文字幕：不，她回答。
英文字幕：In despair.
中文字幕：绝望。
英文字幕：I asked her whether she was enjoying her dinner.
中文字幕：我问她是否喜欢她的晚餐。
英文字幕：Young man, she answered.
中文字幕：年轻人，她回答。
英文字幕：If you ate more and talked less, we would both enjoy our dinner.
中文字幕：如果你多吃少说话，我们俩都会喜欢我们的晚餐。