英文字幕：Lesson 57.
中文字幕：课57。
英文字幕：Can I help you, Madam?
中文字幕：夫人，我能帮你吗？
英文字幕：First, listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：首先，听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Did the woman get what she wanted?
中文字幕：那个女人得到她想要的了吗？
英文字幕：A woman in jeans stood at the window of an expensive shop.
中文字幕：一个穿着牛仔裤的女人站在一家高档商店的橱窗前。
英文字幕：Though she hesitated for a moment, she finally went in and asked to see a dress that was
中文字幕：虽然她犹豫了一会儿，但她终于走了进去，要求看一件
英文字幕：in the window.
中文字幕：在窗口。
英文字幕：The assistant who served her did not like the way she was dressed.
中文字幕：为她服务的助理不喜欢她的穿着。
英文字幕：Glancing at her scornfully, he told her that the dress was sold.
中文字幕：他轻蔑地瞥了她一眼，告诉她那件衣服已经卖完了。
英文字幕：The woman walked out of the shop angrily and decided to punish the assistant next day.
中文字幕：那女人怒气冲冲地走出商店，决定第二天惩罚店员。
英文字幕：She returned to the shop the following morning dressed in a fur coat with a handbag in one hand
中文字幕：第二天早上，她穿着皮大衣，一只手拿着手提包回到商店
英文字幕：and a long umbrella in the other.
中文字幕：另一把是一把长伞。
英文字幕：After seeking out the rude assistant, she asked for the same dress.
中文字幕：在找到那个粗鲁的店员后，她要求穿同样的衣服。
英文字幕：Not realizing who she was, the assistant was eager to serve her this time.
中文字幕：这位助手没有意识到她是谁，这次急于为她服务。
英文字幕：With great difficulty, he climbed into the shop window to get the dress.
中文字幕：他费力地爬进商店橱窗去拿那件衣服。
英文字幕：As soon as she saw it, the woman said she did not like it.
中文字幕：她一看到它，女人就说她不喜欢它。
英文字幕：She enjoyed herself making the assistant bring almost everything in the window.
中文字幕：她很乐意让店员把橱窗里的几乎所有东西都带来。
英文字幕：Before finally buying the dress, she had first asked for.
中文字幕：在最终买下这件衣服之前，她先提出了要求。