英文字幕：Lesson 66.
中文字幕：课66。
英文字幕：Sweaters honey.
中文字幕：毛衣蜂蜜。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What was Sweaters honey and why?
中文字幕：什么是毛衣蜂蜜，为什么？
英文字幕：In 1963, a Lancaster bomber crashed on Wallace Island, a remote place in the South Pacific.
中文字幕：1963年，一架兰开斯特轰炸机在南太平洋的华莱士岛坠毁。
英文字幕：A long way west of Samoa.
中文字幕：萨摩亚以西很远。
英文字幕：The plane wasn't too badly damaged, but over the years the crash was forgotten and the
中文字幕：飞机的损坏并不严重，但多年来，人们已经忘记了那次坠机事件
英文字幕：wreck remained undisturbed.
中文字幕：沉船没有受到干扰。
英文字幕：Then in 1989, 26 years after the crash, the plane was accidentally rediscovered in an aerial
中文字幕：然后在1989年，坠机26年后，这架飞机在一架飞机上意外被重新发现
英文字幕：survey of the island.
中文字幕：岛的调查。
英文字幕：By this time, a Lancaster bomber in reasonable condition was rare and worth rescuing.
中文字幕：到那时，状况良好的兰开斯特轰炸机已经很少见了，值得抢救。
英文字幕：The French authorities had the plane packaged and moved in parts back to France.
中文字幕：法国当局将飞机打包并分批运回法国。
英文字幕：Now a group of enthusiasts are going to have the plane restored.
中文字幕：现在，一群爱好者将修复这架飞机。
英文字幕：It has four Rolls-Royce Merlin engines, but the group will need to have only three of
中文字幕：它有四台劳斯莱斯梅林发动机，但该集团只需要三台
英文字幕：them rebuilt.
中文字幕：他们重建。
英文字幕：Imagine their surprise and delight when they broke open the packing cases and found that
中文字幕：想象一下，当他们打开包装箱发现
英文字幕：the fourth engine was Sweaters honey.
中文字幕：第四台发动机是斯威特蜂蜜发动机。
英文字幕：Still in perfect condition.
中文字幕：仍然处于完美状态。
英文字幕：A colony of bees had turned the engine into a hive and it was totally preserved in beeswax.
中文字幕：一群蜜蜂把发动机变成了蜂箱，它完全保存在蜂蜡里。