英文字幕：Lesson 37
中文字幕：第37课
英文字幕：The Olympic Games
中文字幕：奥林匹克运动会
英文字幕：First listen
中文字幕：先听我说
英文字幕：And then answer the question
中文字幕：然后回答问题
英文字幕：When was the last time this country hosted the Olympic Games?
中文字幕：这个国家上一次举办奥运会是什么时候？
英文字幕：The Olympic Games will be held in our country in four years' time
中文字幕：四年后，奥运会将在我国举行
英文字幕：As a great many people will be visiting the country
中文字幕：由于将有很多人访问这个国家
英文字幕：The government will be building new hotels, an immense stadium, and a new Olympic standard swimming pool
中文字幕：政府将建造新的酒店、一个巨大的体育场和一个新的奥运标准游泳池
英文字幕：They will also be building new roads and a special railway line
中文字幕：他们还将修建新的道路和一条特殊的铁路线
英文字幕：The Games will be held just outside the capital
中文字幕：奥运会将在首都郊外举行
英文字幕：And the whole area will be called Olympic City
中文字幕：整个地区将被称为奥林匹克城
英文字幕：Workers will have completed the new roads by the end of this year
中文字幕：工人们将在今年年底前完成新道路的建设
英文字幕：By the end of next year they will have finished work on the new stadium
中文字幕：到明年年底，他们将完成新体育场的工程
英文字幕：The fantastic modern buildings have been designed by Kurt Gunter
中文字幕：这些梦幻般的现代建筑是由库尔特·冈特设计的
英文字幕：Everybody will be watching anxiously as the new buildings go up
中文字幕：当新建筑拔地而起时，每个人都会焦急地看着
英文字幕：We are all very excited and are looking forward to the Olympic Games
中文字幕：我们都很兴奋，期待着奥运会
英文字幕：Because they have never been held before in this country
中文字幕：因为他们以前从未在这个国家被关押过