英文字幕：Lesson 29. Taxi
中文字幕：课29。出租车
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Does captain force it? Think any trip is too dangerous?
中文字幕：船长会强迫吗？你觉得任何旅行都太危险了吗？
英文字幕：Captain Ben Forset has bought an unusual taxi and has begun a new service.
中文字幕：本·福塞特上尉买了一辆不同寻常的出租车，并开始了一项新服务。
英文字幕：The taxi is a small Swiss aeroplane called a Pilates Porter.
中文字幕：这辆出租车是一架名为Pilates Porter的瑞士小型飞机。
英文字幕：This wonderful plane can carry seven passengers.
中文字幕：这架漂亮的飞机能载七名乘客。
英文字幕：The most surprising thing about it however is that it can land anywhere on snow, water or even on a ploughed field.
中文字幕：然而，最令人惊讶的是，它可以降落在雪地、水面甚至犁地上的任何地方。
英文字幕：Captain Forset's first passenger was a doctor who flew from Birmingham to a lonely village in the Welsh Mountains.
中文字幕：福塞特上尉的第一位乘客是一名医生，他从伯明翰飞往威尔士山脉的一个偏僻村庄。
英文字幕：Since then, captain Forset has flown passengers to many unusual places.
中文字幕：从那时起，福塞特机长就把乘客送到了许多不寻常的地方。
英文字幕：Once he landed on the roof of a block of flats and on another occasion he landed in a deserted car park.
中文字幕：有一次，他降落在一栋公寓楼的屋顶上，另一次他降落在了一个废弃的停车场。
英文字幕：Captain Forset has just refused a strange request from a businessman.
中文字幕：福塞特船长刚刚拒绝了一位商人的奇怪请求。
英文字幕：The man wanted to fly to Rockall, a lonely island in the Atlantic Ocean.
中文字幕：这个人想飞到大西洋上的一个孤岛罗卡尔岛。
英文字幕：But captain Forset did not take him because the trip was too dangerous.
中文字幕：但福塞特船长没有带他去，因为这次旅行太危险了。