英文字幕：Lesson 83.
中文字幕：课83。
英文字幕：After the elections.
中文字幕：选举之后。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why did Patrick keep on asking the same question?
中文字幕：为什么帕特里克总是问同样的问题？
英文字幕：The former Prime Minister, Mr Wentworth Lane,
中文字幕：前首相温特沃斯·莱恩先生，
英文字幕：was defeated in the recent elections.
中文字幕：在最近的选举中被击败。
英文字幕：He is now retiring from political life and has gone abroad.
中文字幕：他现在正从政治生活中退休，已经出国了。
英文字幕：My friend Patrick has always been a fanatical opponent of Mr Lane's radical progressive party.
中文字幕：我的朋友帕特里克一直是莱恩激进进步党的狂热反对者。
英文字幕：After the elections, Patrick went to the former Prime Minister's house.
中文字幕：选举结束后，帕特里克去了前首相家。
英文字幕：When he asked if Mr Lane lived there,
中文字幕：当他问莱恩先生是否住在那里时，
英文字幕：the policeman on duty told him that since his defeat,
中文字幕：值班警察告诉他，自从他失败后，
英文字幕：the ex-Prime Minister had gone abroad.
中文字幕：前首相出国了。
英文字幕：On the following day, Patrick went to the house again.
中文字幕：第二天，帕特里克又去了那所房子。
英文字幕：The same policeman was just walking slowly past the entrance
中文字幕：同一个警察正慢慢地走过入口
英文字幕：when Patrick asked the same question.
中文字幕：帕特里克问了同样的问题。
英文字幕：Though a little suspicious this time,
中文字幕：虽然这次有点可疑，
英文字幕：the policeman gave him the same answer.
中文字幕：警察给了他同样的答案。
英文字幕：The day after, Patrick went to the house once more
中文字幕：第二天，帕特里克又去了那所房子
英文字幕：and asked exactly the same question.
中文字幕：并提出了完全相同的问题。
英文字幕：This time, the policeman lost his temper.
中文字幕：这一次，警察发了脾气。
英文字幕：I told you yesterday and the day before yesterday,
中文字幕：我昨天和前天都告诉过你，
英文字幕：he shouted, Mr Lane was defeated in the elections.
中文字幕：他喊道，莱恩先生在选举中失败了。
英文字幕：He has retired from political life and gone to live abroad.
中文字幕：他已经退出政治生活，去国外生活了。
英文字幕：I know, answered Patrick, but I love to hear you say it.
中文字幕：我知道，帕特里克回答，但我喜欢听你这么说。