英文字幕：Lesson 46. Expensive and uncomfortable.
中文字幕：课46。昂贵又不舒服。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What did the man in this story do?
中文字幕：这个故事中的男人做了什么？
英文字幕：When a plane from London arrived at Sydney Airport,
中文字幕：当一架来自伦敦的飞机抵达悉尼机场时，
英文字幕：workers began to unload a number of wooden boxes which contained clothing.
中文字幕：工人们开始卸下一些装着衣服的木箱。
英文字幕：No one could account for the fact that one of the boxes was extremely heavy.
中文字幕：没有人能解释其中一个箱子非常重的事实。
英文字幕：It suddenly occurred to one of the workers to open up the box.
中文字幕：一个工人突然想到打开箱子。
英文字幕：He was astonished at what he found.
中文字幕：他对自己的发现感到惊讶。
英文字幕：A man was lying in the box on top of a pile of woolen goods.
中文字幕：一个男人躺在箱子里的一堆羊毛制品上。
英文字幕：He was so surprised at being discovered that he did not even try to run away.
中文字幕：他被发现时非常惊讶，甚至没有试图逃跑。
英文字幕：After he was arrested, the man admitted hiding in the box before the plane left London.
中文字幕：被捕后，该男子承认在飞机离开伦敦前躲在箱子里。
英文字幕：He had had a long and uncomfortable trip.
中文字幕：他经历了一次漫长而不舒服的旅行。
英文字幕：For he had been confined to the wooden box for over 18 hours,
中文字幕：因为他被关在木箱里已经18个多小时了，
英文字幕：the man was ordered to pay £3,500 for the cost of the trip.
中文字幕：该男子被命令支付3500英镑的旅行费用。
英文字幕：The normal price of a ticket is £2,000.
中文字幕：门票的正常价格是2000英镑。