英文字幕：Lesson 90.
中文字幕：课90。
英文字幕：What's for supper?
中文字幕：晚饭吃什么？
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What kind of fish are they?
中文字幕：它们是什么鱼？
英文字幕：Fish and chips has always been a favourite dish in Britain.
中文字幕：炸鱼薯条一直是英国人最喜欢的菜。
英文字幕：But as the oceans have been overfished,
中文字幕：但随着海洋被过度捕捞，
英文字幕：fish has become more and more expensive.
中文字幕：鱼变得越来越贵了。
英文字幕：So it comes as a surprise to learn that giant fish are terrifying the divers on North Sea oil rigs.
中文字幕：因此，当得知北海石油钻井平台上的潜水员正被巨型鱼类吓坏时，人们感到很惊讶。
英文字幕：Oil rigs have to be repaired frequently.
中文字幕：石油钻井平台必须经常维修。
英文字幕：And divers, who often have to work in darkness, a hundred feet underwater,
中文字幕：潜水员，他们经常不得不在黑暗中工作，在水下一百英尺处，
英文字幕：have been frightened out of their wits by giant fish bumping into them as they work.
中文字幕：他们工作时被撞到的大鱼吓得魂不附体。
英文字幕：Now they have had special cages made to protect them from these monsters.
中文字幕：现在，他们已经制作了特殊的笼子来保护自己免受这些怪物的伤害。
英文字幕：The fish are not sharks or killer whales,
中文字幕：这些鱼不是鲨鱼或虎鲸，
英文字幕：but favourite eating varieties like cod and skate,
中文字幕：但最受欢迎的食用品种，如鳕鱼和滑冰，
英文字幕：which grow to unnatural sizes,
中文字幕：其生长到不自然的大小，
英文字幕：sometimes as much as 12 feet in length.
中文字幕：有时长达12英尺。
英文字幕：Three factors of course these fish to grow so large.
中文字幕：当然，这些鱼长得这么大有三个因素。
英文字幕：The warm water round the hot oil pipes under the sea.
中文字幕：海底热油管周围的温水。
英文字幕：The plentiful supply of food thrown overboard by the crews on the rigs.
中文字幕：钻井平台上船员扔到船外的大量食物。
英文字幕：The total absence of fishing boats around the oil rigs.
中文字幕：石油钻井平台周围完全没有渔船。
英文字幕：As a result the fish just eat and eat and grow and grow in the lovely warm water.
中文字幕：因此，鱼只是在可爱的温水中吃、吃、长、长。
英文字幕：Who eats who?
中文字幕：谁吃谁？
英文字幕：The fish is the most delicious fish in the world.
中文字幕：这条鱼是世界上最美味的鱼。