英文字幕：Lesson 89. A slip of the tongue. First, listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课89。口误。首先，听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Who made the only funny joke that evening and why?
中文字幕：那天晚上唯一好笑的笑话是谁讲的，为什么？
英文字幕：People will do anything to see a free show, even if it is a bad one.
中文字幕：人们愿意做任何事情去看一场免费的演出，即使它很糟糕。
英文字幕：Then the news got round that a comedy show would be presented at our local cinema by the
中文字幕：然后消息传开了，我们当地的电影院将上演一场喜剧表演
英文字幕：P and U Birdseed company. We all rushed to see it. We had to queue for hours to get in and
中文字幕：P和U Birdseed公司。我们都急着去看。我们不得不排队几个小时才能进去
英文字幕：there must have been several hundred people present just before the show began.
中文字幕：演出开始前一定有几百人出席。
英文字幕：Unfortunately, the show was one of the dullest we have ever seen. Those who failed to get
中文字幕：不幸的是，这场演出是我们见过的最无聊的演出之一。那些没有得到
英文字幕：in need not have felt disappointed as many of the artists who should have appeared did not come.
中文字幕：他们不必感到失望，因为许多应该出现的艺术家没有来。
英文字幕：The only funny things we heard that evening came from the advertiser at the beginning of the program.
中文字幕：那天晚上我们听到的唯一有趣的事情来自节目开始时的广告商。
英文字幕：He was obviously very nervous and for some minutes stood awkwardly before the microphone.
中文字幕：他显然非常紧张，尴尬地站在麦克风前好几分钟。
英文字幕：As soon as he opened his mouth, everyone burst out laughing.
中文字幕：他一开口，大家都笑了起来。
英文字幕：We all know what the poor man should have said, but what he actually said was,
中文字幕：我们都知道这个可怜的人应该说什么，但他实际上说的是，
英文字幕：this is the Poo and E-seed Bird Company. Good ladies, evening and gentlemen.
中文字幕：这是Poo和E-seed Bird公司。女士们，晚上好，先生们。