英文字幕：Lesson 79. Buy air.
中文字幕：课79。买空气。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why did the plane turn back?
中文字幕：飞机为什么折返？
英文字幕：I used to travel by air a great deal when I was a boy.
中文字幕：我小时候经常坐飞机旅行。
英文字幕：My parents used to live in South America,
中文字幕：我父母以前住在南美洲，
英文字幕：and I used to fly there from Europe in the holidays.
中文字幕：我过去常常在假期从欧洲飞到那里。
英文字幕：A flight attendant would take charge of me,
中文字幕：空乘人员会负责我，
英文字幕：and I never had an unpleasant experience.
中文字幕：我从未有过不愉快的经历。
英文字幕：I'm used to travelling by air,
中文字幕：我习惯坐飞机旅行，
英文字幕：and only on one occasion have I ever felt frightened.
中文字幕：只有一次我感到害怕。
英文字幕：After taking off, we were flying low over the city
中文字幕：起飞后，我们在城市上空低空飞行
英文字幕：and slowly gaining height.
中文字幕：并缓慢地增加高度。
英文字幕：When the plane suddenly turned round and flew back to the airport.
中文字幕：当飞机突然掉头飞回机场时。
英文字幕：While we were waiting to land,
中文字幕：当我们等待降落时，
英文字幕：a flight attendant told us to keep calm
中文字幕：一位空姐告诉我们保持冷静
英文字幕：and to get off the plane quietly as soon as it had touched down.
中文字幕：飞机一着陆就安静地下了飞机。
英文字幕：Everybody on board was worried,
中文字幕：船上的每个人都很担心，
英文字幕：and we were curious to find out what had happened.
中文字幕：我们很想知道发生了什么事。
英文字幕：Later we learned that there was a very important person on board.
中文字幕：后来我们得知船上有一个非常重要的人。
英文字幕：The police had been told that a bomb had been planted on the plane.
中文字幕：警方被告知飞机上安放了一枚炸弹。
英文字幕：After we had landed, the plane was searched thoroughly.
中文字幕：我们降落后，对飞机进行了彻底搜查。
英文字幕：Fortunately, nothing was found,
中文字幕：幸运的是，什么也没找到，
英文字幕：and five hours later we were able to take off again.
中文字幕：五个小时后，我们又可以起飞了。