英文字幕：Lesson 87. A perfect alibi. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课87。完美的不在场证明。听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What was wrong with the man's story?
中文字幕：这个男人的故事怎么了？
英文字幕：At the time the murderer was committed, I was travelling on the eight o'clock train
中文字幕：凶手被杀时，我正乘坐八点钟的火车
英文字幕：to London, said the man.
中文字幕：去伦敦，那人说。
英文字幕：Do you always catch such an early train?
中文字幕：你总是赶这么早的火车吗？
英文字幕：Asked the inspector.
中文字幕：检查员问。
英文字幕：Of course I do, answered the man.
中文字幕：我当然知道，那人回答。
英文字幕：I must be at work at ten o'clock.
中文字幕：我必须在十点钟上班。
英文字幕：My employer will confirm that I was there on time.
中文字幕：我的雇主会确认我准时到了那里。
英文字幕：Would a later train get you to work on time?
中文字幕：晚点的火车能让你准时上班吗？
英文字幕：Asked the inspector.
中文字幕：检查员问。
英文字幕：I suppose it would, but I never catch a later train.
中文字幕：我想会的，但我从来没有赶上晚一点的火车。
英文字幕：At what time did you arrive at the station?
中文字幕：你什么时候到车站的？
英文字幕：At ten to eight.
中文字幕：十点八分。
英文字幕：I bought a paper and waited for the train.
中文字幕：我买了一份报纸，等着火车。
英文字幕：And you didn't notice anything unusual?
中文字幕：你没有注意到任何异常吗？
英文字幕：Of course not.
中文字幕：当然不是。
英文字幕：I suggest, said the inspector, that you are not telling the truth.
中文字幕：我建议，巡查员说，你没有说实话。
英文字幕：I suggest that you did not catch the eight o'clock train,
中文字幕：我建议你没有赶上八点钟的火车，
英文字幕：but that you caught the eight twenty-five,
中文字幕：但你抓住了八点二十五分，
英文字幕：which would still get you to work on time.
中文字幕：这仍然会让你准时工作。
英文字幕：You see, on the morning of the murder,
中文字幕：你看，在谋杀案发生的那天早上，
英文字幕：the eight o'clock train did not run at all.
中文字幕：八点钟的火车根本没开。
英文字幕：It broke down at Fern Green station and was taken off the line.
中文字幕：它在Fern Green站发生故障，被下了车。