英文字幕：Lesson 88.
中文字幕：课88。
英文字幕：Trapped in a mine.
中文字幕：被困在矿井里。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why is the rescue taking so long?
中文字幕：为什么救援需要这么长时间？
英文字幕：Six men have been trapped in a mine for 17 hours.
中文字幕：六名男子被困在矿井里17个小时。
英文字幕：If they are not brought to the surface soon, they may lose their lives.
中文字幕：如果他们不尽快浮出水面，他们可能会失去生命。
英文字幕：However, rescue operations are proving difficult.
中文字幕：然而，事实证明救援行动很困难。
英文字幕：If explosives are used, vibrations will cause the roof of the mine to collapse.
中文字幕：如果使用炸药，震动会导致矿井顶部坍塌。
英文字幕：Rescue workers are therefore drilling a hole on the north side of the mine.
中文字幕：因此，救援人员正在矿井北侧钻孔。
英文字幕：They intend to bring the men up in a special capsule.
中文字幕：他们打算用一个特殊的太空舱把这些人带上来。
英文字幕：If they had not been a hard layer of rock beneath the soil, they would have completed
中文字幕：如果它们不是土壤下的一层坚硬的岩石，它们就会完成
英文字幕：the job in a few hours.
中文字幕：几个小时后就可以完成工作了。
英文字幕：As it is, they have been drilling for 16 hours and they still have a long way to go.
中文字幕：事实上，他们已经钻探了16个小时，还有很长的路要走。
英文字幕：Meanwhile a microphone which was lowered into the mine two hours ago has enabled the men
中文字幕：与此同时，两小时前放入矿井的麦克风使这些人能够
英文字幕：to keep in touch with their closest relatives.
中文字幕：与他们最亲近的亲戚保持联系。
英文字幕：Although they are running out of food and drink, the men are cheerful and confident that
中文字幕：尽管他们的食物和饮料快用完了，但这些人仍然很开心，很有信心
英文字幕：they would get out soon, they have been told that the rescue operations are progressing
中文字幕：他们很快就会出来的，他们被告知救援行动正在进行中
英文字幕：smoothly.
中文字幕：顺利。
英文字幕：If they knew how difficult it was to drill through the hard rock, they would lose heart.
中文字幕：如果他们知道钻穿坚硬的岩石有多难，他们就会失去信心。