英文字幕：Lesson 43
中文字幕：第43课
英文字幕：Over the South Pole
中文字幕：南极上空
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：How was the plane able to clear the mountains?
中文字幕：这架飞机是如何越过山脉的？
英文字幕：In 1929, three years after his flight over the North Pole,
中文字幕：1929年，在他飞越北极三年后，
英文字幕：the American explorer R.E. Bird successfully flew over the South Pole for the first time.
中文字幕：美国探险家R.E.伯德首次成功飞越南极。
英文字幕：Though at first, bird and his men were able to take a great many photographs of the mountains that lay below,
中文字幕：虽然起初，伯德和他的手下能够拍摄到下面山脉的大量照片，
英文字幕：they soon ran into serious trouble.
中文字幕：他们很快就遇到了严重的麻烦。
英文字幕：At one point, it seemed certain that their plane would crash.
中文字幕：有一次，他们的飞机似乎肯定会坠毁。
英文字幕：It could only get over the mountains if it rose to ten thousand feet.
中文字幕：只有上升到一万英尺，它才能越过山脉。
英文字幕：Bird at once ordered his men to throw out two heavy food sacks.
中文字幕：伯德立刻命令手下扔掉两个沉重的食物袋。
英文字幕：The plane was then able to rise and it cleared the mountains by four hundred feet.
中文字幕：飞机随后能够上升，并越过四百英尺的山脉。
英文字幕：Bird now knew that he would be able to reach the South Pole,
中文字幕：伯德现在知道他能够到达南极，
英文字幕：which was three hundred miles away, so there were no more mountains in sight.
中文字幕：那里有三百英里远，所以看不到更多的山了。
英文字幕：The aircraft was able to fly over the endless white plains without difficulty.
中文字幕：飞机能够毫无困难地飞越无边无际的白色平原。