英文字幕：Lesson 96. The dead return. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课96。死者归来。先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What happens to the lanterns at the end of the festival?
中文字幕：节日结束时灯笼会怎么样？
英文字幕：A festival for the dead is held once a year in Japan. This festival is a cheerful occasion.
中文字幕：日本每年都会举行一次亡灵节。这个节日是一个欢乐的时刻。
英文字幕：For on this day, the dead are said to return to their homes and they are welcomed by the living.
中文字幕：因为在这一天，据说死者会回到家中，受到生者的欢迎。
英文字幕：As they are expected to be hungry after their long journey, food is laid out for them.
中文字幕：由于预计他们长途旅行后会饿，所以为他们准备了食物。
英文字幕：Especially made lanterns are hung outside each house to help the dead to find their way.
中文字幕：每栋房子外面都挂着特制的灯笼，帮助死者找到路。
英文字幕：All night long, people dance and sing.
中文字幕：整夜，人们载歌载舞。
英文字幕：In the early morning, the food that had been laid out for the dead is thrown into a river or into the sea,
中文字幕：清晨，为死者准备的食物被扔进河里或海里，
英文字幕：as it is considered unlucky for anyone living to eat it.
中文字幕：因为活着的人吃它被认为是不吉利的。
英文字幕：In towns that are near the sea, the tiny lanterns which had been hung in the streets the night before,
中文字幕：在靠近大海的城镇，前一天晚上挂在街上的小灯笼，
英文字幕：are placed into the water when the festival is over.
中文字幕：节日结束后，它们被放入水中。
英文字幕：Thousands of lanterns slowly drift out to sea, guiding the dead on their return journey to the other world.
中文字幕：成千上万的灯笼缓缓飘向大海，引导死者返回另一个世界。
英文字幕：This is a moving spectacle for crowds of people stand on the shore, watching the lanterns drifting away,
中文字幕：这是一个感人的场面，人们站在岸边，看着灯笼飘走，
英文字幕：until they can be seen no more.
中文字幕：直到他们再也看不见了。