英文字幕：Lesson 23. A new house.
中文字幕：课23。一栋新房子。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why is the new house special?
中文字幕：为什么新房子很特别？
英文字幕：I had a letter from my sister yesterday.
中文字幕：我昨天收到我姐姐的一封信。
英文字幕：She lives in Nigeria.
中文字幕：她住在尼日利亚。
英文字幕：In her letter, she said that she would come to England next year.
中文字幕：她在信中说她明年要来英国。
英文字幕：If she comes, she will get a surprise.
中文字幕：如果她来了，她会得到一个惊喜。
英文字幕：We are now living in a beautiful new house in the country.
中文字幕：我们现在住在乡下一栋漂亮的新房子里。
英文字幕：Work on it had begun before my sister left.
中文字幕：在我姐姐离开之前，这项工作已经开始了。
英文字幕：The house was completed five months ago.
中文字幕：这房子五个月前竣工了。
英文字幕：In my letter, I told her that she could stay with us.
中文字幕：我在信中告诉她，她可以和我们住在一起。
英文字幕：The house has many large rooms and there is a lovely garden.
中文字幕：这所房子有许多大房间，还有一个可爱的花园。
英文字幕：It is a very modern house, so it looks strange to some people.
中文字幕：这是一座非常现代的房子，所以对一些人来说看起来很奇怪。
英文字幕：It must be the only modern house in the district.
中文字幕：这一定是这个地区唯一一栋现代化的房子。
英文字幕：The house is a very modern house.
中文字幕：这房子很现代。