英文字幕：Lesson 70. Red for danger. First, listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课70。红色代表危险。首先，听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：How was the drunk removed from the ring?
中文字幕：那个醉汉是怎么从拳击场上被带走的？
英文字幕：During a bullfight, a drunk suddenly wandered into the middle of the ring.
中文字幕：斗牛时，一个醉汉突然走进斗牛场中央。
英文字幕：The crowd began to shout, but the drunk was unaware of the danger.
中文字幕：人群开始大喊大叫，但醉汉没有意识到危险。
英文字幕：The bull was busy with the Matador at the time, but it suddenly caught sight of the drunk,
中文字幕：公牛当时正忙着对付斗牛士，但突然看见了醉汉，
英文字幕：who was shouting rude remarks and waving a red cap.
中文字幕：他大喊着粗鲁的话，挥舞着一顶红帽子。
英文字幕：Apparently sensitive to criticism, the bull forgot all about the Matador and charged at the drunk.
中文字幕：这头公牛显然对批评很敏感，它完全忘记了斗牛士，冲向了醉汉。
英文字幕：The crowd suddenly grew quiet. The drunk, however, seemed quite sure of himself.
中文字幕：人群突然安静下来。然而，醉汉似乎对自己很有信心。
英文字幕：When the bull got close to him, he clumsily stepped aside to let it pass.
中文字幕：当公牛靠近他时，他笨拙地走到一边让它过去。
英文字幕：The crowd broke into cheers and the drunk bowed.
中文字幕：人群爆发出欢呼声，醉汉鞠了一躬。
英文字幕：By this time, however, three men had come into the ring and they quickly dragged the drunk to safety.
中文字幕：然而，这时，三名男子已经进入了拳击场，他们迅速将醉汉拖到了安全地带。
英文字幕：Even the bull seemed to feel sorry for him. For it looked on sympathetically until the drunk was out of the way,
中文字幕：就连那头公牛似乎也为他感到难过。因为它同情地看着醉汉，直到醉汉让路，
英文字幕：before once more turning its attention to the Matador.
中文字幕：然后再次将注意力转向斗牛士。
英文字幕：The bull was in the ring and the drunk was in the ring.
中文字幕：公牛在拳击场，醉汉在拳击场。
英文字幕：The drunk was in the ring and the drunk was out of the way.
中文字幕：醉汉在拳击场上，醉汉躲开了。