英文字幕：Lesson 34. Quick work. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课34。快速工作。先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：How long had the police taken to find his bicycle?
中文字幕：警察花了多长时间才找到他的自行车？
英文字幕：Dan Robinson has been worried all week. Last Tuesday he received a letter from the local
中文字幕：丹·罗宾逊整个星期都很担心。上周二，他收到了当地人的来信
英文字幕：police. In the letter he was asked to call at the station. Dan wondered why he was
中文字幕：警方。信中要求他去车站。丹想知道他为什么
英文字幕：wanted by the police. But he went to the station yesterday and now he is not worried anymore.
中文字幕：被警方通缉。但他昨天去了车站，现在他不再担心了。
英文字幕：At the station he was told by a smiling policeman that his bicycle had been found.
中文字幕：在车站，一位面带微笑的警察告诉他，他的自行车被找到了。
英文字幕：Five days ago the policeman told him the bicycle was picked up in a small village 400 miles away.
中文字幕：五天前，警察告诉他，自行车在400英里外的一个小村庄被捡到。
英文字幕：It is now being sent to his home by train. Dan was most surprised when he heard the news.
中文字幕：现在它正被火车送到他家。丹听到这个消息时非常惊讶。
英文字幕：He was amused too because he never expected the bicycle to be found.
中文字幕：他也很开心，因为他从未想过自行车会被找到。
英文字幕：It was stolen 20 years ago when Dan was a boy of 15.
中文字幕：20年前，当丹还是个15岁的男孩时，它被偷了。