英文字幕：Lesson 56. Faster than sound.
中文字幕：课56。比声音还快。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：How fast did the winning car go?
中文字幕：获胜的赛车跑得有多快？
英文字幕：Once a year a race is held for old cars.
中文字幕：每年都会为旧车举行一次比赛。
英文字幕：A lot of cars entered for this race last year and there was a great deal of excitement just before it began.
中文字幕：去年有很多车参加了这场比赛，在比赛开始前，人们非常兴奋。
英文字幕：One of the most handsome cars was a Rills Royce Silver Ghost.
中文字幕：最漂亮的汽车之一是Rills Royce Silver Ghost。
英文字幕：The most unusual car was a Benz which had only three wheels.
中文字幕：最不寻常的汽车是一辆只有三个轮子的奔驰。
英文字幕：Built in 1885 it was the oldest car taking part.
中文字幕：它建于1885年，是参加比赛的最古老的汽车。
英文字幕：After a great many loud explosions the race began.
中文字幕：在一阵巨大的爆炸声之后，比赛开始了。
英文字幕：Many of the cars broke down on the course and some drivers spent more time under their cars than in them.
中文字幕：许多汽车在赛道上抛锚了，一些司机在车下待的时间比在车里多。
英文字幕：A few cars however completed the race.
中文字幕：然而，有几辆车完成了比赛。
英文字幕：The winning car reached a speed of 40 miles an hour, much faster than any of its rivals.
中文字幕：获胜的赛车达到了每小时40英里的速度，比任何竞争对手都快得多。
英文字幕：It sped downhill at the end of the race and its driver had a lot of trouble trying to stop it.
中文字幕：比赛结束时，它加速下坡，司机在试图阻止它时遇到了很多麻烦。
英文字幕：The race gave everyone a great deal of pleasure.
中文字幕：比赛给每个人带来了极大的快乐。
英文字幕：It was very different from modern car races but no less exciting.
中文字幕：它与现代汽车比赛非常不同，但同样令人兴奋。