英文字幕：Lesson 45. A clear conscience.
中文字幕：课45。问心无愧。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：How did Sam get his money back?
中文字幕：萨姆是怎么把钱要回来的？
英文字幕：The whole village soon learnt that a large sum of money had been lost.
中文字幕：全村很快都知道损失了一大笔钱。
英文字幕：Sam Benton, the local butcher, had lost his wallet while taking his savings to the post office.
中文字幕：当地屠夫萨姆·本顿在把积蓄带到邮局时丢了钱包。
英文字幕：Sam was sure that the wallet must have been found by one of the villagers.
中文字幕：山姆确信钱包一定是被一个村民找到的。
英文字幕：But it was not returned to him.
中文字幕：但它没有还给他。
英文字幕：Three months passed and then one morning, Sam found his wallet outside his front door.
中文字幕：三个月过去了，然后有一天早上，山姆在前门外发现了他的钱包。
英文字幕：It had been wrapped up in newspaper and it contained half the money he had lost.
中文字幕：它被报纸包裹着，里面装着他损失的一半钱。
英文字幕：Together with a note which said,
中文字幕：连同一张纸条，上面写着：，
英文字幕：A thief, yes. But only 50% a thief.
中文字幕：小偷，是的。但只有50%是小偷。
英文字幕：Two months later, some more money was sent to Sam with another note.
中文字幕：两个月后，又有一些钱和另一张纸条寄给了萨姆。
英文字幕：Only 25% a thief now.
中文字幕：现在只有25%是小偷。
英文字幕：In time, all Sam's money was paid back in this way.
中文字幕：随着时间的推移，萨姆的所有钱都以这种方式偿还了。
英文字幕：The last note said,
中文字幕：最后一张纸条上写着：，
英文字幕：I am 100% honest now.
中文字幕：我现在100%诚实。