英文字幕：Lesson 31. Success story. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课31。成功故事。先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What was Frank's first job? Yesterday afternoon, Frank Hawkins was telling me about his experiences
中文字幕：弗兰克的第一份工作是什么？昨天下午，弗兰克·霍金斯向我讲述了他的经历
英文字幕：as a young man. Before he retired, Frank was the head of a very large business company.
中文字幕：在退休之前，弗兰克是一家非常大的商业公司的负责人。
英文字幕：But as a boy, he used to work in a small shop. It was his job to repair bicycles and at that
中文字幕：但小时候，他曾在一家小店工作。修理自行车是他的工作
英文字幕：time, he used to work 14 hours a day. He saved money for years and in 1958, he bought a small
中文字幕：过去，他每天工作14个小时。他存了很多年的钱，1958年，他买了一个小
英文字幕：workshop of his own. In his 20s, Frank used to make spare parts for airplanes. At that time,
中文字幕：他自己的工作室。20多岁时，弗兰克曾为飞机制造备件。当时，
英文字幕：he had two helpers. In a few years, the small workshop had become a large factory, which employed
中文字幕：他有两个助手。几年后，这个小作坊变成了一个大工厂，雇佣了
英文字幕：728 people. Frank smiled when he remembered his hard early years and the long road to success.
中文字幕：728人。弗兰克回忆起早年的艰辛和通往成功的漫长道路时，笑了。
英文字幕：He was still smiling when the door opened and his wife came in. She wanted him to repair their
中文字幕：门打开时，他还在微笑，妻子走了进来。她想让他修理他们的
英文字幕：grandson's bicycle.
中文字幕：孙子的自行车。