英文字幕：Lesson 55. Not a gold mine.
中文字幕：课55。不是金矿。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What did the team find?
中文字幕：团队发现了什么？
英文字幕：Dreams of finding lost treasure almost came true recently.
中文字幕：最近，寻找丢失宝藏的梦想几乎成真了。
英文字幕：A new machine called the Raveela has been invented
中文字幕：一种名为Raveela的新机器被发明出来了
英文字幕：and it has been used to detect gold which has been buried in the ground.
中文字幕：它已被用于探测埋在地下的黄金。
英文字幕：The machine was used in a cave near the seashore where it is said
中文字幕：这台机器是在海边附近的一个山洞里使用的，据说那里
英文字幕：pirates used to hide gold.
中文字幕：海盗过去常常藏金子。
英文字幕：The pirates would often bury gold in the cave and then fail to collect it.
中文字幕：海盗们经常把金子埋在山洞里，然后就收不到了。
英文字幕：Armed with the new machine, a search party went into the cave
中文字幕：一支搜查队带着新机器进入了山洞
英文字幕：hoping to find buried treasure.
中文字幕：希望能找到埋藏的宝藏。
英文字幕：The leader of the party was examining the soil near the entrance to the cave
中文字幕：该党领袖正在检查洞口附近的土壤
英文字幕：when the machine showed that there was gold under the ground.
中文字幕：当机器显示地下有金子时。
英文字幕：Very excited. The party dug a hole two feet deep.
中文字幕：非常兴奋。该党挖了一个两英尺深的洞。
英文字幕：They finally found a small gold coin which was almost worthless.
中文字幕：他们终于找到了一枚几乎一文不值的小金币。
英文字幕：The party then searched the whole cave thoroughly
中文字幕：随后，一行人彻底搜查了整个洞穴
英文字幕：but did not find anything except an empty tin trunk.
中文字幕：但除了一个空锡箱，什么也没找到。
英文字幕：In spite of this many people are confident that the Raveela
中文字幕：尽管如此，许多人仍然相信拉维拉
英文字幕：may reveal something of value fairly soon.
中文字幕：可能很快就会揭示一些有价值的东西。
英文字幕：The Raveela was found in the cave.
中文字幕：拉维拉是在洞穴里发现的。