英文字幕：Lesson 94
中文字幕：第94课
英文字幕：Future Champions
中文字幕：未来冠军
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What kind of race do the children compete in?
中文字幕：孩子们参加什么样的比赛？
英文字幕：Experiments have proved that children can be instructed in swimming at a very early age.
中文字幕：实验证明，孩子们可以在很小的时候就学会游泳。
英文字幕：At a special swimming pool in Los Angeles, children become expert at holding their breath underwater even before they can walk.
中文字幕：在洛杉矶的一个特殊游泳池里，孩子们甚至在能走路之前就已经成为水下屏住呼吸的专家。
英文字幕：Babies of two months old do not appear to be reluctant to enter the water.
中文字幕：两个月大的婴儿似乎并不不愿意下水。
英文字幕：It is not long before they are so accustomed to swimming that they can pick up weights from the floor of the pool.
中文字幕：不久之后，他们就习惯了游泳，可以从游泳池的地板上举重。
英文字幕：A game that is very popular with these young swimmers is the underwater tricycle race.
中文字幕：这些年轻游泳运动员非常喜欢的一项运动是水下三轮车比赛。
英文字幕：Tricycles are lined up on the floor of the pool, seven feet underwater.
中文字幕：三轮车排在游泳池的地板上，水下七英尺。
英文字幕：The children compete against each other to reach the other end of the pool.
中文字幕：孩子们为了到达游泳池的另一端而相互竞争。
英文字幕：Many peddle their tricycles, but most of them prefer to push or drag them.
中文字幕：许多人兜售他们的三轮车，但他们中的大多数人更喜欢推或拖。
英文字幕：Some children can cover the whole length of the pool without coming up for breath even once.
中文字幕：有些孩子可以覆盖整个游泳池，甚至一次也不上来呼吸。
英文字幕：Whether they will ever become future Olympic champions, only time will tell.
中文字幕：他们是否会成为未来的奥运冠军，只有时间会证明。
英文字幕：Meanwhile, they should encourage those among us who cannot swim five yards before they are gasping for air.
中文字幕：与此同时，他们应该鼓励我们中那些在喘不过气来之前不会游五码的人。