英文字幕：Lesson 11
中文字幕：第11课
英文字幕：One good turn deserves another.
中文字幕：一个好的转折值得另一个。
英文字幕：First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：We'll pay for Tony's dinner.
中文字幕：我们会为托尼的晚餐买单。
英文字幕：I was having dinner at a restaurant when Tony's deal came in.
中文字幕：我在一家餐馆吃晚饭时，托尼的交易进来了。
英文字幕：Tony worked in a lawyer's office years ago.
中文字幕：托尼几年前在一家律师事务所工作。
英文字幕：But he is now working at a bank.
中文字幕：但他现在在一家银行工作。
英文字幕：He gets a good salary, but he always borrows money from his friends.
中文字幕：他薪水不错，但他总是向朋友借钱。
英文字幕：And never pays it back.
中文字幕：而且从不还钱。
英文字幕：Tony saw me and came and sat at the same table.
中文字幕：托尼看见我，走过来坐在同一张桌子旁。
英文字幕：He has never borrowed money from me.
中文字幕：他从未向我借钱。
英文字幕：While he was eating, I asked him to lend me £20.
中文字幕：他吃饭的时候，我请他借我20英镑。
英文字幕：And to my surprise, he gave me the money immediately.
中文字幕：令我惊讶的是，他立刻把钱给了我。
英文字幕：I have never borrowed any money from you.
中文字幕：我从未向你借过钱。
英文字幕：Tony said, so now you can pay for my dinner.
中文字幕：托尼说，现在你可以付我的晚餐了。