英文字幕：Lesson 19. Sold out. First listen and then answer the question.
中文字幕：课19。卖完了。先听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：When will the writer see the play?
中文字幕：这位作家什么时候看这出戏？
英文字幕：The play may begin at any moment, I said.
中文字幕：戏随时都可能开始，我说。
英文字幕：It may have begun already, Susan answered.
中文字幕：它可能已经开始了，苏珊回答。
英文字幕：I hurried to the ticket office.
中文字幕：我匆匆赶到售票处。
英文字幕：May I have two tickets please, I asked.
中文字幕：我问，可以给我两张票吗。
英文字幕：I'm sorry, we've sold out, the girl said.
中文字幕：对不起，我们卖完了，女孩说。
英文字幕：What a pity, Susan exclaimed.
中文字幕：真是遗憾，苏珊惊呼道。
英文字幕：Just then a man hurried to the ticket office.
中文字幕：就在这时，一个男人匆匆赶到售票处。
英文字幕：Can I return these two tickets, he asked.
中文字幕：我可以退这两张票吗？他问。
英文字幕：Certainly, the girl said.
中文字幕：当然，女孩说。
英文字幕：I went back to the ticket office at once.
中文字幕：我立刻回到售票处。
英文字幕：Could I have those two tickets please, I asked.
中文字幕：我问，能给我那两张票吗。
英文字幕：Certainly, the girl said.
中文字幕：当然，女孩说。
英文字幕：But there for next Wednesday's performance, do you still want them?
中文字幕：但是下周三的演出，你还想要吗？
英文字幕：I might as well have them.
中文字幕：我也可以拥有它们。
英文字幕：I said, sadly.
中文字幕：我悲伤地说。