英文：Lesson 133 Sensational News Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：第133课爆炸性新闻听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：What reasons did Karen Marsh give for wanting to retire?
中文：凯伦·马什想退休的原因是什么？
英文：Have you just made a new film, Miss Marsh?
中文：你刚拍了一部新电影吗，马什小姐？
英文：Yes, I have.
中文：是的，我有。
英文：Are you going to make another?
中文：你打算再做一个吗？
英文：No, I'm not.
中文：不，我没有。
英文：I'm going to retire.
中文：我要退休了。
英文：I feel very tired.
中文：我觉得很累。
英文：I don't want to make another film for a long time.
中文：我很长一段时间都不想再拍电影了。
英文：Let's buy a newspaper, Liz.
中文：我们买份报纸吧，丽兹。
英文：Listen to this.
中文：听听这个。
英文：Karen Marsh said sensational news by our reporter, Alan Jones.
中文：凯伦·马什说，这是我们的记者艾伦·琼斯的耸人听闻的消息。
英文：Karen Marsh arrived at London Airport today.
中文：凯伦·马什今天抵达伦敦机场。
英文：She was wearing a blue dress and a mink coat.
中文：她穿着一件蓝色连衣裙和一件貂皮大衣。
英文：She told me she had just made a new film.
中文：她告诉我她刚拍了一部新电影。
英文：She said she was not going to make another.
中文：她说她不会再做了。
英文：She said she was going to retire.
中文：她说她要退休了。
英文：She told reporters she felt very tired and didn't want to make another film for a long time.
中文：她告诉记者，她感到很累，很长一段时间都不想再拍电影了。
英文：I wonder why.
中文：我想知道为什么。