英文：Listen 85.
中文：听着85。
英文：Paras in the spring.
中文：春天的Paras。
英文：Listen to the tape.
中文：听录音。
英文：Then answer this question.
中文：然后回答这个问题。
英文：At what time of year did Ken visit Paris?
中文：肯在一年中的什么时候访问巴黎？
英文：Hello, Ken.
中文：你好，肯。
英文：Hi, George.
中文：嗨，乔治。
英文：Have you just been to the cinema?
中文：你刚去过电影院吗？
英文：Yes, I have.
中文：是的，我有。
英文：What's on?
中文：什么节目？
英文：Paris in the spring.
中文：春天的巴黎。
英文：Oh, I've already seen it.
中文：哦，我已经看过了。
英文：I saw it on television last year.
中文：我去年在电视上看过。
英文：It's an old film, but it's very good.
中文：这是一部老电影，但很好。
英文：Paris is a beautiful city.
中文：巴黎是一个美丽的城市。
英文：I've never been there.
中文：我从未去过那里。
英文：Have you ever been there, Ken?
中文：肯，你去过那里吗？
英文：Yes, I have.
中文：是的，我有。
英文：I was there in April.
中文：我四月份去过那里。
英文：Paris in the spring, huh?
中文：春天的巴黎，对吧？
英文：It was spring, but the weather was awful.
中文：当时是春天，但天气很糟糕。
英文：It rained all the time.
中文：一直在下雨。
英文：Just like London.
中文：就像伦敦一样。