英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：What does she mean by change in the last sentence?
中文：她最后一句话的变化是什么意思？
英文：When my husband was going into the dining room this morning, he dropped some coins on the floor.
中文：今天早上，当我丈夫走进餐厅时，他把一些硬币掉在了地板上。
英文：There were coins everywhere.
中文：到处都是硬币。
英文：We looked for them, but we could not find them all.
中文：我们找了他们，但没能全部找到。
英文：While we were having breakfast, our little boy, Tommy, found two small coins on the floor.
中文：当我们吃早餐时，我们的小男孩汤米在地板上发现了两枚小硬币。
英文：He put them both into his mouth.
中文：他把它们都放进嘴里。
英文：We both tried to get the coins, but it was too late.
中文：我们都试图拿到硬币，但为时已晚。
英文：Tommy had already swallowed them.
中文：汤米已经把它们吞下去了。
英文：Later that morning, when I was doing the housework, my husband phoned me from the office.
中文：那天早上晚些时候，当我正在做家务时，我丈夫从办公室给我打电话。
英文：«How's Tommy?» he asked.
中文：“汤米怎么样？”他问。
英文：«I don't know», I answered.
中文：“我不知道”，我回答。
英文：Tommy's been to the toilet three times this morning, but I haven't had any change yet.
中文：汤米今天早上上了三次厕所，但我还没有零钱。