英文：Lesson 101.
中文：第101课。
英文：A card from Jimmy.
中文：吉米的一张卡片。
英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：Does grandmother seem pleased to get a card from Jimmy?
中文：奶奶收到吉米的卡片高兴吗？
英文：Why?
中文：为什么？
英文：Or why not?
中文：或者为什么不呢？
英文：Read Jimmy's card to me, please, Penny.
中文：彭尼，请给我读一下吉米的卡片。
英文：I have just arrived in Scotland and I'm staying at a youth hostel.
中文：我刚到苏格兰，住在一家青年旅社。
英文：Huh?
中文：嗯？
英文：He says he's just arrived in Scotland.
中文：他说他刚到苏格兰。
英文：He says he's staying at a youth hostel.
中文：他说他住在青年旅社。
英文：You know, he's a member of the YHA.
中文：你知道，他是青年旅舍的成员。
英文：The what?
中文：什么？
英文：The YHA mum.
中文：青年旅舍的妈妈。
英文：The Youth Hostile Association.
中文：青年敌对协会。
英文：What else does he say?
中文：他还说了什么？
英文：I'll write a letter soon.
中文：我很快就会写信的。
英文：I hope you are all well.
中文：我希望你们都好。
英文：What?
中文：什么？
英文：Speak up, Penny.
中文：说吧，彭尼。
英文：I'm afraid I can't hear you.
中文：恐怕我听不见你说话。
英文：He says he'll write a letter soon.
中文：他说他很快就会写信。
英文：He hopes we are all well.
中文：他希望我们都很好。
英文：Love, Jimmy.
中文：爱你的吉米。
英文：Is that all?
中文：就这些吗？
英文：He doesn't say very much, does he?
中文：他话不多，是吗？
英文：He can't write very much on a card mum.
中文：妈妈，他不会在卡片上写太多东西。