英文：Lesson 137.
中文：课137。
英文：A pleasant dream.
中文：一个愉快的梦。
英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：What would Julie like to do if she had the money?
中文：如果朱莉有钱，她想做什么？
英文：Are you doing the football, Pools Brian?
中文：你在踢足球吗，波尔斯·布莱恩？
英文：Yes, I've nearly finished Julie.
中文：是的，我快写完朱莉了。
英文：I'm sure we'll win something this week.
中文：我确信我们本周会赢得一些东西。
英文：You always say that, but we never win anything.
中文：你总是这么说，但我们从来没有赢过任何东西。
英文：What will you do if you win a lot of money?
中文：如果你赢了很多钱，你会怎么做？
英文：If I win a lot of money, I'll buy you a mint coat.
中文：如果我赢了很多钱，我就给你买件薄荷大衣。
英文：I don't want a mint coat.
中文：我不想要薄荷色的外套。
英文：I want to see the world.
中文：我想看看世界。
英文：All right, if we win a lot of money, we'll travel around the world and we'll stay at the best hotels.
中文：好吧，如果我们赢了很多钱，我们会环游世界，住在最好的酒店。
英文：Then we'll return home and buy a big house in the country.
中文：然后我们回家，在乡下买一栋大房子。
英文：We'll have a beautiful garden and...
中文：我们将拥有一个美丽的花园，并且。。。
英文：But if we spend all that money, we'll be poor again.
中文：但如果我们花光了所有的钱，我们就会再次变穷。
英文：What will we do then?
中文：那我们该怎么办？
英文：If we spend all the money, we'll try and win the football polls again.
中文：如果我们花光所有的钱，我们将再次赢得足球民意调查。
英文：It's a pleasant dream, but everything depends on if.
中文：这是一个愉快的梦，但一切都取决于是否。