英文：Lesson 103.
中文：课103。
英文：The French test.
中文：法国测试。
英文：Listen to the tape.
中文：听录音。
英文：Then answer this question.
中文：然后回答这个问题。
英文：How long did the exam last?
中文：考试持续了多长时间？
英文：How was the exam, Richard?
中文：理查德，考试怎么样？
英文：Not too bad.
中文：还不错。
英文：I think I passed in English and mathematics.
中文：我想我的英语和数学及格了。
英文：The questions were very easy.
中文：问题很简单。
英文：How about you, Gary?
中文：你呢，加里？
英文：The English and maths papers weren't easy enough for me.
中文：英语和数学试卷对我来说不够容易。
英文：I hope I haven't failed.
中文：我希望我没有失败。
英文：I think I failed the French paper.
中文：我想我的法语试卷不及格。
英文：I could answer 16 of the questions.
中文：我可以回答16个问题。
英文：They were very easy, but I couldn't answer the rest.
中文：它们很简单，但我无法回答其余的问题。
英文：They were too difficult for me.
中文：他们对我来说太难了。
英文：French tests are awful, aren't they?
中文：法语考试很糟糕，不是吗？
英文：I hate them.
中文：我讨厌他们。
英文：I'm sure I've got a low mark.
中文：我肯定我得了低分。
英文：Oh, cheer up.
中文：哦，振作起来。
英文：Perhaps we didn't do too badly.
中文：也许我们没有做得太糟糕。
英文：The guy next to me wrote his name at the top of the paper.
中文：我旁边的那个人在报纸的顶部写下了他的名字。
英文：Yes?
中文：对？
英文：Then he sat there and looked at it for three hours.
中文：然后他坐在那里看了三个小时。
英文：He didn't write a word.
中文：他一个字也没写。
英文：Thank you.
中文：非常感谢。