英文：Lesson 77.
中文：课77。
英文：Terrible toothache.
中文：牙痛得厉害。
英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：What time of days it do you think?
中文：你觉得一天中的什么时候？
英文：How do you know?
中文：你怎么知道？
英文：Good morning, Mr.
中文：早上好，先生。
英文：Croft.
中文：克罗夫特。
英文：Good morning, Nurse.
中文：早上好，护士。
英文：I want to see the dentist, please.
中文：我想去看牙医。
英文：Do you have an appointment?
中文：你有预约吗？
英文：No, I don't.
中文：不，我没有。
英文：Is it urgent?
中文：有急事吗？
英文：Yes, it is.
中文：是的。
英文：It's very urgent.
中文：非常紧急。
英文：I feel awful.
中文：我感觉糟透了。
英文：I have a terrible toothache.
中文：我牙疼得厉害。
英文：Can you come at 10am on Monday, April 24th?
中文：你能在4月24日星期一上午10点来吗？
英文：I must see the dentist now, Nurse.
中文：护士，我现在必须去看牙医。
英文：The dentist is very busy at the moment.
中文：牙医现在很忙。
英文：Can you come at 2pm?
中文：你能在下午2点来吗？
英文：That's very late.
中文：太晚了。
英文：Can the dentist see me now?
中文：牙医现在可以见我吗？
英文：I'm afraid that he can't, Mr.
中文：恐怕他不能，先生。
英文：Croft.
中文：克罗夫特。
英文：Can't you wait till this afternoon?
中文：你就不能等到今天下午吗？
英文：I can wait, but my toothache can't.
中文：我可以等，但牙痛不能等。