英文：Lesson 129.
中文：课129。
英文：Seventy miles an hour.
中文：时速七十英里。
英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：What does Anne advise her husband to do next time?
中文：安妮建议她丈夫下次做什么？
英文：Look, Gary, that policeman's waving to you.
中文：看，加里，那个警察在向你挥手。
英文：He wants you to stop.
中文：他想让你停下来。
英文：Where do you think you are?
中文：你以为你在哪里？
英文：On a racetrack?
中文：在赛道上？
英文：You must have been driving at Seventy miles an hour.
中文：你一定是以每小时70英里的速度开车的。
英文：I can't have been.
中文：我不可能。
英文：I was doing 80 when I overtook you.
中文：我追上你的时候，我已经80了。
英文：Didn't you see the speed limit?
中文：你没看到限速吗？
英文：I'm afraid I didn't, Officer.
中文：恐怕我没有，警官。
英文：I must have been dreaming.
中文：我一定是在做梦。
英文：He wasn't dreaming, Officer.
中文：他不是在做梦，警官。
英文：I was telling him to drive slowly.
中文：我告诉他开慢点。
英文：That's why I didn't see the sign.
中文：这就是为什么我没有看到标志。
英文：Let me see your driving license.
中文：让我看看你的驾驶执照。
英文：I won't charge you this time, but you'd better not do it again.
中文：这次我不会向你收费，但你最好不要再这样做了。
英文：Thank you.
中文：非常感谢。
英文：I'll certainly be more careful.
中文：我肯定会更加小心。
英文：I told you to drive slowly, Gary.
中文：我告诉过你开慢点，加里。
英文：You always tell me to drive slowly, darling.
中文：亲爱的，你总是告诉我开慢点。
英文：Well, next time, you'd better take my advice.
中文：好吧，下次你最好听我的建议。