英文：Lesson 69.
中文：课69。
英文：The car race.
中文：赛车比赛。
英文：Listen to the tape.
中文：听录音。
英文：Then answer this question.
中文：然后回答这个问题。
英文：Which car was the winner in 1995?
中文：哪辆车是1995年的冠军？
英文：There is a car race near our town every year.
中文：每年我们镇附近都有一场汽车比赛。
英文：In 1995, there was a very big race.
中文：1995年，有一场非常激烈的比赛。
英文：There were hundreds of people there.
中文：那里有数百人。
英文：My wife and I were at the race.
中文：我和妻子参加了比赛。
英文：Our friends, Julie and Jack were there too.
中文：我们的朋友朱莉和杰克也在那里。
英文：You can see us in the crowd.
中文：你可以在人群中看到我们。
英文：We are standing on the left.
中文：我们站在左边。
英文：There were 20 cars in the race.
中文：比赛中有20辆车。
英文：There were English cars, French cars, German cars, Italian cars, American cars and Japanese cars.
中文：有英国车、法国车、德国车、意大利车、美国车和日本车。
英文：It was an exciting finish.
中文：这是一个令人兴奋的结局。
英文：The winner was Billy Stewart.
中文：获胜者是比利·斯图尔特。
英文：He was in car number 15.
中文：他在15号车里。
英文：Five other cars were just behind him.
中文：另外五辆车就在他身后。
英文：On the way home, my wife said to me, don't drive so quickly.
中文：在回家的路上，我妻子对我说，别开那么快。
英文：You are not Billy Stewart.
中文：你不是比利·斯图尔特。