英文：Lesson 131.
中文：课131。
英文：Don't be so sure.
中文：别那么肯定。
英文：Listen to the tape.
中文：听录音。
英文：Then answer this question.
中文：然后回答这个问题。
英文：What's the problem about deciding on a holiday?
中文：决定度假有什么问题？
英文：Where are you going to spend your holidays this year, Gary?
中文：加里，你今年打算在哪里度假？
英文：We may go abroad.
中文：我们可以出国。
英文：I'm not sure.
中文：我不确定。
英文：My wife wants to go to Egypt.
中文：我妻子想去埃及。
英文：I'd like to go there too.
中文：我也想去那里。
英文：We can't make up our minds.
中文：我们拿不定主意。
英文：Will you travel by sea or by air?
中文：你打算坐船还是坐飞机旅行？
英文：We may travel by sea.
中文：我们可以坐船旅行。
英文：It's cheaper, isn't it?
中文：它更便宜，不是吗？
英文：It may be cheaper, but it takes a long time.
中文：它可能更便宜，但需要很长时间。
英文：I'm sure you'll enjoy yourselves.
中文：我相信你们会玩得很开心的。
英文：Don't be so sure.
中文：别那么肯定。
英文：We might not go anywhere.
中文：我们可能哪儿也去不了。
英文：My wife always worries too much.
中文：我妻子总是担心得太多。
英文：Who's going to look after the dog?
中文：谁来照顾狗？
英文：Who's going to look after the house?
中文：谁来照看房子？
英文：Who's going to look after the garden?
中文：谁来照看花园？
英文：We have this problem every year.
中文：我们每年都有这个问题。
英文：In the end, we stay at home and look after everything.
中文：最后，我们呆在家里照顾一切。