英文：Lesson 57.
中文：课57。
英文：An unusual day.
中文：不寻常的一天。
英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：What is Mr.
中文：什么是Mr。
英文：Sawyer doing tonight?
中文：索耶今晚做什么？
英文：It is 8 o'clock.
中文：现在是8点钟。
英文：The children go to school by car every day.
中文：孩子们每天开车上学。
英文：But today, they are going to school on foot.
中文：但今天，他们步行去上学。
英文：It is 10 o'clock.
中文：现在是10点钟。
英文：Mrs.
中文：夫人
英文：Sawyer usually stays at home in the morning, but this morning, she is going to the shops.
中文：索耶通常早上呆在家里，但今天早上，她要去商店。
英文：It is 4 o'clock.
中文：现在是四点钟。
英文：In the afternoon, Mrs.
中文：下午，夫人。
英文：Sawyer usually drinks tea in the living room.
中文：索耶通常在客厅喝茶。
英文：But this afternoon, she is drinking tea in the garden.
中文：但今天下午，她正在花园里喝茶。
英文：It is 6 o'clock.
中文：现在是六点钟。
英文：In the evening, the children usually do their homework.
中文：晚上，孩子们通常做作业。
英文：But this evening, they are not doing their homework.
中文：但今晚，他们没有做作业。
英文：At the moment, they are playing in the garden.
中文：此刻，他们正在花园里玩。
英文：It is 9 o'clock.
中文：现在是九点钟。
英文：Mr.
中文：先生。
英文：Sawyer usually reads his newspaper at night, but he is not reading his newspaper tonight.
中文：索耶通常在晚上看报纸，但他今晚不看报纸。
英文：At the moment, he is reading an interesting book.
中文：此刻，他正在读一本有趣的书。