英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：Is Karen Marsh going to retire, do you think?
中文：你觉得凯伦·马什会退休吗？
英文：Are you really going to retire, Ms.
中文：你真的要退休了吗。
英文：Marsh?
中文：沼泽？
英文：I may.
中文：我可以。
英文：I can't make up my mind.
中文：我拿不定主意。
英文：I will have to ask my future husband.
中文：我得问问我未来的丈夫。
英文：He won't let me make enough of it.
中文：他不会让我受够的。
英文：Your future husband, Ms.
中文：你未来的丈夫，女士。
英文：Marsh?
中文：沼泽？
英文：Yes.
中文：对。
英文：Let me introduce him to you.
中文：让我把他介绍给你。
英文：His name is Carlos.
中文：他的名字叫卡洛斯。
英文：We're going to get married next week.
中文：我们下周就要结婚了。
英文：Look, Liz.
中文：看，丽兹。
英文：Here's another report about Karen Marsh.
中文：这是另一篇关于凯伦·马什的报道。
英文：Listen, Karen Marsh, the latest.
中文：听着，凯伦·马什，最新消息。
英文：At her London hotel today, Ms.
中文：今天在伦敦的酒店里。
英文：Marsh told reporters she might retire.
中文：马什告诉记者，她可能会退休。
英文：She said she couldn't make up her mind.
中文：她说她拿不定主意。
英文：She said she would have to ask her future husband.
中文：她说她必须问她未来的丈夫。
英文：She said her future husband would not let her make another film.
中文：她说她未来的丈夫不会让她再拍一部电影。
英文：Then she introduced us to Carlos and told us they would get married next week.
中文：然后她把我们介绍给卡洛斯，告诉我们他们下周结婚。
英文：That sensational news, isn't it Kate?
中文：那个耸人听闻的消息，不是凯特吗？
英文：It certainly is.
中文：确实如此。
英文：He'll be her sixth husband.
中文：他将成为她的第六任丈夫。
英文：Thank you.
中文：非常感谢。