英文：Lesson 73.
中文：课73。
英文：The Way to King Street.
中文：通往国王街的路。
英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：Why did the man need a phrase book?
中文：为什么这个人需要一本短语书？
英文：Last week Mrs.
中文：上周，Mrs。
英文：Mills went to London.
中文：米尔斯去了伦敦。
英文：She does not know London very well and she lost her way.
中文：她对伦敦不太熟悉，迷路了。
英文：Suddenly she saw a man near a bus stop.
中文：突然，她看见一个男人在公共汽车站附近。
英文：I can ask him the way she said to herself.
中文：我可以像她对自己说的那样问他。
英文：Excuse me, she said.
中文：对不起，她说。
英文：Can you tell me the way to King Street please?
中文：你能告诉我去国王街的路吗？
英文：The man smiled pleasantly.
中文：那人愉快地笑了。
英文：He did not understand English.
中文：他不懂英语。
英文：He spoke German.
中文：他说德语。
英文：He was a tourist.
中文：他是个游客。
英文：Then he put his hand into his pocket and took out a phrase book.
中文：然后，他把手伸进口袋，拿出一本短语书。
英文：He opened the book and found a phrase.
中文：他翻开书，发现了一个短语。
英文：He read the phrase slowly.
中文：他慢慢地读着这句话。
英文：I am sorry, he said.
中文：对不起，他说。
英文：I do not speak English.
中文：我不会说英语。