英文：Lesson 49.
中文：课49。
英文：At the butchers.
中文：在屠夫那里。
英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：What does Mr.
中文：先生做什么。
英文：Bird like?
中文：像鸟？
英文：Do you want any meat today, Mrs.
中文：夫人，你今天想吃点肉吗。
英文：Bird?
中文：鸟？
英文：Yes, please.
中文：好的，请。
英文：Do you want beef or lamb?
中文：你想要牛肉还是羊肉？
英文：Beef, please.
中文：请给我牛肉。
英文：This lamb's very good.
中文：这只小羊很好吃。
英文：I like lamb, but my husband doesn't.
中文：我喜欢羊肉，但我丈夫不喜欢。
英文：What about some steak?
中文：来点牛排怎么样？
英文：This is a nice piece.
中文：这是一件很好的作品。
英文：Give me that piece, please.
中文：请把那块给我。
英文：And a pound of mince, too.
中文：还有一磅肉馅。
英文：Do you want a chicken, Mrs.
中文：你想要一只鸡吗，夫人。
英文：Bird?
中文：鸟？
英文：They're very nice.
中文：他们非常好。
英文：No, thank you.
中文：不用了，谢谢。
英文：My husband likes steak, but he doesn't like chicken.
中文：我丈夫喜欢牛排，但他不喜欢鸡肉。
英文：To tell you the truth, Mrs.
中文：说实话，夫人。
英文：Bird, I don't like chicken either.
中文：小鸟，我也不喜欢鸡肉。