英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：Why was the mother embarrassed?
中文：妈妈为什么尴尬？
英文：Last week, my four-year-old daughter, Sally, was invited to a children's party.
中文：上周，我四岁的女儿萨莉应邀参加了一个儿童聚会。
英文：I decided to take her by train.
中文：我决定乘火车带她去。
英文：Sally was very excited because she had never travelled on a train before.
中文：萨莉很兴奋，因为她以前从未坐过火车。
英文：She sat near the window and asked questions about everything she saw.
中文：她坐在窗边，问她所看到的一切。
英文：Suddenly, a middle-aged lady got on the train and sat opposite Sally.
中文：突然，一位中年女士上了火车，坐在萨莉对面。
英文：Hello, little girl!
中文：你好，小姑娘！
英文：She said.
中文：她说。
英文：Sally did not answer, but looked at her curiously.
中文：萨莉没有回答，只是好奇地看着她。
英文：The lady was dressed in a blue coat and a large, funny hat.
中文：这位女士穿着一件蓝色外套，戴着一顶又大又滑稽的帽子。
英文：After the train had left the station, the lady opened her handbag and took out her powder compact.
中文：火车离开车站后，这位女士打开手提包，拿出粉盒。
英文：She then began to make up her face.
中文：然后她开始化妆。
英文：Why are you doing that?
中文：你为什么这么做？
英文：Sally asked.
中文：萨莉问。
英文：To make myself beautiful, the lady answered.
中文：为了让自己变得漂亮，这位女士回答。
英文：She put away her compact and smiled kindly.
中文：她收起粉盒，慈祥地笑了。
英文：But you are still ugly, Sally said.
中文：但你还是很丑，萨莉说。
英文：Sally was amused, but I was very embarrassed.
中文：萨莉很开心，但我很尴尬。