英文：Lesson 93.
中文：课93。
英文：Our new neighbour.
中文：我们的新邻居。
英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：Why is Nigel a lucky man?
中文：为什么奈杰尔是个幸运的人？
英文：Nigel is our new next-door neighbour.
中文：奈杰尔是我们的新邻居。
英文：He's a pilot.
中文：他是一名飞行员。
英文：He was in the RAF.
中文：他曾在英国皇家空军服役。
英文：He will fly to New York next month.
中文：他下个月将飞往纽约。
英文：The month after next, he'll fly to Tokyo.
中文：下个月，他将飞往东京。
英文：At the moment, he's in Madrid.
中文：目前，他在马德里。
英文：He flew to Spain a week ago.
中文：他一周前飞往西班牙。
英文：He'll return to London the week after next.
中文：他将于后周返回伦敦。
英文：He's only 41 years old, and he has already been to nearly every country in the world.
中文：他只有41岁，已经去过世界上几乎每个国家。
英文：Nigel is a very lucky man.
中文：奈杰尔是个非常幸运的人。
英文：But his wife isn't very lucky.
中文：但他的妻子不是很幸运。
英文：She usually stays at home.
中文：她通常呆在家里。