英文：Lesson 75 Uncomfortable shoes Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：第75课鞋子不舒服听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：What's wrong with the fashionable shoes?
中文：这双时髦的鞋子怎么了？
英文：Do you have any shoes like these?
中文：你有这样的鞋子吗？
英文：What size?
中文：什么尺寸？
英文：Size 5.
中文：尺码5。
英文：What color?
中文：什么颜色？
英文：Black.
中文：黑色。
英文：I'm sorry.
中文：我很抱歉。
英文：We don't have any.
中文：我们没有。
英文：But my sister bought this pair last month.
中文：但我姐姐上个月买了这双。
英文：Did she buy them here?
中文：她在这里买的吗？
英文：No, she bought them in the US.
中文：不，她是在美国买的。
英文：We had some shoes like those a month ago, but we don't have any now.
中文：一个月前我们有一些这样的鞋子，但现在没有了。
英文：Can you get a pair for me please?
中文：你能给我拿一双吗？
英文：I'm afraid that I can't.
中文：恐怕我不能。
英文：They were in fashion last year, and the year before last.
中文：它们去年和前年都很流行。
英文：But they're not in fashion this year.
中文：但它们今年并不流行。
英文：These shoes are in fashion now.
中文：这些鞋现在很流行。
英文：They look very uncomfortable.
中文：他们看起来很不舒服。
英文：They are very uncomfortable, but women always wear uncomfortable shoes.
中文：它们很不舒服，但女人总是穿不舒服的鞋子。