英文：Lesson 35.
中文：课35。
英文：Our village Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：我们村听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：Are the children coming out of the park or going into it?
中文：孩子们是走出公园还是走进公园？
英文：This is a photograph of our village.
中文：这是我们村的照片。
英文：Our village is in a valley.
中文：我们的村庄在山谷里。
英文：It is between two hills.
中文：它位于两座山之间。
英文：The village is on a river.
中文：这个村庄在河边。
英文：Here is another photograph of the village.
中文：这是村子的另一张照片。
英文：My wife and I are walking along the banks of the river.
中文：我和妻子正沿着河岸散步。
英文：We are on the left.
中文：我们在左边。
英文：There is a boy in the water.
中文：水里有个男孩。
英文：He is swimming across the river.
中文：他正在游过河。
英文：Here is another photograph.
中文：这是另一张照片。
英文：This is the school building.
中文：这是学校大楼。
英文：It is beside a park.
中文：它在公园旁边。
英文：The park is on the right.
中文：公园在右边。
英文：Some children are coming out of the building.
中文：一些孩子正从大楼里出来。
英文：Some of them are going into the park.
中文：他们中的一些人正在进入公园。
英文：The village is on the right.
中文：村子在右边。