英文：Lesson 111.
中文：第111课。
英文：The most expensive model.
中文：最贵的型号。
英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：Can Mr.
中文：可以先生。
英文：Frith buy the television on installments?
中文：弗里斯分期付款买电视？
英文：How does it work?
中文：它是如何工作的？
英文：I like this television very much.
中文：我非常喜欢这台电视。
英文：How much does it cost?
中文：这要花多少钱？
英文：It's the most expensive model in the shop.
中文：这是店里最贵的型号。
英文：It costs 500 pounds.
中文：它值500英镑。
英文：That's too expensive for us.
中文：那对我们来说太贵了。
英文：We can't afford all that money.
中文：我们负担不起那么多钱。
英文：This model's less expensive than that one.
中文：这个型号比那个便宜。
英文：It's only 300 pounds.
中文：它只有300磅。
英文：But of course, it's not as good as the expensive one.
中文：但当然，它没有昂贵的好。
英文：I don't like this model.
中文：我不喜欢这个型号。
英文：The other model's more expensive, but it's worth the money.
中文：另一种型号更贵，但物有所值。
英文：Can we buy it on installments?
中文：我们可以分期付款吗？
英文：Of course.
中文：当然。
英文：You can pay a deposit of 30 pounds and then 14 pounds a month for three years.
中文：你可以先支付30英镑的押金，然后每月支付14英镑，为期三年。
英文：Do you like it dear?
中文：亲爱的，你喜欢吗？
英文：I certainly do, but I don't like the price.
中文：我当然喜欢，但我不喜欢这个价格。
英文：You always want the best, but we can't afford it.
中文：你总是想要最好的，但我们买不起。
英文：Sometimes you think you're a millionaire.
中文：有时候你觉得自己是个百万富翁。
英文：Millionaires don't buy things on installments.
中文：百万富翁不会分期付款买东西。