英文：Lesson 51.
中文：课51。
英文：A pleasant climate.
中文：宜人的气候。
英文：Listen to the tape.
中文：听录音。
英文：Then answer this question.
中文：然后回答这个问题。
英文：Does it ever snow in Greece?
中文：希腊会下雪吗？
英文：Where do you come from?
中文：你来自哪里？
英文：I come from Greece.
中文：我来自希腊。
英文：What's the climate like in your country?
中文：你们国家的气候怎么样？
英文：It's very pleasant.
中文：这很令人愉快。
英文：What's the weather like in spring?
中文：春天的天气怎么样？
英文：It's often windy in March.
中文：三月经常刮风。
英文：It's always warm in April and May.
中文：四月和五月总是很暖和。
英文：But it rains sometimes.
中文：但有时会下雨。
英文：What's it like in summer?
中文：夏天是什么样子的？
英文：It's always hot in June, July and August.
中文：六月、七月和八月总是很热。
英文：The sun shines every day.
中文：太阳每天都在照耀。
英文：Is it cold or warm in autumn?
中文：秋天是冷还是暖？
英文：It's always warm in September and October.
中文：九月和十月总是很暖和。
英文：It's often cold in November and it rains sometimes.
中文：十一月通常很冷，有时会下雨。
英文：Is it very cold in winter?
中文：冬天很冷吗？
英文：It's often cold in December, January and February.
中文：十二月、一月和二月通常很冷。
英文：It snows sometimes.
中文：有时下雪。