英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：What is the favourite subject of conversation in England?
中文：在英国，人们最喜欢谈论的话题是什么？
英文：Where do you come from?
中文：你来自哪里？
英文：I come from England.
中文：我来自英国。
英文：What is the climate like in your country?
中文：你们国家的气候怎么样？
英文：It's mild, but it's not always pleasant.
中文：天气温和，但并不总是令人愉快。
英文：The weather is often cold in the north and windy in the east.
中文：北方的天气通常很冷，东部有风。
英文：It's often wet in the west and sometimes warm in the south.
中文：西部经常潮湿，南部有时温暖。
英文：Which seasons do you like best?
中文：你最喜欢哪个季节？
英文：I like spring and summer.
中文：我喜欢春天和夏天。
英文：The days are long and the nights are short.
中文：白天很长，夜晚很短。
英文：The sun rises early and sets late.
中文：太阳升得早，落得晚。
英文：I don't like autumn and winter.
中文：我不喜欢秋天和冬天。
英文：The days are short and the nights are long.
中文：白天很短，夜晚很长。
英文：The sun rises late and sets early.
中文：太阳升得晚，落得早。
英文：Our climate is not very good, but it's certainly interesting.
中文：我们的气候不是很好，但确实很有趣。
英文：It's our favourite subject of conversation.
中文：这是我们最喜欢的话题。