英文：Lesson 71.
中文：课71。
英文：He's awful.
中文：他太可怕了。
英文：Listen to the tape.
中文：听录音。
英文：Then answer this question.
中文：然后回答这个问题。
英文：How did Pauline answer the telephone at 9 o'clock?
中文：波林九点钟是怎么接电话的？
英文：What's Ron Maaston like, Pauline?
中文：罗恩·马斯顿是什么样的人，波林？
英文：He's awful.
中文：他太可怕了。
英文：He telephone me four times yesterday and three times the day before yesterday.
中文：他昨天给我打了四次电话，前天打了三次。
英文：He telephone the office yesterday morning and yesterday afternoon.
中文：他昨天上午和昨天下午给办公室打了电话。
英文：My boss answered the telephone.
中文：我的老板接了电话。
英文：What did your boss say to him?
中文：你的老板对他说了什么？
英文：He said, Pauline is typing letters.
中文：他说，波林正在打字。
英文：She can't speak to you now.
中文：她现在不能和你说话。
英文：Then I arrived home at six o'clock yesterday evening.
中文：然后我昨天晚上六点回到家。
英文：He telephoned again.
中文：他又打电话来了。
英文：But I didn't answer the phone.
中文：但我没有接电话。
英文：Did he telephone again last night?
中文：他昨晚又打电话了吗？
英文：Yes, he did.
中文：是的，他做到了。
英文：He telephoned at 9 o'clock.
中文：他九点钟打电话来。
英文：What did you say to him?
中文：你对他说了什么？
英文：I said, this is Pauline's mother.
中文：我说，这是波林的母亲。
英文：Please don't telephone my daughter again.
中文：请不要再给我女儿打电话了。
英文：Did he telephone again?
中文：他又打电话了吗？
英文：No, he didn't.
中文：不，他没有。
英文：Thank you.
中文：非常感谢。