英文：Lesson 107.
中文：第107课。
英文：It's too small.
中文：它太小了。
英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：What kind of dress does the lady want?
中文：这位女士想要什么样的衣服？
英文：Do you like this dress, madam?
中文：夫人，你喜欢这件衣服吗？
英文：I like the colour very much.
中文：我非常喜欢这个颜色。
英文：It's a lovely dress.
中文：这是一件漂亮的裙子。
英文：But it's too small for me.
中文：但它对我来说太小了。
英文：What about this one?
中文：这个怎么样？
英文：It's a lovely dress.
中文：这是一件漂亮的裙子。
英文：It's very smart.
中文：它非常聪明。
英文：Short skirts are in fashion now.
中文：短裙现在很流行。
英文：Would you like to try it?
中文：你想试试吗？
英文：All right.
中文：好吧。
英文：I'm afraid this green dress is too small for me as well.
中文：恐怕这件绿色连衣裙对我来说也太小了。
英文：It's smaller than the blue one.
中文：它比蓝色的小。
英文：I don't like the colour either.
中文：我也不喜欢这个颜色。
英文：It doesn't suit me at all.
中文：它一点也不适合我。
英文：I think the blue dress is prettier.
中文：我觉得那件蓝色的裙子更漂亮。
英文：Could you show me another blue dress?
中文：你能给我看看另一件蓝色连衣裙吗？
英文：I want a dress like that one, but it must be my size.
中文：我想要一件那样的裙子，但它必须是我的尺码。
英文：I'm afraid I haven't got a larger dress.
中文：恐怕我没有大一点的衣服。
英文：This is the largest dress in the shop.
中文：这是店里最大的一件衣服。