英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：Who called out to the thieves in the dark?
中文：谁在黑暗中向小偷喊话？
英文：Do you like stories?
中文：你喜欢故事吗？
英文：I want to tell you a true story.
中文：我想告诉你一个真实的故事。
英文：It happened to a friend of mine a year ago.
中文：一年前，我的一个朋友也遇到了这种情况。
英文：While my friend George was reading in bed, two thieves climbed into his kitchen.
中文：当我的朋友乔治在床上看书时，两个小偷爬进了他的厨房。
英文：After they had entered the house, they went into the dining room.
中文：他们进屋后，走进餐厅。
英文：It was very dark, so they turned on a torch.
中文：天很黑，所以他们打开了手电筒。
英文：Suddenly, they heard a voice behind them.
中文：突然，他们听到身后有个声音。
英文：What's up?
中文：怎么了？
英文：Someone called.
中文：有人打电话来。
英文：The thieves dropped the torch and ran away as quickly as they could.
中文：小偷们扔下火把，以最快的速度逃走了。
英文：George heard the noise and came downstairs quickly.
中文：乔治听到声音，迅速下楼。
英文：He turned on the light, but he couldn't see anyone.
中文：他打开了灯，但看不见任何人。
英文：The thieves had already gone.
中文：小偷已经走了。
英文：But George's parrot Henry was still there.
中文：但乔治的鹦鹉亨利还在那里。
英文：What's up, George?
中文：怎么了，乔治？
英文：he called.
中文：他打电话来。
英文：Nothing Henry George said and smiled.
中文：亨利·乔治什么也没说，只是笑了。
英文：Go back to sleep.
中文：回去睡吧。