英文：Listen to the tape.
中文：听录音。
英文：Then answer this question.
中文：然后回答这个问题。
英文：What are the Johnson's going to do at the weekend?
中文：约翰逊一家周末打算做什么？
英文：Hello.
中文：你好。
英文：Were you at the butchers?
中文：你在肉铺吗？
英文：Yes, I was.
中文：是的，我是。
英文：Were you at the butchers too?
中文：你也去肉铺了吗？
英文：No, I wasn't.
中文：不，我没有。
英文：I was at the green grocers.
中文：我在绿色杂货店。
英文：How's Jimmy today?
中文：吉米今天怎么样？
英文：He's very well, thank you.
中文：他很好，谢谢你。
英文：Was he absent from school last week?
中文：他上周没来上学吗？
英文：Yes, he was.
中文：是的，他是。
英文：He was absent on Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday and Thursday.
中文：他周一、周二、周三和周四缺席。
英文：How are you all keeping?
中文：你们都过得怎么样？
英文：Very well, thank you.
中文：很好，谢谢。
英文：We're going to spend three days in the country.
中文：我们打算在乡下呆三天。
英文：We're going to stay at my mother's for the weekend.
中文：我们打算周末住在我妈妈家。
英文：Friday, Saturday and Sunday in the country.
中文：星期五、星期六和星期日在国内。
英文：Aren't you lucky?
中文：你是不是很幸运？