英文：Lesson 121.
中文：课121。
英文：The man in a hat.
中文：戴帽子的那个人。
英文：Listen to the tape.
中文：听录音。
英文：Then answer this question.
中文：然后回答这个问题。
英文：Why didn't Caroline recognize the customer straight away?
中文：为什么卡罗琳没有马上认出这位顾客？
英文：I bought two expensive dictionaries here half an hour ago, but I forgot to take them with me.
中文：半小时前我在这里买了两本昂贵的词典，但我忘了带。
英文：Who served you, sir?
中文：谁为你服务的，先生？
英文：The lady who is standing behind that counter.
中文：站在柜台后面的那位女士。
英文：Which books did you buy?
中文：你买了哪些书？
英文：The books which are on the counter.
中文：柜台上的书。
英文：Did you serve this gentleman half an hour ago, Caroline?
中文：卡罗琳，你半小时前招待过这位先生吗？
英文：He says he's the man who bought these books.
中文：他说他就是买这些书的人。
英文：I can't remember.
中文：我不记得了。
英文：The man who I served was wearing a hat.
中文：我服务的那个人戴着一顶帽子。
英文：Have you got a hat, sir?
中文：先生，你有帽子吗？
英文：Yes, I have.
中文：是的，我有。
英文：Would you put it on, please?
中文：请你穿上好吗？
英文：All right.
中文：好吧。
英文：Is this the man that you serve, Caroline?
中文：卡罗琳，这就是你服务的人吗？
英文：Yes, I recognize him now.
中文：是的，我现在认出他了。