英文：Lesson 79.
中文：课79。
英文：Carol's shopping list.
中文：卡罗尔的购物清单。
英文：Listen to the tape.
中文：听录音。
英文：Then answer this question.
中文：然后回答这个问题。
英文：What is Carol not going to buy?
中文：卡罗尔不打算买什么？
英文：What are you doing, Carol?
中文：你在干什么，卡罗尔？
英文：I'm making a shopping list, Tom.
中文：汤姆，我在列购物清单。
英文：What do we need?
中文：我们需要什么？
英文：We need a lot of things this week.
中文：本周我们需要很多东西。
英文：I must go to the grocers.
中文：我必须去杂货店。
英文：We haven't got much tea or coffee, and we haven't got any sugar or jam.
中文：我们没有多少茶或咖啡，也没有糖或果酱。
英文：What about vegetables?
中文：蔬菜呢？
英文：I must go to the green grocers.
中文：我必须去绿色杂货店。
英文：We haven't got many tomatoes, but we've got a lot of potatoes.
中文：我们没有很多西红柿，但我们有很多土豆。
英文：I must go to the butcher's too.
中文：我也必须去肉铺。
英文：We need some meat.
中文：我们需要一些肉。
英文：We haven't got any meat at all.
中文：我们一点肉也没有。
英文：Have we got any beer and wine?
中文：我们有啤酒和葡萄酒吗？
英文：No, we haven't, and I'm not going to get any.
中文：不，我们没有，我也不会买。
英文：I hope that you've got some money.
中文：我希望你有一些钱。
英文：I haven't got much.
中文：我没有多少。
英文：Well, I haven't got much either.
中文：嗯，我也没有多少。