英文：Lesson 143.
中文：课143。
英文：A walk through the woods.
中文：穿过树林散步。
英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：What was so funny about the words on the sign?
中文：招牌上的字有什么好笑的？
英文：I live in a very old town, which is surrounded by beautiful woods.
中文：我住在一个非常古老的小镇，周围环绕着美丽的树林。
英文：It is a famous beauty spot.
中文：这是一个著名的景点。
英文：On Sundays, hundreds of people come from the city to see our town and to walk through the woods.
中文：星期天，数百人从城里来参观我们的小镇，穿过树林。
英文：Visitors have been asked to keep the woods clean and tidy.
中文：游客们被要求保持树林干净整洁。
英文：Little baskets have been placed under the trees, but people still throw their rubbish everywhere.
中文：树下已经放了小篮子，但人们仍然到处乱扔垃圾。
英文：Last Wednesday, I went for a walk in the woods.
中文：上周三，我去林中散步。
英文：What I saw made me very sad.
中文：我所看到的让我非常难过。
英文：I counted seven old cars and three old refrigerators.
中文：我数了数七辆旧车和三台旧冰箱。
英文：The litter baskets were empty and the ground was covered with pieces of paper, cigarette ends, old tires, empty bottles and rusty tins.
中文：垃圾篮是空的，地上满是纸片、烟头、旧轮胎、空瓶子和生锈的罐头。
英文：Among the rubbish, I found a sign which said, anyone who leaves litter in these woods will be prosecuted.
中文：在垃圾中，我发现了一块牌子，上面写着：任何在这些树林里乱扔垃圾的人都会被起诉。