英文：Listen 91.
中文：听91。
英文：Poor Ian.
中文：可怜的伊恩。
英文：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文：Who wanted to sell the house?
中文：谁想卖房子？
英文：As Ian sold his house yet?
中文：伊恩卖掉房子了吗？
英文：Yes, he has.
中文：是的，他有。
英文：He sold it last week.
中文：他上周卖掉了它。
英文：Has he moved to his new house yet?
中文：他搬到新家了吗？
英文：No, not yet.
中文：不，还没有。
英文：He's still here.
中文：他还在这里。
英文：He's going to move tomorrow.
中文：他明天要搬家。
英文：When?
中文：什么时候？
英文：Tomorrow morning?
中文：明天早上？
英文：No, tomorrow afternoon.
中文：不，明天下午。
英文：I'll miss him.
中文：我会想念他的。
英文：He has always been a good neighbour.
中文：他一直是个好邻居。
英文：He's a very nice person.
中文：他是个很好的人。
英文：We'll all miss him.
中文：我们都会想念他的。
英文：When will the new people move into this house?
中文：新来的人什么时候搬进这所房子？
英文：I think that they'll move in the day after tomorrow.
中文：我想他们后天会搬进来。
英文：Will you see Ian today, Jenny?
中文：珍妮，你今天要见伊恩吗？
英文：Yes, I will.
中文：是的，我会的。
英文：Please give him my regards.
中文：请代我向他问好。
英文：Poor Ian.
中文：可怜的伊恩。
英文：He didn't want to leave this house.
中文：他不想离开这所房子。
英文：No, he didn't want to leave.
中文：不，他不想离开。
英文：But his wife did.
中文：但他的妻子做到了。