英文字幕：Lesson 77. Terrible toothache.
中文字幕：课77。牙痛得厉害。
英文字幕：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文字幕：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What time of days it do you think? How do you know?
中文字幕：你觉得一天中的什么时候？你怎么知道？
英文字幕：Good morning, Mr. Croft.
中文字幕：早上好，克罗夫特先生。
英文字幕：Good morning, Nurse. I want to see the dentist, please.
中文字幕：早上好，护士。我想去看牙医。
英文字幕：Do you have an appointment? No, I don't.
中文字幕：你有预约吗？不，我没有。
英文字幕：Is it urgent? Yes, it is. It's very urgent.
中文字幕：有急事吗？是的，很紧急。
英文字幕：I feel awful. I have a terrible toothache.
中文字幕：我感觉糟透了。我牙疼得厉害。
英文字幕：Can you come at 10am on Monday, April the 24th?
中文字幕：你能在4月24日星期一上午10点来吗？
英文字幕：I must see the dentist now, Nurse.
中文字幕：护士，我现在必须去看牙医。
英文字幕：The dentist is very busy at the moment.
中文字幕：牙医现在很忙。
英文字幕：Can you come at 2pm?
中文字幕：你能在下午2点来吗？
英文字幕：That's very late. Can the dentist see me now?
中文字幕：太晚了。牙医现在可以见我吗？
英文字幕：I'm afraid that he can't, Mr. Croft.
中文字幕：恐怕他不能，克罗夫特先生。
英文字幕：Can't you wait till this afternoon?
中文字幕：你就不能等到今天下午吗？
英文字幕：I can wait, but my toothache can't.
中文字幕：我可以等，但牙痛不能等。