英文字幕：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文字幕：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Who called out to the thieves in the dark?
中文字幕：谁在黑暗中向小偷喊话？
英文字幕：Do you like stories?
中文字幕：你喜欢故事吗？
英文字幕：I want to tell you a true story.
中文字幕：我想告诉你一个真实的故事。
英文字幕：It happened to a friend of mine a year ago.
中文字幕：一年前，我的一个朋友也遇到了这种情况。
英文字幕：Tell my friend George was reading in bed.
中文字幕：告诉我的朋友乔治在床上看书。
英文字幕：Two thieves climbed into his kitchen.
中文字幕：两个小偷爬进了他的厨房。
英文字幕：After they had entered the house, they went into the dining room.
中文字幕：他们进屋后，走进餐厅。
英文字幕：It was very dark, so they turned on a torch.
中文字幕：天很黑，所以他们打开了手电筒。
英文字幕：Suddenly, they heard a voice behind them.
中文字幕：突然，他们听到身后有个声音。
英文字幕：What's up?
中文字幕：怎么了？
英文字幕：Someone called.
中文字幕：有人打电话来。
英文字幕：The thieves dropped the torch and ran away as quickly as they could.
中文字幕：小偷们扔下火把，以最快的速度逃走了。
英文字幕：George heard the noise and came downstairs quickly.
中文字幕：乔治听到声音，迅速下楼。
英文字幕：He turned on the light, but he couldn't see anyone.
中文字幕：他打开了灯，但看不见任何人。
英文字幕：The thieves had already gone.
中文字幕：小偷已经走了。
英文字幕：But George's parrot Henry was still there.
中文字幕：但乔治的鹦鹉亨利还在那里。
英文字幕：What's up, George? he called.
中文字幕：怎么了，乔治？他打电话来。
英文字幕：Nothing Henry George said and smiled.
中文字幕：亨利·乔治什么也没说，只是笑了。
英文字幕：Go back to sleep.
中文字幕：回去睡吧。