英文字幕：Lesson 137. A pleasant dream. Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文字幕：课137。一个愉快的梦。听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What would Julie like to do if she had the money?
中文字幕：如果朱莉有钱，她想做什么？
英文字幕：Are you doing the football, Pools Brian?
中文字幕：你在踢足球吗，波尔斯·布莱恩？
英文字幕：Yes, I've nearly finished Julie. I'm sure we'll win something this week.
中文字幕：是的，我快写完朱莉了。我确信我们本周会赢得一些东西。
英文字幕：You always say that, but we never win anything.
中文字幕：你总是这么说，但我们从来没有赢过任何东西。
英文字幕：What will you do if you win a lot of money?
中文字幕：如果你赢了很多钱，你会怎么做？
英文字幕：If I win a lot of money, I'll buy you a mint coat.
中文字幕：如果我赢了很多钱，我就给你买件薄荷大衣。
英文字幕：I don't want a mint coat. I want to see the world.
中文字幕：我不想要薄荷色的外套。我想看看世界。
英文字幕：All right, if we win a lot of money, we'll travel around the world
中文字幕：好吧，如果我们赢了很多钱，我们就环游世界
英文字幕：and we'll stay at the best hotels. Then we'll return home and buy a big house in the country.
中文字幕：我们会住在最好的酒店。然后我们回家，在乡下买一栋大房子。
英文字幕：We'll have a beautiful garden and...
中文字幕：我们将拥有一个美丽的花园，并且。。。
英文字幕：But if we spend all that money, we'll be poor again.
中文字幕：但如果我们花光了所有的钱，我们就会再次变穷。
英文字幕：What will we do then?
中文字幕：那我们该怎么办？
英文字幕：If we spend all the money, we'll try and win the football polls again.
中文字幕：如果我们花光所有的钱，我们将再次赢得足球民意调查。
英文字幕：It's a pleasant dream, but everything depends on if.
中文字幕：这是一个愉快的梦，但一切都取决于是否。