英文字幕：Lesson 73. The Way to King Street.
中文字幕：课73。通往国王街的路。
英文字幕：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文字幕：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why did the man need a phrase book?
中文字幕：为什么这个人需要一本短语书？
英文字幕：Last week Mrs. Mills went to London.
中文字幕：上周米尔斯夫人去了伦敦。
英文字幕：She does not know London very well and she lost her way.
中文字幕：她对伦敦不太熟悉，迷路了。
英文字幕：Suddenly she saw a man near a bus stop.
中文字幕：突然，她看见一个男人在公共汽车站附近。
英文字幕：I can ask him the way she said to herself.
中文字幕：我可以像她对自己说的那样问他。
英文字幕：Excuse me, she said.
中文字幕：对不起，她说。
英文字幕：Can you tell me the way to King Street please?
中文字幕：你能告诉我去国王街的路吗？
英文字幕：The man smiled pleasantly.
中文字幕：那人愉快地笑了。
英文字幕：He did not understand English.
中文字幕：他不懂英语。
英文字幕：He spoke German. He was a tourist.
中文字幕：他说德语。他是个游客。
英文字幕：Then he put his hand into his pocket and took out a phrase book.
中文字幕：然后，他把手伸进口袋，拿出一本短语书。
英文字幕：He opened the book and found a phrase.
中文字幕：他翻开书，发现了一个短语。
英文字幕：He read the phrase slowly.
中文字幕：他慢慢地读着这句话。
英文字幕：I am sorry, he said.
中文字幕：对不起，他说。
英文字幕：I do not speak English.
中文字幕：我不会说英语。