英文字幕：Lesson 143. A walk through the woods. Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文字幕：课143。穿过树林散步。听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What was so funny about the words on the sign?
中文字幕：招牌上的字有什么好笑的？
英文字幕：I live in a very old town, which is surrounded by beautiful woods. It is a famous beauty
中文字幕：我住在一个非常古老的小镇，周围环绕着美丽的树林。它是一位著名的美人
英文字幕：spot. On Sundays, hundreds of people come from the city to see our town and to walk through
中文字幕：地点。星期天，数百人从城里来参观我们的小镇，并漫步其中
英文字幕：the woods. Visitors have been asked to keep the woods clean and tidy. Little baskets have
中文字幕：树林。游客们被要求保持树林干净整洁。小篮子有
英文字幕：been placed under the trees, but people still throw their rubbish everywhere.
中文字幕：被放在树下，但人们仍然到处乱扔垃圾。
英文字幕：Last Wednesday, I went for a walk in the woods. What I saw made me very sad. I counted seven
中文字幕：上周三，我去林中散步。我所看到的让我非常难过。我数到七
英文字幕：old cars and three old refrigerators. The litter baskets were empty, and the ground
中文字幕：旧汽车和三台旧冰箱。垃圾篮是空的，地上
英文字幕：was covered with pieces of paper, cigarette ends, old tires, empty bottles and rusty tins.
中文字幕：到处都是纸片、烟头、旧轮胎、空瓶子和生锈的罐头。
英文字幕：Among the rubbish, I found a sign which said,
中文字幕：在垃圾堆里，我发现了一块牌子，上面写着：，
英文字幕：anyone who leaves litter in these woods will be prosecuted.
中文字幕：任何在这些树林里乱扔垃圾的人都会被起诉。