英文字幕：Listen to the tape. Then answer this question.
中文字幕：听录音。然后回答这个问题。
英文字幕：What are the Johnson's going to do at the weekend?
中文字幕：约翰逊一家周末打算做什么？
英文字幕：Hello. Were you at the butchers?
中文字幕：你好。你在肉铺吗？
英文字幕：Yes, I was. Were you at the butchers too?
中文字幕：是的，我是。你也去肉铺了吗？
英文字幕：No, I wasn't. I was at the green grocers.
中文字幕：不，我没有。我在绿色杂货店。
英文字幕：How's Jimmy today?
中文字幕：吉米今天怎么样？
英文字幕：He's very well, thank you.
中文字幕：他很好，谢谢你。
英文字幕：Was he absent from school last week?
中文字幕：他上周没来上学吗？
英文字幕：Yes, he was. He was absent on Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday and Thursday.
中文字幕：是的，他是。他周一、周二、周三和周四缺席。
英文字幕：How are you all keeping?
中文字幕：你们都过得怎么样？
英文字幕：Very well, thank you. We're going to spend three days in the country.
中文字幕：很好，谢谢。我们打算在乡下呆三天。
英文字幕：We're going to stay at my mother's for the weekend.
中文字幕：我们打算周末住在我妈妈家。
英文字幕：Friday, Saturday and Sunday in the country. Aren't you lucky?
中文字幕：星期五、星期六和星期日在国内。你是不是很幸运？