英文字幕：Listen 91.
中文字幕：听91。
英文字幕：Poor Ian.
中文字幕：可怜的伊恩。
英文字幕：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文字幕：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Who wanted to sell the house?
中文字幕：谁想卖房子？
英文字幕：As Ian sold his house yet?
中文字幕：伊恩卖掉房子了吗？
英文字幕：Yes, he has. He sold it last week.
中文字幕：是的，他有。他上周卖掉了它。
英文字幕：Has he moved to his new house yet?
中文字幕：他搬到新家了吗？
英文字幕：No, not yet. He's still here. He's going to move tomorrow.
中文字幕：不，还没有。他还在这里。他明天要搬家。
英文字幕：When? Tomorrow morning?
中文字幕：什么时候？明天早上？
英文字幕：No, tomorrow afternoon. I'll miss him.
中文字幕：不，明天下午。我会想念他的。
英文字幕：He has always been a good neighbour.
中文字幕：他一直是个好邻居。
英文字幕：He's a very nice person. We'll all miss him.
中文字幕：他是个很好的人。我们都会想念他的。
英文字幕：When will the new people move into this house?
中文字幕：新来的人什么时候搬进这所房子？
英文字幕：I think that they'll move in the day after tomorrow.
中文字幕：我想他们后天会搬进来。
英文字幕：Will you see Ian today, Jenny?
中文字幕：珍妮，你今天要见伊恩吗？
英文字幕：Yes, I will.
中文字幕：是的，我会的。
英文字幕：Please give him my regards.
中文字幕：请代我向他问好。
英文字幕：Poor Ian. He didn't want to leave this house.
中文字幕：可怜的伊恩。他不想离开这所房子。
英文字幕：No, he didn't want to leave. But his wife did.
中文字幕：不，他不想离开。但他的妻子做到了。