英文字幕：Lesson 63. Thank you, doctor.
中文字幕：课63。谢谢你，医生。
英文字幕：Listen to the tape. Then answer this question.
中文字幕：听录音。然后回答这个问题。
英文字幕：Who else is in bed today? Why?
中文字幕：今天还有谁在床上？为什么？
英文字幕：How is Jimmy today?
中文字幕：吉米今天怎么样？
英文字幕：Better thank you, doctor.
中文字幕：最好谢谢你，医生。
英文字幕：Can I see him, please, Mrs Williams?
中文字幕：威廉姆斯太太，我能见见他吗？
英文字幕：Certainly, doctor. Come upstairs.
中文字幕：当然，医生。上楼来。
英文字幕：You look very well, Jimmy. You are better now.
中文字幕：你看起来气色很好，吉米。你现在好多了。
英文字幕：But you mustn't get up yet. You must stay in bed for another two days.
中文字幕：但你还不能起床。你必须再卧床两天。
英文字幕：The boy mustn't go to school yet, Mrs Williams. And he mustn't eat rich food.
中文字幕：威廉姆斯太太，这个男孩还不能去上学。他不能吃油腻的食物。
英文字幕：Does he have a temperature, doctor?
中文字幕：医生，他发烧了吗？
英文字幕：No, he doesn't.
中文字幕：不，他没有。
英文字幕：Must he stay in bed?
中文字幕：他必须卧床休息吗？
英文字幕：Yes. He must remain in bed for another two days.
中文字幕：对。他必须再卧床两天。
英文字幕：He can get up for about two hours each day.
中文字幕：他每天可以起床大约两个小时。
英文字幕：But you must keep the room warm.
中文字幕：但你必须保持房间温暖。
英文字幕：Where's Mr Williams this evening?
中文字幕：威廉姆斯先生今晚在哪里？
英文字幕：He's in bed, doctor. Can you see him, please?
中文字幕：他在床上，医生。你能看见他吗？
英文字幕：He has a bad cold, too.
中文字幕：他也得了重感冒。