英文字幕：Lesson 131.
中文字幕：课131。
英文字幕：Don't be so sure.
中文字幕：别那么肯定。
英文字幕：Listen to the tape.
中文字幕：听录音。
英文字幕：Then answer this question.
中文字幕：然后回答这个问题。
英文字幕：What's the problem about deciding on a holiday?
中文字幕：决定度假有什么问题？
英文字幕：Where are you going to spend your holidays this year, Gary?
中文字幕：加里，你今年打算在哪里度假？
英文字幕：We may go abroad.
中文字幕：我们可以出国。
英文字幕：I'm not sure.
中文字幕：我不确定。
英文字幕：My wife wants to go to Egypt.
中文字幕：我妻子想去埃及。
英文字幕：I'd like to go there too.
中文字幕：我也想去那里。
英文字幕：We can't make up our minds.
中文字幕：我们拿不定主意。
英文字幕：Will you travel by sea or by air?
中文字幕：你打算坐船还是坐飞机旅行？
英文字幕：We may travel by sea.
中文字幕：我们可以坐船旅行。
英文字幕：It's cheaper, isn't it?
中文字幕：它更便宜，不是吗？
英文字幕：It may be cheaper, but it takes a long time.
中文字幕：它可能更便宜，但需要很长时间。
英文字幕：I'm sure you'll enjoy yourselves.
中文字幕：我相信你们会玩得很开心的。
英文字幕：Don't be so sure.
中文字幕：别那么肯定。
英文字幕：We might not go anywhere.
中文字幕：我们可能哪儿也去不了。
英文字幕：My wife always worries too much.
中文字幕：我妻子总是担心得太多。
英文字幕：Who's going to look after the dog?
中文字幕：谁来照顾狗？
英文字幕：Who's going to look after the house?
中文字幕：谁来照看房子？
英文字幕：Who's going to look after the garden?
中文字幕：谁来照看花园？
英文字幕：We have this problem every year.
中文字幕：我们每年都有这个问题。
英文字幕：In the end, we stay at home and look after everything.
中文字幕：最后，我们呆在家里照顾一切。
英文字幕：I'm going to go to the garden.
中文字幕：我要去花园。