英文字幕：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文字幕：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Is Karen Marsh going to retire, do you think?
中文字幕：你觉得凯伦·马什会退休吗？
英文字幕：Are you really going to retire, Ms. Marsh?
中文字幕：你真的要退休吗，马什女士？
英文字幕：I may. I can't make up my mind.
中文字幕：我可以。我拿不定主意。
英文字幕：I will have to ask my future husband.
中文字幕：我得问问我未来的丈夫。
英文字幕：He won't let me make enough of it.
中文字幕：他不会让我受够的。
英文字幕：He won't let me make another film.
中文字幕：他不让我再拍电影了。
英文字幕：Your future husband, Ms. Marsh?
中文字幕：你未来的丈夫，马什女士？
英文字幕：Yes, let me introduce him to you.
中文字幕：是的，让我把他介绍给你。
英文字幕：His name is Carlos.
中文字幕：他的名字叫卡洛斯。
英文字幕：We're going to get married next week.
中文字幕：我们下周就要结婚了。
英文字幕：Look, Liz, here's another report about Karen Marsh.
中文字幕：看，丽兹，这是另一篇关于凯伦·马什的报道。
英文字幕：Listen, Karen Marsh, the latest.
中文字幕：听着，凯伦·马什，最新消息。
英文字幕：At her London hotel today, Ms. Marsh told reporters she might retire.
中文字幕：今天在伦敦的酒店，马什女士告诉记者，她可能会退休。
英文字幕：She said she couldn't make up her mind.
中文字幕：她说她拿不定主意。
英文字幕：She said she would have to ask her future husband.
中文字幕：她说她必须问她未来的丈夫。
英文字幕：She said her future husband would not let her make another film.
中文字幕：她说她未来的丈夫不会让她再拍一部电影。
英文字幕：Then she introduced us to Carlos and told us they would get married next week.
中文字幕：然后她把我们介绍给卡洛斯，告诉我们他们下周结婚。
英文字幕：That sensational news, isn't it Kate?
中文字幕：那个耸人听闻的消息，不是凯特吗？
英文字幕：It certainly is.
中文字幕：确实如此。
英文字幕：He'll be her sixth husband.
中文字幕：他将成为她的第六任丈夫。