英文字幕：Lesson 71. He's awful. Listen to the tape. Then answer this question.
中文字幕：课71。他太可怕了。听录音。然后回答这个问题。
英文字幕：How did Pauline answer the telephone at 9 o'clock?
中文字幕：波林九点钟是怎么接电话的？
英文字幕：What's Ron Maaston like, Pauline?
中文字幕：罗恩·马斯顿是什么样的人，波林？
英文字幕：He's awful. He telephone me four times yesterday and three times the day before yesterday.
中文字幕：他太可怕了。他昨天给我打了四次电话，前天打了三次。
英文字幕：He telephone the office yesterday morning and yesterday afternoon.
中文字幕：他昨天上午和昨天下午给办公室打了电话。
英文字幕：My boss answered the telephone.
中文字幕：我的老板接了电话。
英文字幕：What did your boss say to him?
中文字幕：你的老板对他说了什么？
英文字幕：He said, Pauline is typing letters. She can't speak to you now.
中文字幕：他说，波林正在打字。她现在不能和你说话。
英文字幕：Then I arrived home at six o'clock yesterday evening.
中文字幕：然后我昨天晚上六点回到家。
英文字幕：He telephoned again. But I didn't answer the phone.
中文字幕：他又打电话来了。但我没有接电话。
英文字幕：Did he telephone again last night?
中文字幕：他昨晚又打电话了吗？
英文字幕：Yes, he did. He telephoned at 9 o'clock.
中文字幕：是的，他做到了。他九点钟打电话来。
英文字幕：What did you say to him?
中文字幕：你对他说了什么？
英文字幕：I said, this is Pauline's mother.
中文字幕：我说，这是波林的母亲。
英文字幕：Please don't telephone my daughter again.
中文字幕：请不要再给我女儿打电话了。
英文字幕：Did he telephone again?
中文字幕：他又打电话了吗？
英文字幕：No, he didn't.
中文字幕：不，他没有。
英文字幕：You're not going to be able to answer the telephone.
中文字幕：你将无法接听电话。