英文字幕：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文字幕：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：Why was the mother embarrassed?
中文字幕：妈妈为什么尴尬？
英文字幕：Last week, my four-year-old daughter, Sally, was invited to a children's party.
中文字幕：上周，我四岁的女儿萨莉应邀参加了一个儿童聚会。
英文字幕：I decided to take her by train.
中文字幕：我决定乘火车带她去。
英文字幕：Sally was very excited because she had never travelled on a train before.
中文字幕：萨莉很兴奋，因为她以前从未坐过火车。
英文字幕：She sat near the window and asked questions about everything she saw.
中文字幕：她坐在窗边，问她所看到的一切。
英文字幕：Suddenly, a middle-aged lady got on the train and sat opposite Sally.
中文字幕：突然，一位中年女士上了火车，坐在萨莉对面。
英文字幕：Hello, little girl! She said.
中文字幕：你好，小姑娘！她说。
英文字幕：Sally did not answer, but looked at her curiously.
中文字幕：萨莉没有回答，只是好奇地看着她。
英文字幕：The lady was dressed in a blue coat and a large, funny hat.
中文字幕：这位女士穿着一件蓝色外套，戴着一顶又大又滑稽的帽子。
英文字幕：After the train had left the station, the lady opened her handbag and took out her powder compact.
中文字幕：火车离开车站后，这位女士打开手提包，拿出粉盒。
英文字幕：She then began to make up her face.
中文字幕：然后她开始化妆。
英文字幕：Why are you doing that?
中文字幕：你为什么这么做？
英文字幕：Sally asked.
中文字幕：萨莉问。
英文字幕：To make myself beautiful, the lady answered.
中文字幕：为了让自己变得漂亮，这位女士回答。
英文字幕：She put away her compact and smiled kindly.
中文字幕：她收起粉盒，慈祥地笑了。
英文字幕：But you are still ugly.
中文字幕：但你仍然很丑。
英文字幕：Sally said.
中文字幕：萨莉说。
英文字幕：Sally was amused, but I was very embarrassed.
中文字幕：萨莉很开心，但我很尴尬。
英文字幕：Surprised?
中文字幕：惊讶？