英文字幕：Listen 87. A car crash. Listen to the tape. Then answer this question.
中文字幕：听着87。车祸。听录音。然后回答这个问题。
英文字幕：Can the mechanics repair Mr. Woods' car?
中文字幕：机械师能修理伍兹先生的车吗？
英文字幕：Is my car ready yet? I don't know, sir. What's the number of your car?
中文字幕：我的车准备好了吗？我不知道，先生。你的汽车号码是多少？
英文字幕：L, F, Z, 3, 1, 2, G. When did you bring it to us?
中文字幕：L、 F，Z，3，1，2，G。你什么时候给我们带来的？
英文字幕：I brought it here three days ago. Oh yes, I remember now.
中文字幕：我三天前把它带来的。哦，是的，我现在想起来了。
英文字幕：Have your mechanics finished yet? No, they're still working on it. Let's go into the garage
中文字幕：你的机修工做完了吗？不，他们还在做。我们去车库吧
英文字幕：and have a look at it. Isn't that your car? Well, it was my car.
中文字幕：看看它。那不是你的车吗？嗯，那是我的车。
英文字幕：Didn't you have a crash? That's right. I drove it into a lamppost.
中文字幕：你不是撞车了吗？这是正确的。我把它撞到灯柱上了。
英文字幕：Can your mechanics repair it? Well, they're trying to repair it, sir.
中文字幕：你的机械师能修理它吗？他们正在努力修复它，先生。
英文字幕：But to tell you the truth, you need a new car.
中文字幕：但说实话，你需要一辆新车。