英文字幕：Lesson 79.
中文字幕：课79。
英文字幕：Carol's shopping list.
中文字幕：卡罗尔的购物清单。
英文字幕：Listen to the tape.
中文字幕：听录音。
英文字幕：Then answer this question.
中文字幕：然后回答这个问题。
英文字幕：What is Carol not going to buy?
中文字幕：卡罗尔不打算买什么？
英文字幕：What are you doing, Carol?
中文字幕：你在干什么，卡罗尔？
英文字幕：I'm making a shopping list, Tom.
中文字幕：汤姆，我在列购物清单。
英文字幕：What do we need?
中文字幕：我们需要什么？
英文字幕：We need a lot of things this week.
中文字幕：本周我们需要很多东西。
英文字幕：I must go to the grocers.
中文字幕：我必须去杂货店。
英文字幕：We haven't got much tea or coffee, and we haven't got any sugar or jam.
中文字幕：我们没有多少茶或咖啡，也没有糖或果酱。
英文字幕：What about vegetables?
中文字幕：蔬菜呢？
英文字幕：I must go to the green grocers.
中文字幕：我必须去绿色杂货店。
英文字幕：We haven't got many tomatoes, but we've got a lot of potatoes.
中文字幕：我们没有很多西红柿，但我们有很多土豆。
英文字幕：I must go to the butchers too.
中文字幕：我也必须去肉铺。
英文字幕：We need some meat.
中文字幕：我们需要一些肉。
英文字幕：We haven't got any meat at all.
中文字幕：我们一点肉也没有。
英文字幕：Have we got any beer and wine?
中文字幕：我们有啤酒和葡萄酒吗？
英文字幕：No, we haven't, and I'm not going to get any.
中文字幕：不，我们没有，我也不会买。
英文字幕：I hope that you've got some money.
中文字幕：我希望你有一些钱。
英文字幕：I haven't got much.
中文字幕：我没有多少。
英文字幕：Well, I haven't got much either.
中文字幕：嗯，我也没有多少。
英文字幕：I'm going to get some coffee.
中文字幕：我去喝点咖啡。