英文字幕：Lesson 133 Sensational News
中文字幕：第133课耸人听闻的新闻
英文字幕：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文字幕：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What reasons did Karen Marsh give for wanting to retire?
中文字幕：凯伦·马什想退休的原因是什么？
英文字幕：Have you just made a new film, Miss Marsh?
中文字幕：你刚拍了一部新电影吗，马什小姐？
英文字幕：Yes, I have.
中文字幕：是的，我有。
英文字幕：Are you going to make another?
中文字幕：你打算再做一个吗？
英文字幕：No, I'm not. I'm going to retire.
中文字幕：不，我没有。我要退休了。
英文字幕：I feel very tired.
中文字幕：我觉得很累。
英文字幕：I don't want to make another film for a long time.
中文字幕：我很长一段时间都不想再拍电影了。
英文字幕：Let's buy a newspaper, Liz.
中文字幕：我们买份报纸吧，丽兹。
英文字幕：Listen to this.
中文字幕：听听这个。
英文字幕：Karen Marsh said sensational news by our reporter, Alan Jones.
中文字幕：凯伦·马什说，这是我们的记者艾伦·琼斯的耸人听闻的消息。
英文字幕：Karen Marsh arrived at London Airport today.
中文字幕：凯伦·马什今天抵达伦敦机场。
英文字幕：She was wearing a blue dress and a mink coat.
中文字幕：她穿着一件蓝色连衣裙和一件貂皮大衣。
英文字幕：She told me she had just made a new film.
中文字幕：她告诉我她刚拍了一部新电影。
英文字幕：She said she was not going to make another.
中文字幕：她说她不会再做了。
英文字幕：She said she was going to retire.
中文字幕：她说她要退休了。
英文字幕：She told reporters she felt very tired and didn't want to make another film for a long time.
中文字幕：她告诉记者，她感到很累，很长一段时间都不想再拍电影了。
英文字幕：I wonder why.
中文字幕：我想知道为什么。