英文字幕：Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
中文字幕：听录音，然后回答问题。
英文字幕：What does she mean by change in the last sentence?
中文字幕：她最后一句话的变化是什么意思？
英文字幕：When my husband was going into the dining room this morning, he dropped some coins on the
中文字幕：今天早上，当我丈夫走进餐厅时，他往桌子上扔了一些硬币
英文字幕：floor.
中文字幕：地板。
英文字幕：They were coins everywhere.
中文字幕：到处都是硬币。
英文字幕：We looked for them, but we could not find them all.
中文字幕：我们找了他们，但没能全部找到。
英文字幕：While we were having breakfast, our little boy, Tommy, found two small coins on the floor.
中文字幕：当我们吃早餐时，我们的小男孩汤米在地板上发现了两枚小硬币。
英文字幕：He put them both into his mouth.
中文字幕：他把它们都放进嘴里。
英文字幕：We both tried to get the coins, but it was too late.
中文字幕：我们都试图拿到硬币，但为时已晚。
英文字幕：Tommy had already swallowed them.
中文字幕：汤米已经把它们吞下去了。
英文字幕：To that morning, when I was doing the housework, my husband phoned me from the office.
中文字幕：直到那天早上，当我在做家务时，我丈夫从办公室给我打电话。
英文字幕：How's Tommy?
中文字幕：汤米怎么样了？
英文字幕：He asked.
中文字幕：他问。
英文字幕：I don't know, I answered.
中文字幕：我不知道，我回答。
英文字幕：Tommy's been to the toilet three times this morning, but I haven't had any change yet.
中文字幕：汤米今天早上上了三次厕所，但我还没有零钱。
英文字幕：I'm sorry.
中文字幕：我很抱歉。