英文字幕：Lesson 69. The car race.
中文字幕：课69。赛车比赛。
英文字幕：Listen to the tape. Then answer this question.
中文字幕：听录音。然后回答这个问题。
英文字幕：Which car was the winner in 1995?
中文字幕：哪辆车是1995年的冠军？
英文字幕：There is a car race near our town every year.
中文字幕：每年我们镇附近都有一场汽车比赛。
英文字幕：In 1995, there was a very big race.
中文字幕：1995年，有一场非常激烈的比赛。
英文字幕：There were hundreds of people there.
中文字幕：那里有数百人。
英文字幕：My wife and I were at the race.
中文字幕：我和妻子参加了比赛。
英文字幕：Our friends, Julie and Jack were there too.
中文字幕：我们的朋友朱莉和杰克也在那里。
英文字幕：You can see us in the crowd.
中文字幕：你可以在人群中看到我们。
英文字幕：We are standing on the left.
中文字幕：我们站在左边。
英文字幕：There were 20 cars in the race.
中文字幕：比赛中有20辆车。
英文字幕：There were English cars, French cars, German cars,
中文字幕：有英国车、法国车、德国车，
英文字幕：Italian cars, American cars and Japanese cars.
中文字幕：意大利汽车、美国汽车和日本汽车。
英文字幕：It was an exciting finish.
中文字幕：这是一个令人兴奋的结局。
英文字幕：The winner was Billy Stewart.
中文字幕：获胜者是比利·斯图尔特。
英文字幕：He was in car number 15.
中文字幕：他在15号车里。
英文字幕：Five other cars were just behind him.
中文字幕：另外五辆车就在他身后。
英文字幕：On the way home, my wife said to me,
中文字幕：在回家的路上，我妻子对我说：，
英文字幕：don't drive so quickly.
中文字幕：别开那么快。
英文字幕：You are not Billy Stewart.
中文字幕：你不是比利·斯图尔特。