英文字幕：Lesson 103. The French test.
中文字幕：课103。法国测试。
英文字幕：Listen to the tape. Then answer this question.
中文字幕：听录音。然后回答这个问题。
英文字幕：How long did the exam last?
中文字幕：考试持续了多长时间？
英文字幕：How was the exam, Richard?
中文字幕：理查德，考试怎么样？
英文字幕：Not too bad. I think I passed in English and mathematics.
中文字幕：还不错。我想我的英语和数学及格了。
英文字幕：The questions were very easy. How about you, Gary?
中文字幕：问题很简单。你呢，加里？
英文字幕：The English and maths papers weren't easy enough for me.
中文字幕：英语和数学试卷对我来说不够容易。
英文字幕：I hope I haven't failed.
中文字幕：我希望我没有失败。
英文字幕：I think I failed the French paper. I could answer 16 of the questions.
中文字幕：我想我的法语试卷不及格。我可以回答16个问题。
英文字幕：They were very easy, but I couldn't answer the rest.
中文字幕：它们很简单，但我无法回答其余的问题。
英文字幕：They were too difficult for me.
中文字幕：他们对我来说太难了。
英文字幕：The French tests are awful, aren't they?
中文字幕：法国的考试很糟糕，不是吗？
英文字幕：I hate them. I'm sure I've got a low mark.
中文字幕：我讨厌他们。我肯定我得了低分。
英文字幕：Oh, cheer up. Perhaps we didn't do too badly.
中文字幕：哦，振作起来。也许我们没有做得太糟糕。
英文字幕：The guy next to me wrote his name at the top of the paper.
中文字幕：我旁边的那个人在报纸的顶部写下了他的名字。
英文字幕：Yes?
中文字幕：对？
英文字幕：Then he sat there and looked at it for three hours.
中文字幕：然后他坐在那里看了三个小时。
英文字幕：He didn't write a word.
中文字幕：他一个字也没写。