Lesson 57.
An unusual day.
Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
What is Mr.
Sawyer doing tonight?
It is 8 o'clock.
The children go to school by car every day.
But today, they are going to school on foot.
It is 10 o'clock.
Mrs.
Sawyer usually stays at home in the morning, but this morning, she is going to the shops.
It is 4 o'clock.
In the afternoon, Mrs.
Sawyer usually drinks tea in the living room.
But this afternoon, she is drinking tea in the garden.
It is 6 o'clock.
In the evening, the children usually do their homework.
But this evening, they are not doing their homework.
At the moment, they are playing in the garden.
It is 9 o'clock.
Mr.
Sawyer usually reads his newspaper at night, but he is not reading his newspaper tonight.
At the moment, he is reading an interesting book.