Lesson 139.
Is that you, John?
Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
Which John Smith does Graham Turner think he is talking to?
Is that you, John?
Yes, speaking.
Tell Mary will be late for dinner this evening.
I'm afraid I don't understand.
Hasn't Mary told you?
She invited Charlotte and me to dinner this evening.
I said I would be at your house at six o'clock, but the boss wants me to do some extra work.
I'll have to stay at the office.
I don't know when I'll finish.
Oh, and by the way, my wife wants to know if Mary needs any help.
I don't know what you're talking about.
That is John Smith, isn't it?
Yes, I'm John Smith.
You are John Smith, the engineer, aren't you?
That's right.
You work for the overseas engineering company, don't you?
No, I don't.
I'm John Smith, the telephone engineer, and I'm repairing your telephone line.