Lesson 79.
Carol's shopping list.
Listen to the tape.
Then answer this question.
What is Carol not going to buy?
What are you doing, Carol?
I'm making a shopping list, Tom.
What do we need?
We need a lot of things this week.
I must go to the grocers.
We haven't got much tea or coffee, and we haven't got any sugar or jam.
What about vegetables?
I must go to the green grocers.
We haven't got many tomatoes, but we've got a lot of potatoes.
I must go to the butcher's too.
We need some meat.
We haven't got any meat at all.
Have we got any beer and wine?
No, we haven't, and I'm not going to get any.
I hope that you've got some money.
I haven't got much.
Well, I haven't got much either.