Lesson 111.
The most expensive model.
Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
Can Mr.
Frith buy the television on installments?
How does it work?
I like this television very much.
How much does it cost?
It's the most expensive model in the shop.
It costs 500 pounds.
That's too expensive for us.
We can't afford all that money.
This model's less expensive than that one.
It's only 300 pounds.
But of course, it's not as good as the expensive one.
I don't like this model.
The other model's more expensive, but it's worth the money.
Can we buy it on installments?
Of course.
You can pay a deposit of 30 pounds and then 14 pounds a month for three years.
Do you like it dear?
I certainly do, but I don't like the price.
You always want the best, but we can't afford it.
Sometimes you think you're a millionaire.
Millionaires don't buy things on installments.