Lesson 75 Uncomfortable shoes Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
What's wrong with the fashionable shoes?
Do you have any shoes like these?
What size?
Size 5.
What color?
Black.
I'm sorry.
We don't have any.
But my sister bought this pair last month.
Did she buy them here?
No, she bought them in the US.
We had some shoes like those a month ago, but we don't have any now.
Can you get a pair for me please?
I'm afraid that I can't.
They were in fashion last year, and the year before last.
But they're not in fashion this year.
These shoes are in fashion now.
They look very uncomfortable.
They are very uncomfortable, but women always wear uncomfortable shoes.