Lesson 115.
Knock, knock.
Listen to the tape.
Then answer this question.
What does Jim have to drink?
Isn't there anyone at home?
I'll knock again, Helen.
Everything's very quiet.
I'm sure there's no one at home.
But that's impossible.
Carolyn Tom invited us to lunch.
Look through the window.
Can you see anything?
Nothing at all.
Let's try the back door.
Look, everyone's in the garden.
Hello, Helen.
Hello, Jim.
Everybody wants to have lunch in the garden.
It's nice and warm out here.
Come and have something to drink.
Thanks, Carol.
May I have a glass of beer, please?
Beer?
There's none left.
You can have some lemonade.
Lemonade?
Don't believe her, Jim.
She's only joking.
Have some beer.