Lesson 137.
A pleasant dream.
Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
What would Julie like to do if she had the money?
Are you doing the football, Pools Brian?
Yes, I've nearly finished Julie.
I'm sure we'll win something this week.
You always say that, but we never win anything.
What will you do if you win a lot of money?
If I win a lot of money, I'll buy you a mint coat.
I don't want a mint coat.
I want to see the world.
All right, if we win a lot of money, we'll travel around the world and we'll stay at the best hotels.
Then we'll return home and buy a big house in the country.
We'll have a beautiful garden and...
But if we spend all that money, we'll be poor again.
What will we do then?
If we spend all the money, we'll try and win the football polls again.
It's a pleasant dream, but everything depends on if.