Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
What does she mean by change in the last sentence?
When my husband was going into the dining room this morning, he dropped some coins on the floor.
There were coins everywhere.
We looked for them, but we could not find them all.
While we were having breakfast, our little boy, Tommy, found two small coins on the floor.
He put them both into his mouth.
We both tried to get the coins, but it was too late.
Tommy had already swallowed them.
Later that morning, when I was doing the housework, my husband phoned me from the office.
«How's Tommy?» he asked.
«I don't know», I answered.
Tommy's been to the toilet three times this morning, but I haven't had any change yet.