Lesson 83.
Going on holiday.
Listen to the tape.
Then answer this question.
Where did Sam go for his holiday this year?
Hello, Sam.
Come in.
Hi, Sam.
We're having lunch.
Do you want to have lunch with us?
No, thank you, Tom.
I've already had lunch.
I had lunch at half past twelve.
Have a cup of coffee then.
I've just had a cup, thank you.
I had one after my lunch.
Let's go into the living room, Carol.
We can have our coffee there.
Excuse the mess, Sam.
This room's very untidy.
We're packing our suitcases.
We're going to leave tomorrow.
Tom and I are going to have a holiday.
Aren't you lucky?
When are you going to have a holiday, Sam?
I don't know.
I've already had my holiday this year.
Where did you go?
I stayed at home.