Lesson 101.
A card from Jimmy.
Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
Does grandmother seem pleased to get a card from Jimmy?
Why?
Or why not?
Read Jimmy's card to me, please, Penny.
I have just arrived in Scotland and I'm staying at a youth hostel.
Huh?
He says he's just arrived in Scotland.
He says he's staying at a youth hostel.
You know, he's a member of the YHA.
The what?
The YHA mum.
The Youth Hostile Association.
What else does he say?
I'll write a letter soon.
I hope you are all well.
What?
Speak up, Penny.
I'm afraid I can't hear you.
He says he'll write a letter soon.
He hopes we are all well.
Love, Jimmy.
Is that all?
He doesn't say very much, does he?
He can't write very much on a card mum.