Lesson 129.
Seventy miles an hour.
Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
What does Anne advise her husband to do next time?
Look, Gary, that policeman's waving to you.
He wants you to stop.
Where do you think you are?
On a racetrack?
You must have been driving at Seventy miles an hour.
I can't have been.
I was doing 80 when I overtook you.
Didn't you see the speed limit?
I'm afraid I didn't, Officer.
I must have been dreaming.
He wasn't dreaming, Officer.
I was telling him to drive slowly.
That's why I didn't see the sign.
Let me see your driving license.
I won't charge you this time, but you'd better not do it again.
Thank you.
I'll certainly be more careful.
I told you to drive slowly, Gary.
You always tell me to drive slowly, darling.
Well, next time, you'd better take my advice.