Lesson 63.
Thank you, doctor.
Listen to the tape.
Then answer this question.
Who else is in bed today?
Why?
How is Jimmy today?
Better thank you, doctor.
Can I see him, please, Mrs Williams?
Certainly, doctor.
Come upstairs.
You look very well, Jimmy.
You are better now.
But you mustn't get up yet.
You must stay in bed for another two days.
The boy mustn't go to school yet, Mrs Williams.
And he mustn't eat rich food.
Does he have a temperature, doctor?
No, he doesn't.
Must he stay in bed?
Yes.
He must remain in bed for another two days.
He can get up for about two hours each day.
But you must keep the room warm.
Where's Mr Williams this evening?
He's in bed, doctor.
Can you see him, please?
He has a bad cold, too.