Lesson 143.
A walk through the woods.
Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
What was so funny about the words on the sign?
I live in a very old town, which is surrounded by beautiful woods.
It is a famous beauty spot.
On Sundays, hundreds of people come from the city to see our town and to walk through the woods.
Visitors have been asked to keep the woods clean and tidy.
Little baskets have been placed under the trees, but people still throw their rubbish everywhere.
Last Wednesday, I went for a walk in the woods.
What I saw made me very sad.
I counted seven old cars and three old refrigerators.
The litter baskets were empty and the ground was covered with pieces of paper, cigarette ends, old tires, empty bottles and rusty tins.
Among the rubbish, I found a sign which said, anyone who leaves litter in these woods will be prosecuted.