Lesson 107.
It's too small.
Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
What kind of dress does the lady want?
Do you like this dress, madam?
I like the colour very much.
It's a lovely dress.
But it's too small for me.
What about this one?
It's a lovely dress.
It's very smart.
Short skirts are in fashion now.
Would you like to try it?
All right.
I'm afraid this green dress is too small for me as well.
It's smaller than the blue one.
I don't like the colour either.
It doesn't suit me at all.
I think the blue dress is prettier.
Could you show me another blue dress?
I want a dress like that one, but it must be my size.
I'm afraid I haven't got a larger dress.
This is the largest dress in the shop.