Lesson 71.
He's awful.
Listen to the tape.
Then answer this question.
How did Pauline answer the telephone at 9 o'clock?
What's Ron Maaston like, Pauline?
He's awful.
He telephone me four times yesterday and three times the day before yesterday.
He telephone the office yesterday morning and yesterday afternoon.
My boss answered the telephone.
What did your boss say to him?
He said, Pauline is typing letters.
She can't speak to you now.
Then I arrived home at six o'clock yesterday evening.
He telephoned again.
But I didn't answer the phone.
Did he telephone again last night?
Yes, he did.
He telephoned at 9 o'clock.
What did you say to him?
I said, this is Pauline's mother.
Please don't telephone my daughter again.
Did he telephone again?
No, he didn't.
Thank you.