Lesson 103.
The French test.
Listen to the tape.
Then answer this question.
How long did the exam last?
How was the exam, Richard?
Not too bad.
I think I passed in English and mathematics.
The questions were very easy.
How about you, Gary?
The English and maths papers weren't easy enough for me.
I hope I haven't failed.
I think I failed the French paper.
I could answer 16 of the questions.
They were very easy, but I couldn't answer the rest.
They were too difficult for me.
French tests are awful, aren't they?
I hate them.
I'm sure I've got a low mark.
Oh, cheer up.
Perhaps we didn't do too badly.
The guy next to me wrote his name at the top of the paper.
Yes?
Then he sat there and looked at it for three hours.
He didn't write a word.
Thank you.