Lesson 69.
The car race.
Listen to the tape.
Then answer this question.
Which car was the winner in 1995?
There is a car race near our town every year.
In 1995, there was a very big race.
There were hundreds of people there.
My wife and I were at the race.
Our friends, Julie and Jack were there too.
You can see us in the crowd.
We are standing on the left.
There were 20 cars in the race.
There were English cars, French cars, German cars, Italian cars, American cars and Japanese cars.
It was an exciting finish.
The winner was Billy Stewart.
He was in car number 15.
Five other cars were just behind him.
On the way home, my wife said to me, don't drive so quickly.
You are not Billy Stewart.