Lesson 121.
The man in a hat.
Listen to the tape.
Then answer this question.
Why didn't Caroline recognize the customer straight away?
I bought two expensive dictionaries here half an hour ago, but I forgot to take them with me.
Who served you, sir?
The lady who is standing behind that counter.
Which books did you buy?
The books which are on the counter.
Did you serve this gentleman half an hour ago, Caroline?
He says he's the man who bought these books.
I can't remember.
The man who I served was wearing a hat.
Have you got a hat, sir?
Yes, I have.
Would you put it on, please?
All right.
Is this the man that you serve, Caroline?
Yes, I recognize him now.