Listen to the tape, then answer this question.
Is Karen Marsh going to retire, do you think?
Are you really going to retire, Ms.
Marsh?
I may.
I can't make up my mind.
I will have to ask my future husband.
He won't let me make enough of it.
Your future husband, Ms.
Marsh?
Yes.
Let me introduce him to you.
His name is Carlos.
We're going to get married next week.
Look, Liz.
Here's another report about Karen Marsh.
Listen, Karen Marsh, the latest.
At her London hotel today, Ms.
Marsh told reporters she might retire.
She said she couldn't make up her mind.
She said she would have to ask her future husband.
She said her future husband would not let her make another film.
Then she introduced us to Carlos and told us they would get married next week.
That sensational news, isn't it Kate?
It certainly is.
He'll be her sixth husband.
Thank you.